One shot
two shots in the night and they're gone
and he's all left alone,
he's just
one boy
two dead at his feet
and the blood stains the street
and there's nothing
no, there's nothing he can -
do...
except be the baddest man that there's ever been
He's gonna carry the weight
He's gonna get revenge
He's got Gotham
He'll never refuse 'em
He's got bat nunchucks,
and boy, he knows how to use 'em!
one man
one bat in a cave
with a city to save
He makes
one vow
two lifes he will lead,
he'll protect those in need
and there's nothing
no, there's nothing
he can't
do...
Harr!
Alright, yous goons!
Take these here drugs
put them in that empty guns
and then hand them out to those gabling prostitutes. Yay, yay, yay.
I don't know about this...
Should we really be doing these illegal activities...
In a children's hospital for orphans?
Why not?
...[???]...
When he got iced.
By the bat.
Shut your ...[???]..., Matches! There ain't no such thing as a bat!
Now hurry up! We got lots more racketeering to do tonight. [laughs]
Well, ain't it a good thing I brought - my racket?
Oh, Matches!
You make me laugh like nobody else! [reference to: Starship from team starkid]
Now what do you say we go grab a delicious...
What was that?
It sounded just like a bat.
Damn! What happened to the light?
I can't sees nothing! It's like I'm blind.
Blind as a...
A bat!
Fractured jar!
broken rib!
...[???]...
Shattered tibia!
He? What tibia?
Oh, my fucking tibia!
That'll teach you to ...[???]...
Support your families like the rest of us.
Be born billionairs.
Teargas!
Ah! Commissioner Gordon!
Get a load of this!
Another pair of goons hanging upside down from a lamppost!
Uh, man!
Who could have done this?
What do you think, Dr. Meridian?
Hm. In all my years as an animal psychologist I've only encountered one creature to exhibit such behavior.
A bat!
Geez!
Commissioner! Commissioner, those goones we cut down, they had a note attached to 'em!
Oh, well, maybe we should read it!
It says: Criminals of Gotham fear me!
Oh!
And then it's signed:
Bruce Wayne!
But then that's crossed out and underneath it's written...
B@man!
And he's catching those crooks with his grappling hooks
He's here to saved the day, it makes me want to say...
Holy musical B@man!
Whoa!
Commissioner! The bat strikes again! The whole gang of ...[???]... is outside hanging upside down from a lamppost!
Oh, peaches!
I'm barefoot!
How does a bat become a man?
And why does he have such a strong sense of justice? Does he want ...[???]...?
[telephone rings]
Hello, this is commissioner Gordon, you better have some good news.
Tonight will be a night of TERROR!
What? That's terrible news!
Yo!
Is yous here for the illegal deal, or what?
I sure am, you got the money?
Yeah... If you got the shipment of pirated DVDs.
I sure do. Don't know who'd wanted this many copies of 'Notting Hill', but...
Sure it is the bosses orders.
Alright let's just load them into the truck...
What was that?
Sounded like some kind of sonic bomb.
As if something was breaking the sound barrier.
Something like a bat.
Whoa! What the heck...
Whoa! Look up there in the sky!
It's a plane! A hightech plane!
It's shooting missiles at us!
Quick boys! Shoot it down with these vintage tommy guns!
[making sounds like shooting]
[B@man laughs]
Nice try, punks.
But I'm three miles above the earth's surface, don't even bother looking up.
I'd be much more concerned with your patellar tendons.
Why? What's the matter with our patellar tendons?
Yeah...
This!
[screaming]
God help me! I'll never walk again!
God's not up here. Only B@man!
Oh boy!
What a day!
[laughs]
Well, I'm plain old Bill.
Well, let me just lock up the old store now.
Head on home to my loving wife Belinda.
Probably cooking up some tasty lasagna.
Oh! What's this?
Rats! That's a dollar bill!
Well, I must have taken it from the register by accident.
Should I return it now or in the morning?
You know what? I'll just do it in the morning. That should...
Stop, thief!
Oh, no, no B@man...[screams]
[more screams]
Alright everybody, that's my ...[???]... and you're wearing it out.
Just calm down, no ...[???]... question.
Commissioner, Vicki Vale here from channel 7.
Hey, Vicki.
My viewers are dying to know what were those terrible noises and explosions that rocked Gotham city last night?
Oh those, ahm...
Well, those appear to be the work of, ah,the B@man!
B@man? No, no no!
Yep, yep. Ahm, it appears he has a plane.
A plane!
Uuuuh!
Well, what are you gonna do about it?
Well, nothing! I'm not gonna tell B@man what to do, he's B@man!
To fight the fiends and the foul
He'll don the cape and the cowl
He's here to save the day
It makes me want to say...
Holy musical B@man!
Another mob was brought to justice today by the b@man.
but as his crime fighting career continues,
all of Gotham is wondering: Who is the man behind the mask?
Hey. We got another pizza to deliver.
And get this: B@man ordered it!
Oh wow! Where are we heading?
Ah... Wayne manor.
Ah... I wonder if Bruce Wayne knows that B@man lives under his house...
He probably does, god bless him.
And god bless B@man.
You know what, everybody? This pizza's on the house!
And he's breaking up gangs
with his bat boomerangs
He's here to save the day
makes me wanna say
Holy musical B@man!
Woah!
Vicki Vale here from channel 7 and I'm sittin' down with commissioner Gordon of the Gotham city police department.
Now commissioner, a lot of people are saying that B@man is doing your job.
So I gotta ask:
Do the GCPD and the caped crusader work in tandem?
What IS the deal?
Well... ahm... B@man sent me this message and he wants me to read it on the air, if you don't mind.
Please!
Dear people of Gotham,
[B@mans voice] Your police force is inept and useless.
Your elected officials are as corrupted as they are stupid.
And your judicial system is nothing more than an elaborate Hocus [Not sure at the last word...]
run by the very ...[???]...
was created to destroy.
But none of that matters now.
Because I'm not fighting for the cops
Or city hall. Or you!
I'm fighting for me.
This is my war now.
I am vengeance.
I am the knight!
So stay out of my way!
[Gordon]love B@man. [B@man] love B@man.
Wow, he's such a dark hero.
He's so ...[???]...!
And I wouldn't want him any other way.
Holy musical B@man!
Alright everybody, pizza on me!
B@man strikes again, once more battling his arch nemesis, the Joker!
Holy musical B@man!
After their race and running the Joker was last seen falling from the greater Gotham bridge.
Though his body has not yet been found, it is unlikely the Joker survived his latest encounter with the bat ...[???]...
This just in: Jokers body has been found at Gotham peer. He is dead!
B@man!