Alright. Oh boy. Good job everybody.
Now, welcome. Welcome, welcome to the 200th birthday of Gotham.
I am pleased to announce that today the citiy's crime rate [??? has reached ???] an all time low.
YEAH!
Yeah, still the highest in the world but we're working on it.
And we owe it all to our beloved dark knight. Which is why we're gathered here today to honor him with the key to the city (shitty).
Yay!
Yeah, were's that key? Oh okay, I'll trade you!
Here you go.
To present the key here's a special guest all the way from Metropolis...
- Oooh.
-Yeah.
So everybody get pumped, because he should be here any minute - what was that?
- It's an attack!
-We're doomed!
- Protect the woman and children!
[screaming]
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Striking terror - that's part of the job.
Oh... no... Up there in the sky!
Oh, that's just B@man in his plane.
Oh! Whew!
Oh, he got us again with another good natured prank.
Flying his supersonic jet through the city's streets. Classic!
We love you, B@man!
Look at those little ragit pin-head puppets of Gotham.
They all look like bullseyes from up here.
You saved my life, B@man. Don't know how I could ever repay you.
Let my parents die, will you?
Well, you're all criminals in my eyes.
You just haven't committed any crimes...
...yet!
But when you do - I'll be there!
I'm everywhere!
I'm the fastest thing in the...
Who's...
Hey, look up in the sky! It's a boy!
Oh no! Not here!
No you bonehead, that's B@man's plane!
Not now!
It's Captain Marvel!
Not him!
No! It's Superman.
Hey guys! It's Captain Marvel. All the way from Metropolis.
- It's Superman.
- That's Captain Marvel.
- Well, what do we have here?
-Uagh!
Hey, license and registration, please.
I'm just kidding.
Uah. Eat my dust you super slowpoke!
Turbo drive, activate!
I see. You wanna race, huh?
Hey guys. Check it out! Captain Marvel is racing B@man's plane.
Go get him, B@man!
Ha, ha, ha, ha. I'm winning!
Ah, oh god! Are my limitless power's about to run out? Uah!
No!
What, what, what?
[???] Where did he go?
What the hell? Where did he go?
Behind you! I just flew around the world.
Oh, back from space. Hey, moon rock?
- No.
-No? Alright.
Hey,I caught the Riddler. You were waiting for the guy, right?
Hey! Put down my villain!
Okay.
Green Goblin.
Guys, this plane is not that scary. It lost the race.
Yeah, it can't even beat Captain Marvel.
Ha, ha, ha!
Okay B@man. You come down here in that cute little plane of yours. You come and get your key to the city.
Yeah, come on down here, you hero.
Guys, maybe he's not in there. Maybe the plane is set on autopilot.
No. No, no, no, he's in there.
Oh, x-ray vision. Hey, come on down here, B@man!
Alright.
The caped crusader.
Nice to finally meet you. Hey, I'm Superman.
Yeah. Duh!
Let's just get this over with.
Alright everybody. Now that the honored guest is here, we can begin the ceremony.
Now, when I [???] Huckleberry Finn...
Hey.
Hey, dude!
Sorry if I embarrassed you back there. I can't always help how powerful I am. You know?
Yeah.
Sure.
But... You must have...
...some weakness.
Hmm? Uh... no. No.
Oh, okay.
Not even Kryptonite?
- Where did you hear that from?
-From Lex Luther... @gov.
He also told me that you can't see through lead.
Which is why my mask is lined with it.
Sorry. Some of us superheroes like having secret identities, Clark Kent!
Who's that? I don't even know who that is!
Oh, that's funny. Because it's you!
- Proof it!
- Okay, I will!
Oh... crunch!
Hey, did you loose a diamond ring?
Thank you.
I'll give it to Lois Lane tonight. After I naked her.
Hey, that's a pretty nice plane you got over there.
- Thanks. I build it myself.
You know. You should get it looked at, because it's not very fast.
Well... Yes, of course.
Of course it's not very fast, that's because it's...
- ...my old plane.
- Old plane?
- Yeah!
- Really?
- Uh hu.
- Got another one?
Yeah. It's my new plane. And I don't bring it out during the day, so you'll probably never see it, but it is FAST.
- Really?
- Uh hu.
How fast?
Faster than you.
You don't know how fast I am.
I'm so fast that if I wanted to...
...I could fly around the world, till it started traveling in the opposite direction.
And then everything will go back in time, okay?
And you'd be a little baby.
And I'd spank you, like a little bad (bat) child.
- No, you couldn't.
- How do you know?
Cause you don't know who I am.
- Fuck you!
- Fuck YOU!
[Horror]
Forget this. I'm outta here!
He vanished.
Eww, he's always like this.
- Gotta love him...
- Hey guys, three cheers for B@man, huh?
Cheers, Cheers, Cheers!
Alright citizens, citizens. Let's not overexert ourselves.
Ah, commissioner. I was thinking, you know.
Being a hero myself - the first hero by the way, ...
...that I can accept that key on behalf of B@man.
Or you know, you could just give it to me. Since I'm all around faster and more powerful and all around supererior to B@man.
Hey, quit picking on B@man, why don't you?
I'm not picking on anybody. I'm just stating facts. B@man is not that great!
Oh! Not that great?!?
He may not have superpowers and nothing, but he's a Gotham boy!
He protects us, you know?!?
You mess with one of us, you mess with all of us!
Yup. Yeah. Hey, take this you super shmock!
Don't shoot me!
Criminy!