Welcome home, sir.
[scream]
Get rid of it. I never want to see it again.
What are you talking about, sir?
The plane, Alfre-D!
But master Wayne, you love this plane.
No. I hate that plane.
It's a slow plane, just - destroy it!
It's not just your plane - it's your father's plane!
And it's all that's left of him.
Don't destroy it.
Fine!
Then - get rid of it, I - I don't know...
Send it to Spiderman! Who cares. Just get it out of my sight.
I know that's an idea. Spiderman could use a good plane.
This world... It's rotten, Alferd. Rotten to the core.
It's just full of people who...
kill your parents and...
fly faster then your plane...!
You know, the one thing that made me happy,
the one thing, that I liked,
was being more powerful then everyone else.
Soring godlike in the sky...
blasting laser guided precision missiles...
crippling misguided youngsters that I never met...
made me feel like I was worth a damn.
But if I can't even fly faster then superman...
I might as well die...!
Come on then, sir! Cheer up.
You know there's more to life then senseless violence. And extravagant peacocking.
Like what?
Well, like family. And friends. Think, sir: Who do you like spending time with?
The Joker.
But he's in heaven now.
With mom and paps.
Making them laugh, I just know it.
The closest thing that I have to a  friend is - you.
But I pay you.
Apples and pears.
But, ah... surely there's somebody else.
What about your work friends?
[laughs]
I've never worked a goddamned day in my life!
You know that, Alfred.
'Cause the only person I ...[???]... is -
Lucius Falks!
Yeah! He's always making me planes and tanks and guns and stuff.
That means he's my friend, right?
Well, there you go.One friend.
Things aren't as bad as they seem.
Yeah! Why, I haven't talked to him in a ...[???]...! I'll give him a call, right now!
Oh, right now! Well, perhaps I should leave the room first...
No, Alferd, you'll stick around, you can say hi too, he'll love it!
No, wait! Sir! Please!
[Phone rings]
I've a confession to make, sir.
You're not the only one with a secret identity.
Turn around.
The other way.
what?
That's right. Lucius Falks and Alfred Pennyworth are the same person.
You see, when I was stationed in Birma with your father - this was before the war -
I made a promise:
I swore that if anything ever happened to him, I would pretend to be your butler.
So I, Lucius Falks, took the disuise of Alfred Pennyworth, so that I could give you words of wisdom twenty four, seven,
eight days a week.
At work and at home.
So,
all those times that you cleaned the entire mansion...
a ruse.
And my laundry?
I destroyed them at the end of the week, I buy you new clothes.
So, what you're saying is that...
I... I don't have one friend after all?
ALFRED!
How could you do this to me? You got my hopes up so high, and then you mocked and shut them in an alleyway!
Turns out that I can't even trust you after all.
You're fired, you old fraud!
Get the hell out of the bat cave!
Well, if that's what you bloody want, then fine!
Fine!
Good!
Great!
You wouldn't last a day without me!
Oh, I will two!
Wanna bet?
Yeah!
Fuck you!
What, fuck you!!!
Yeah.
good villains.
I don't need any stupid Alfred.
Wait...
Oh, what have I done?
...[???]... morning, sir!
Who are you?
And how did you get into the bat cave?
Oh me? Ahm -  well, the agency just send me over.
I'm ah - I'm ...[???]... replacement.
My name is O'Malley. The irish butler.
Good to meet you, O'Malley.
I'm B@man.
And I'm in a bad mood.
And -
the cave is a mess...
That's a nice cave.
You know, before the war your father used these tunnels to help build the underground robot.
Oh, I'm sorry. Would you like to be alone?
I am alone.
This is what it means to be B@man.
Darkness.
Solitude.
This is the life that I have chosen.
Nay.
The life that has chosen me!
Poor master Bruce.
He's such a dark, sad, lonely, melancholy knight.
Poor master Bruce, poor Mr. Wayne
Lonely caboose on a one car train
And it pains me to watch you amble along
This track of loneliness I laid down for you
I remember that horrible night,
the night you were split in two
and I swore I'd protect you
and I haven't
So I built a wall all around you
but the wall was too tall
and it blocked out all
of the birds and the sun
I tried to raise you right
I tried to raise you proper
I tried to be a mentor and a friend, and a mama and a papa too
And insulate you
from any outside source of fright
And make bloody sure
That you'll never see another dark, sad, lonely night
When I look at my life I see something's not right
like a thousand percent
And I wonder what it is
how it is that it's
always just me here crying alone
at the end of the night
a ten thousand percent
I put most of the blame on Alfred
How come he couldn't take that bullet intended
for mama and papa?
I never had a pony
I never had pets
Just a bullshit butler
who builds bullshit jets
Oh! I'm falling apart
I need a friend
Somebody to hold on to
Somebody to confide in
Think of the children
next time you gun down their mama and papa
their only mama and papa
because they probably
don't have another mama and papa!
I was seeing a girl for a while
a couple of days anyway
and I told her I loved her
Oh - oh - oh
She said: 'you're such a good friend and that rash is bad
you should probably go see your doctor.'
Oh - oh - oh
Oooooh!
Then she just disappeared
sent me some text about bad timing
and my love being selfish
Oh - oh - oh
Then my doctor called up and the blood came back
and as it turns out
I'm allergic to peanuts and shellfish
I loved peanuts and shellfish once
I'm falling apart!
I'm lacking punch
I can barely eat
This morning I barely touched my brunch
two spoons of oatmeal
a couple of nuts and half a banana
And like my soul
the banana was bruised and black
I'm falling apart
I need a friend
Somebody to hold on to
Somebody to confide in
Somebody to ride in
the cockpit
Co-captain of the friendship ship
Or maybe just a friend ship
Well, if I had a buddy
with me to discuss
just what we call friendship
I wanna be somebody's buddy
of somebody who could be my buddy back
anybody but a dumb shit butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
somebody who could be my buddy back
anybody but a dumb shit butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who could be my buddy back
Anybody but a bothering butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who could be my buddy back
Anybody but a dumb shit butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who could be my buddy back
Anybody but a ...[???]... butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who could be my buddy back
Anybody but a dumb shit butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who could be my buddy back
Anybody but my lame butler
I wanna be somebody's buddy
Somebody who can be my buddy back
I wanna be
Somebody's buddy
Master Bruce needs companionship. But where does a young handsome man gotta meet friends in the year 1997?
Duh, O'Malley! Get with the time!
The personal ...[???]... of course!
Let's see here...
single wild female seeking old english butler for a good time.
Uh! I just keep that one!
Put it in my pocket. Save it for a rainy day, I will.
Let's see... Dogs for sale. No.
Orphans for sale?!?
Even better. ...[???]...
[Phone rings]