[Phone rings]
You've reached the voicemail of - 'B@man.' - Please leave a message after the tone.
[1 kHz tone]
Hey, B@man. It's Superman. Ah...
Listen, I'm just calling because I feel like we kinda got off the wrong foot the other day, you know.
I was thinking about it. You're a hero...
...I'm a Superhero, let's be friends!
Ah, so me and Aquaman and some of the other guys, we are gonna be fighting Solomon Grundy on Monday, and ah...
...I'd love if you could be there, you know?
We can throw a Boomerang at him, [or] whatever you do.
Or probably just punch him.
Ah, you know, it's gonna be great.
And ah, also Wonderwoman is gonna be there.
So... there you go!
This message is getting kinda long, I guess. So, ah, you can just...
...call me back any time.
Actually no, call me back in the afternoon, 'course...
...all night long, I'm busy partying with all my friends at the fortress...
...of solitude.
Ah... give me a call-back. Bye.
♪ Wanna be... ♪
- Hey, the GL! [Green Lantern]
- The boy in blue!
- What up, my dog?
- Hey, hey. Not too much. Eh, were you just talking to B@man?
Yeah, yeah. Well, his machine anyway.
Oh, cool.
You want a beer? I can make 'Rolling Rock' or 'Heinecken'.
Oh, sure, sure. Ahm...
I'll have a - a Heinecken sounds good.
- Oh - not Rolling Rockers, that's fine.
- There you go!
Cheers.
- Thanks.
- [Random stranger singing]
Ua, ah!
[Sounds of disbelieve]
Oh man! Oh, geez! Oh man!
OH SUPERMAN AND THE GREEN LANTERN!!!
Oh man!
HEY, WOAH!
CAN I GET A PICTURE?
- Oh yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Ah, sure, it's fine.
Oh man! Oh, ho ho. Here!
Oh, oh man!
Oh, the Green Lantern!
You're, you're like...You're...  My kid sister is gonna freak!
You're like our second favorite superhero.
- [???] second, me. Well thanks.
- Right behind B@man.
- Look right over there.
- Alright, smile!
Ahh!
- Got it.
- Alright, yeah!
Oh! Oh, no, no, no!
I want a hug.
Great, great.
- Thank you so much!
- No, no. Thank you.
Uhm hum. Uhm hum.
Have a good day.
- Here you go. - Okay.
-Yoink.
Ha ha.
Duh!
Picture is ruined.
You cut my head off!
You super-putz!
- Hey!
- Woah! Woah, woah, are you gonna take that?
I'm used to it.
Man...
Fuck B@man! Sorry!
Woah, woah, woah! What's wrong with B@man?
I don't know. I just feel like he's an overrated hero, you know?
The guy doesn't even have any superpowers and have you seen how many Twitter followers he has?
Oh, no man. I'm not on the Twitter.
He's got a lot.
- More than you?
- Yeah!
But it's not fair, because he's got the Twitter-Name B@man.
Somebody already took the Twitter-Name 'Superman' and all he do is tweet about how dumb I am.
Who would do a thing like that?
I don't know. Some asshole named Bruce Wayne.
Anyway, my Twitter-Name is 'The Real Superman'.
Which of course makes it sound like I'm the fake Superman.
That's rough, Clark.
Wait!
You know my secret identity?
This is secret?!?
Oh, come on. Nobody cares who Superman is!
You know what else is stupid about B@man? His villains!
Oh no, no, no. They're classic!
No! No, they're corny. And...
It's just a new guy in a different colored suite wearing a thing on his head and making puns based of his stupid theme.
Yeah. I guess I really never thought about it like that before. Yeah, Riddler? Guy in a suite, thing on his head.
Mad Hatter - Guy in a suit, thing on his head.
And Two-Face - Guy in a suit, scar on his head. It's...
Two-Face is the worst. It's like - His theme is just the number two.
What's he gonna do? Rob the second national bank of all of it's two-dollar bills?
- God forbid Gotham run out of two dollar bills!
- Ha, ha, ha.
Anything goes with these guys in Gotham.
You know...
I'd... It's like... I bet the next person that B@man is gonna fight is gonna be...
So... what's the stupidest thing I can think of?
- Candy! A candy themed villain. Somebody who kills people with candy!
- Yeah!
Yeah, but if they're so stupid, why are they so famous?
They're only famous because B@man screws up all the time and let's them kill people.
You know, my villains never get that chance.
It's like have you ever heard of Mister Mxyzptlk?
- No.
- No!
It's right. It's because I do my damn job.
The point is: I'm the most powerful superhero. So shouldn't I be the most popular?
Yeah, yeah. [Something rings]
Oh. Oh wait, hold on. My ring is ringing.
Yeah hello?!?
Aha...
Ah crap. Uhm, back to Oa?
Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
Uhm hum!
- I gotta go.
- What's up?
Sinestro is forming an evil corps. The guardians is... ah... work stuff.
Alright.
I'll just see you on Monday, I guess.
Why?
Dude!!!
Solomon Grundy thing! You're coming, right?
Oh... Ah... yeah...
- Maybe! [vanishes]
- Hey!
[sigh]
You've reached the voicemail of - Wonderwoman - please leave a message after the tone. [The tone]
Hey, Wonderwoman. It's Superman.
So ah - I knew you're kinda on the fence about that whole Solomon Grundy thing, but I just wanted to tell you that...
...ah B@man is gonna be there.
So... there you go!