Woah!
Line up,
sign up
if you're looking for some sin
And a dirty way to win
Get pissed,
enlist
tap in
to the devil within
Let the villainy begin
We join in classrooms [not sure about that...]
We're making clever quips
We revel in malevolence
Four thousand horses of the apocalypse
Giddyap, Gotham
Giddyap, ap, ap
We're going rogue, rogue, rogue!
Rogues are we
We are the harlots and the hussies
We are the swindlers and the cheats
Rogues are we
We're rising up from the underground
We're taking over your streets
Woah!
Riddle me this
I've got a puzzle that will put you to tears
I'm cruel but never crass
Look no further than here to see a Penguin without peer
I've got a certain touch of class
I made a fear toxin in the form of gas
Then I wear a scary mask
I've got ice in my veins
Venom on the vine, I'll weed out any wussy
I'm a pretty little kitty, but I ain't no...
Rogues are we
we are the harlots and the hussies
We are the swindlers and the cheats
Rogues are we
we're rising up from the underground
We're taking over your streets
Rogues are we
Quak, quak, quak, quak! Riddler! ...
Well...
isn't this a cool crowd?
It is so ice to see you all again.
Mr. Freeze, you cold hearted snake, come over here and kiss my little flipper.
One more time. Alright sit down, frosty,before you melt away.
enough pussy footing, penguin, and let's get the meeting started meow, shall we?
Oh, I thought, I saw a pussy cat. I did! I did saw a pussy cat!
[Reference to: Warner Bros. Tweety]
That's what I love about you, catwoman: A Chick -
Who likes to get down to business.
[Laughs]
Now
Ladies and Gentlemen, I'm sure you know why you are here, I'm sure you've all been reading my...
tweets.
We rogues have burned some of our feathers and we are gettig plucked together by a man, who dresses up like a bat!
[Protest]
He's got us peaking all of our businesses, and quite frankly -
it's starting to ruffle my feathers.
Because of B@man my operations have been put on ice.
My assets are frozen.
I've been uprooted.
He's given me an awful fright.
We better Cat-nap this thing ...[???]... before that mouse with wings sends us all to the pound, meow.
I second that!
suffering ...[???]...! Who invited Two-Face?
How are you, weenies?
Let's make this quick, I'm double-parked!
Two-Face, you douchebag, you didn't get an invite.
I know, but that's the second meeting you guys haven't invited me to, and it's not fair!
Because I'm twice as ...[???]... as the rest of you!
Oh yeah? What's your latest sub-bar evil ice-capade?
What are you going to do? Robber the second national bank of it's two dollar bills?
[laughs]
Yeah! On February, 2nd!
I hate to let the cat out of the bag, but your two-theme is a cat-astrophe!
You're a lame duck, and you know it.
Yeah, but you guys didn't hear the part about the double homicide!
Come on! Please let me doing the counselor of rogues! Please let me do it! Please...!
No way!
Leave!
Fly the coup, Two-Face. You're a secondary villain!
wherever I wouldn't have it any other way.
I was off gonna go over to the ...[???]... anyway to catch a double-feature!
Catch you on a flipside? No my coin!
That's okay. 'Cause I always carry -
two.
Get your broke-ass out of here, Two-Face!
...[???]...
- Excuse me.
- No, it was my fault.
And mine!
So what are we going to do about this bird-brained dark knight, because quite frankly, I am stubbed [is the last one right?]
Well, well, well...
Looks like you guys are up to your old twix
A Twix-bar?
Alright -
Who's the wise-guy who thinks he's the Joker?
The Joker? [laughs]
The Joker was a sucker.
You can call me
Sweet-tooth.
And as you can see, I'm a lot tastier.
[sounds of fear] Sweet-tooth!
Sweet-tooth is the coolest new villain in town!
He's been terrorising Gotham with his candy-themed crime.
Yeah, it's been quite as free, hasn't it?
And yet, I sure haven't been invited to join the rogues gallery.
More like the peanut-gallery if you ask me.
I mean, what are you planning to do this time?
Kidnap the mayor and ransom him off for a hundred rand? [Laughs]
How boring.
What you need is a new leader.
My mama named me. [laughs again]
Quit your squaking, Sweet-tooth!
I'm cock of the walk around here! CHILLY WILLY!
Yeah, boss?
Chilly Willy, extract this tooth from the ...[???]...
With pleasure, Mr. Guin!
No, no, no, no, it's just Penguin, it's just one name, Chilly.
Sure thing, Mr. Pen.
Okay.
Perhaps you all need a demonstration of my villainy.
If you will. Chilly Willy.
Yeah, boss?
I've got a question for you.
How many licks does it take to kill you?
One -
Two -
Three!
[screams]
Three...
I say...
we kill the bat!
[laughs]
What a positively peRRRRRRRRRfect plan, Sweet-tooth.
Kill the bat - If I had thought of that, I'd still be the head of this ...[???]... house.
Sweet-tooth, my top-head and monocle are off to you.
Ladies and gentlemen, put your flippers together for the new king of crime in Gotham!
Yes, yes, yes, but quit your snickering, you air-heads.
We've got a bat ...[???]... free.
And if we ever want it to be payday,
We've got to strengthen our numbers.
See, divided we rogues are just runts.
But together we pack a sour punch.
If we work together, I mean there's no way
one man can stop us. No matter
how bat/bad he is. So -
We need to recruit every villain in Gotham.
Cool themes, lame themes, themes that don't match their powers, even the villains that take their names from public domain story.
Hey, I take offense in that!
Oh, grab a brain, Scare-crow.
Yeah, or the ...[???]... will do...
Does this mean I can join you?
Oh, you're welcome in our round table, evil King Arthur!
And what about me?
But of course...!
Finally! A chance to proof myself!
When the citizens of Gotham see the might of my heat-ray, there won't be a soul alive who doesn't fear the name
Sherlock Holmes.
Excellent, Sherlock! And put out the word to evil mother goose and Huckleberry Finn as well.
Gotham's been chewing on some bad casserole for far too long.
But tonight, we provide a little ...[???]... Moving on to the dessert ...[???]...
We're gonna give Gotham something sweet to suck on, baby!
Rogues! (Hup)
Assemble - gather - unite (bee bop)
And take a mental snapshot of this most suspicious night (wooo)
We got strength in numbers now, the battle can begin (uh hu)
We're waking war on B@man and the war is ours to win.
Rise up, like a natural disaster
We'll take the bat and then we take back the town
We harm in harmony, arm in arm we hold our stance
In solidarity, he hasn't a chance
Rise up, like a natural disaster
We take the bat and then we take back the town
We harm in harmony, arm in arm we hold our stance
In solidarity, he hasn't a chance
Let's dance
Rogues are we - rise up! Like a natural disaster
We take the bat and then we take back the town
We harm in harmony, arm in arm we hold our stance
in solidarity, he hasn't a chance
Let's dance
Rogues are we - Honk!