[Sobbing]
Sir, it's me, O'Mally.
You can't stay in your pillow fort and cry forever.
Yes, I can.
But I've got a surprise for you.
What kind of surprise?
A visitor.
I don't like visitors.
Yes, I know. But ah, ...  but this visitor is unlike any other.
You see this visitor - he's from the circus.
You like the circus, don't you?
Yeah.
Who likes the circus?
B@man.
You like the circus!
B@man loves the circus.
Oh will you come on and give it a shot?
I'll try.
Very good, Sir.
Our guest is waited in the drawing room.
Ah.
Let's get this tied around your little waist, huh?
It feels nice and secure - there you are.
Thank you, O'Mally.
You know, you remind me of two great men.
That I once found out were the same man.
Very good, Sir.
[Opens imaginary door] What?!?
A kid!?!
O'Mally, I thought it was going to be an elephant.
Or a clown, at least.
I miss the Joker.
Give this young man a chance, please Sir.
He's fallen on a patch of bad luck.
You see...
He's an orphan.
An orphan?
But...
What happened to his Mommy - and his papa?
Both dead, I'm afraid.
And his heart is heavy with dread.
Well, I know how that is.
And he's such a teeny little guy.
You know what?
I'm going to introduce myself to him.
Very good, Sir.
Hi.
I'm Bruce Man - I mean...
I'm Bat Wayne - FUCK!
Can I start over?
Sure.
Hi.
I'm B@man - FUCK!
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Charmed, I'm sure.
They call me...
...Dick.
Does that hurt your feelings?
No.
Because it's my name.
Dick Grayson.
What else does these little bastards call you?
They call me - THE FINE GRAYSON!
Dazzling.
Well it's nice to see you two hitting it off.
Can I get you something to drink, Sir?
[Both] A juice box. And make it a [???], god damn it!
Huh.
Very good, Sir.
So, Dick.
What do you think of my manor?
It's gloomy.
And old.
And the floorboards are ??? with tears of sorrow.
I like it.
- Really?
- Uhm hum.
Well, thing is that you are a homeless orphan.
You can stay here a while.
If you'd like.
Mister Wayne. May I be frank with you?
Well, sure Frank. If you prefer it to Dick.
I'd been ward my fair share of wealthy billionaires throughout the years.
And it's always the same old song and dance with you types.
Sure, you think it's fun to take in the young acrobat and watch him fly around for a while.
But after the novelty is worn off, I'm back on the streets.
As alone as the day my parents where stolen from me by death's greedy hand.
So what makes you any different from the rest of them, eh?
Who is Bruce Wayne?
Huh?
Good question, kid.
Oh, I'm just your average...
...[???] in the middle, down on his luck...
billionaire.
No, that's not who I really am.
Bruce Wayne died!
The night that his parents where gunned down in front of his very eyes.
And from his ashes I arose.
To clean the streets of Gotham of it's scum!
- So that what happened to me...
- will never happen to anyone again!
YES!!!
Dick!
I know that you're just a teeny little boy and we've only just now met, but...
- I feel like we're the same.
- We're the same!
- Split right down the middle.
- Split down the middle.
Dick, I wanna tell you something.
Something that I've never told anyone before.
Except for a couple of my ex girlfriends.
And my last butler. And my new butler.
What is it, Bruce?
- I'm B@man!
- Ohhh!
I knew it!
- What?!?
- I knew you were B@man right from the moment you walked in this room.
- How?
- But it wasn't this B@ Symbol on your chest.
Or the cape that is carelessly dangling from beneath your robe.
No.
It was the man behind the B@ symbol on your chest.
And in front of the cape.
Me?
Yes.
And now, I have something to tell you.
It's always been my secret dream to join in your crusade...
...and fight along side as your sidekick.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Yeah. No!
- What?
No, Dick. I can't.
Why?
I live a dark and [???] life of solitude.
To be B@man is...
...is to be alone.
But B@man!
I'm alone too.
Perhaps...
...we could be alone...
...together.
Then so it shall be.
Now, Dick.
Are you ready to take the secret oath?
The secret oath that I took many years ago.
- Repeat after me!
- No, not yet.
- No, I haven't started.
- No, I haven't stated.
[both] You're doing that...
[ -_- ]
You wanna fight crime with me or what?
Yes, I would like that.
Good.
Then you must do as I do.
Just strike terror into the hearts of the superstitious criminal scum of Gotham.
You must take on the guys of that what you fear most to scare...
...them.
Yeah!
So tell me, Dick.
What are you afraid of?
What am I afraid of?
Years ago...
...when I was humble circus boy...
...my parents and I performed together - in an acrobatic trio...
...until one night...
...with performing their most dangerous and all inspiring feat...
...the Gryson Dive...
...they were murdered.
Mid air.
By a Robin.
By a ROBBER!!!
No.
A Robin.
What's a Robin?
Sound like a lizard.
It's a songbird.
Oh.
My god, that must be huge.
It's quite small, actually.
Oh.
Well, that's good.
Small is good.
Actually on my first night out, I was Pterodactylman.
But wouldn't you know that people laughed at me.
And I think that B@man works really well, because I'm a huge bat.
But I'm a tiny pterodactyl.
Yes, and ever since that night...
..whenever I hear that cheerful chirp of a blue jay...
...or a [???] dove...
...I'm filled with quite white rage.
Yes, use that rage. Become that songbird!
Yes!
I can feel my transformation beginning.
Yes. Yes, I like that.
What ah - what are you doing with your fingers?
Those are my feathers.
Yeah.
From this moment forth...
...the rogues of Gotham...
...should tremble in fear...
before the tweeting song...
of the ROBIN!
Oh, it's you!
You look just like a giant bird.
I'm sorry for frightening you.
No, it's good.
Because tonight...
...B@man and Robin take to the streets.
- Tonight will be a night
- of dancing.
Ah...
Yeah!
It's nice to see you smiling again, Sir.
I mean - for the first time.
O'Mally!
You drunken son of a bitch.
Come here!
Don't wait up.
Hey, Robin.
- I'll race you to the B@mobil!
-Alright.
[laughing]