Just when it seemed as if B@man had cleaned up Gotham for good,
a whole new wave of trashes glutted the streets.
Police are baffled by what they are referring to
as a boom in the super-villain population.
Clock-king, The Wizard and False-face,
These are just as few of the new shitty characters that have
been crawling out of the woodwork over the past few days.
Though experts aren't concerned about any one villain in particular, given that they are all so shitty,
some are worried that this new army of crime will overpower the B@man in sheer numbers.
Good luck, B@man. This could be your darkest night yet.
Finally! Out of the slammer and surgery.
Time to get back to our life of crime, yay,yay,yay,yay,yay...
Only this time let's not get caught by the bat.
Don't worry, not even the bat does mess with our new boss.
Egg-head.
Alright, you turkeys! Load the chickens into the trucks.
Yeah, egg-cellent.
Let's see what Gotham city does without a ready supply of eggs.
Hey, what the devil was that?
Sounded just like a boid.
Yes, because we're standing by a truck full of chickens, you chicken!
That was no clucking chicken.
Sounded more like...
[Sound of a chicken]
A giant Robin!
Ha! We heard you were hatching a scheme, Egg-head,
But we've cracked the case!
It's over.
Yeah, over easy.
Scramble!
We're like long lost brothers who found each other
And love each other like family.
And though we're not related
and it's totally belated
I'm elated just to say you are
my bro
Mi amigo.
And where I go
Is where we go
And it feels as though it was destined to be so
So very nice
Look, B@man, a dog!
Quick, Robin! ...[???]...
Hey welcome to TGI Friday - OH MY GOD! It's Calendar-man!
Right! You may have four hours waiten for a table, but now it's time to march -
to your death. Quick!
Take this pillowcase. Fill it with ...[???]...
get that vintage Elvis-posterand don't forget Billy 'The big mouth' Bess.
You know, I'm sorry, but here at TGI-Fridays all we can offer you is ...[???]... service and a forced fun atmosphere.
[screams]
Calendar-man, your days are numbered!
Hihihihi!
B@man! The tiny little bird.
Well,well. Looks like today's not your lucky day.
Boxing day's coming early.
I'm gonna punch you weaklings into next month!
Come at me, you april-fools!
Thank you, B@man...
How could it all have been so
lonesome and hopeless? I know
Promise you won't go out and get mugged and murdered on me
I cross my heart
I'll never let that happen
We'll have each other's backs and
listen to the Jackson five and dance the night away
Robin, you parted the clouds
By the light of the moon we have found the sunrise
And not in my though I'd find it
nearly blinded by it
So bright, so bright, so bright
You are my bright knight
You're my morningbird
We're wingmen singing in thirds
Spring to my winter
flying in the friendship ship
B@man
Robin
You are my bright knight
you're my morning bird
We're wingmen, my vision is blurred
For the tears of joy
no more dark, sad, lonely nights
[scream]
Ha ha! More like 'La cage au fouls'!
[laughs]
Finally, B@man, I have you trapped.
Right where I want you. In a gigatic birdcage.
Let me tell you a story, B@man.
Back when I was just a baby emperor penguin my mother
used to keep a birdcage in the kitchen quite similar
to this one except much smaller in size.
And in that birdcage she kept a sparrow.
Or a swallow, I don't really remember.
The point is, is that the sound that bird made -
it went tweet-tweet, B@man -
tweet-tweet
And that's the last sound you're ever gonna hear.
Because as soon as the birdseed fills the bottom of that birdcage,
I'm gonna release my hummingbird-ostrich-hybrid murder birds!
And they're gonna peck your fucking brains out, B@man!
[laughs]
You're a fiend, Penguin!
Oh, what's the matter, B@man? Not a bird-lover?
On the contrary.
There's one bird that I love.
- Very much.
- Oh!
And what bird would that be, B@man?
A Robin.
A Robin? Isn't that like a lizzard or...
[Screams]
I can't believe this is happening!
Oh... It's happening, man.
Thanks, old chump. You sure got me out of a birdcage.
Hey! Don't mention it, B@man.
Now, let's get this tear-bird back to the cuckoo's nest.
High five, all you ones!
But Gotham city still has a sweet tooth.
And that means, no-one's safe.
Gotham city still has a sweet tooth? What is that supposed to mean?
Talk, you ...[???]...!
Sorry, B@man.
But I'm no gusher.
His head! It turned into a - ...[???]... blue raspberry.
No, Robin, doooon't -
eat those. They're poisoned.
oh my!
Gotham city still has a sweet tooth?
What could it mean, B@man?
Du you think that it's some kind of riddle?
I'm - not sure...
But reguardless, we've got to get to the bottom of this.
We've got to find this sweet tooth and plug it.
Before Gotham gets a cavity.
Well, I'm not worried. Because there's nothing, that we can't do - together. Isn't that right?
Life-long friend?
No.
Life-partner!
Buddies, bros, homies, amigos.
Pizza, Nintendo, woo,woo,woo, let go!
We're like long lost brothers
who found each other
and love each other
like family.
You are my bro
mi amigo
And where I go
Is where we go
And it feels as though
it was destined to be so
So very nice
Oh - oh - oh
Oh, hiss and ...[???]...! What are we supposed to do meow?
Yes. B@man was fearsome before, but now he's got Robin...
Wait! Say that again.
B@man was fearsome before, but...
But now he's got Robin!
...[???]... have a good plan.
What is it, my candy prince of crime?
The bat's got a soft spot for that bird.
And another word for soft spot is weak spot.
I think it's time we put an end to this dynamic duett, don't you?
Say good-night, dark knight. Parting is such sweet sorrow.
[laughing]