It appears the caped crusader has taken on a ward.
That's right: Robin!
The boy-wonder. And this bird-boy has all of Gotham ...[???]...
We here at channel 7 have taken to the streets
to find out, what Gotham has to say about
the dark knight's not so dark new pal.
Oh! Yeah, Robin...
uh, what do I think about Robin...?
Uh, B@man's hanging out with some ...[???]... kid now? What am I think of that?
What can I say about Robin that hasn't been said already?
It's plain to me that...
I might be the only one who thinks this, but ah...
I'm pretty sure, everyone agrees, that...
Robin sucks!
B@man's a loader, you know, but now he's
running around, telling jokes with some kid, it's like -
Don't do that!
Where's the kid's pants?
The B@man should always be a solitary figure. Else the concept of a child-crime-fighter is ridiculous.
It ruins the gritty realism of a man, who fights crime just as a bat!
So say we all. [BSG]
Amen to that.
B@man doesn't need a sidekick
undermines his whole aesthetic
whole thing just gives me a headache
Robin sucks
[Phone rings]
You've reached the voicemail of - Bruce man - I mean B@ Wayne - I mean B@... ah, fuck - please leave a message after the tone.
[tone]
Hey B@man! It's Superman.
So, I heard about your new sidekick... That's cool...
So, you're copying me again?
I mean, everyone remembers my sidekick.
Krypto? The super-dog?
Been growing up that super-dog as a Superman's best friend.
Then we moved to Metropolis and -
He started chasing cars and destroying them, and, ah...
leaving some super-poops on the floor of my - not so super efficiancy.
And then he super-humps Lois's leg and put her into that full body cast. That was kind of strike 3 for Krypto.
So I moved him to a pen in the fortress.
But I guess he couldn't take the solitude.
He wanted to run, not being coopeed up, so -
he ran off on me.
Miss that dog.
Speaking of missing things: Where were you for the Solomon Grundy thing on Monday?
Turned out to be smaller then I expected, just a couple of cool guys.
Me and...
Solomon Grundy...
Yeah, anyway, just give me a call-back.
[Howling]
Krypto!
Extra, extra! Read all about it! Robin sucks!
I'll take one of those.
I'll take one of those, man!
Yep.
Hey!
Thank you.
He may be a solid dude
but B@man, he needs solitude
Robin makes him fricking cute
Robin sucks!
Tanya said, that Larry said,
that Sarah said he wets the bed
He probably does, he's only ten
Robin sucks!
Now get out of my office!
Yep, I live here.
Another criminal, commissioner. I caught this roughy here trying to download Photoshop onto more then one computer.
Ooooh...
I'd like to speak to my lawyer.
Quiet, you.
Ew... Thanks, Robin, but, ahm...
where are your pants?
pants are luxury. My costume is designed to be aerodynamically perfect.
Ew... God, you suck!
If I would wear pants, it would decrease my crime-fighting ability by twenty percent. [DeathNote]
I can't afford that, can you?
Well, geez, if you can't afford a pair of pants, I'll give you mine! Let me just...
...get them off me... here you go... Hey!
Where did he go? He vanished!
Robins aren't scary
they're completely ordinary
Might as well call him canary
freaking Robin sucks!
Robins are so common
they're the statebird of Wisconsin
So, what else do you need to know
Robin sucks!
Boing!
Help! Help! Somebody help me!
I know that sound all too well.
That's the sound of an innocent soul falling victim to the world's injustice.
Well, it's time for the Robin to swoop in.
Grayson dive!
Help! Help! Somebody please, help me!
Miss Rachel Daws of the DA's office!
Well, don't worry, I'm here to help.
Oh thank god!...Oh!
Robin. Great, I wanted help, not a babysitting gig.
Just when I thought this mugging couldn't get any worse.
Huh! Get behind me!
Stand down, criminal, or I'll be forced to use force.
Good heavens, sir, you look ill!
Oh my! Heavens to Betsy!
This man needs a doctor! He has to go to the hospital,
so he could go to jail.
The boss said the pain would go away. That my tum-tum wouldn't hurt no more...
What's the matter with your tum-tum?
- It's ficking upset!
- Oh!
The boss...
he...
he mades me eat...
what?
What did he make you eat?
...[???]...rocks... and a Coca-Cola
...[???]...-rocks and a coke...
Miss Daws! Keep dooown!
BOOM
[laughing]
I was like to enter on a bang.
Ah, who... who are you?
Me?
I'm the one who's been feeding Gotham's craving for chaos.
Haven't you and B@man enjoyed my latest ...[???]... m&m's - Murder and mayhem? There they are!
Gotham city still has a - sweet tooth!
That's me.
And you are the one behind all the new villains in town!
Aren't you a smarty!
Oh, I like these.
Good! Good!
Well, your sugar-high is over, Sweet-Tooth.
And you're right about to crash. Into Arkham Asylum that is.
Get ready to trade your Peppermint Patty for a padded cell.
Oh, you're the one, who's nutty, think I'm going to the nut-house.
My ...[???]... wonder.
uh - I don't like these.
Oh! Well, perhaps you'll enjoy my next batch.
Get him, my sour patch kids!
'bout time we candy-coated this Robin's breast red.
We're gonna tear out your jelly belly.
Miss Daws, go! I'll take care of the lollipop-guild.
Thanks, Robin. Now I feel bad for thinking you suck.
Just go.
Oh, you're not going anywhere, Miss Daws.
Gob, stop her!
I'm sorry Gob, but I'm the only jawbreaker around here.
Do I have to do everything myself? Hand me my Bazooka, Joe!
Now, god damn it!
Damn it! Take it. How do you... How do you work this thing?
Ah-ha!
That Bazooka is shooting my legs with bubblegum.
Mh, I can't move them.
They're wrapped in bubbleitious.
Miss Daws!
And I thought, I was a gumshoe.
[laughing] Now that's what I call a sticky situation!
- ...[???]...
- You said it, Candy.
Well, what do you think, Robin? Doesn't Candy here look good enough to eat? She's my little sugar-baby.
Yeah, and he's my sweetheart.
I'm the one who makes the candy-puns around here! Got it?
Oh, Miss! Miss, oh, Miss! Did he hurt you?
No. It felt like -
a kiss.
Kiss... What could it mean?
Take this, bird-boy!
Oh, a bird in the hand!
So, what do you say, S-T: Shall we kill him now -
or later?
No, no, no, no. I have plans for this little chicklet.
Take five, boys! We've got a long night ahead of us.
Candy, be a dove and tell my troops to advance on Gotham square.
Get ready, my darling delooted dark knight!
It's gonna be a hard ...[???]... in the old town tonight.
[Laughs]