Mail, Sir.
Oh, thank you, O'Mally.
- Here you are.
- Hmm...
Let's see.
What have we got here?
Hmm...
Bills. Bills. Bills.
Hey, what's this?
It's a letter from Spiderman.
I bet it's about that lousy ass slow plane that I send him.
Let's take a look.
Dear B@s, thanks for the offer but I won't be able to take the plane off of your hands.
I don't have any place to - stick.
[Grunts]
Love, your friendly neighborhood Spiderman.
P.s.: I'm a huge fan. I follow you on the web.
[laughing]
Wow, what a sweetheart.
You know what? This is going up on the B@fridge. Quick, O'Mally! To the B@fridge!
There. I put it right next to Robin's great drawing that I gave an A+.
+++++++++++++++++++++++
Well, I'll just - ah - I take this rubbish away.
Newspapers. Most of the time they're a waste of time.
O'Mally! I wanna read the funnies.
No, wait - ah - Let me read them for you.
Okay.
[???] co workers have made a quip at his expense.
Well that man [???].
That sounds funny. Give it to me!
Wait, no Sir. Please!
What?!?
Robin the boy blunder?
What's this?
Nah.
B@man's new sidekick is a lame, cheery, cheesy, fruity, fruit cake?
With no pants and a hamburglar mask?
He ruins the once beloved dark and gritty B@man?
Robin ruin B@man? But - but that's not true.
Robin make B@man happy.
O'Mally, why would somebody write something like this?
Well, I ah - I suppose they ah...
...think he's stupid.
Ha, ha, ha. That's ridiculous.
What's stupid about a happy little boy flying around Gotham city? Spreading cheer to all of the people?
Well, when you put it that way...
- ...you can't blame them. I mean almost anything is stupid...
- WHAT?!?
- ...but...
- ROBIN'S NOT STUPID!
You're stupid.
- Hey.
- You've always hated Robin, haven't you?
Don't think I haven't noticed!
Well, your backsliding days are over.
Get out of the B@cave, you drunken slob! You're fired!
You're getting lost in this crazy character of yours.
What?
But if that's what you bloody want then fine.
Fine.
- Good.
- Great.
- I'll pack my things.
- Oh, don't bother. I'll have them burned.
- Fuck you!
Fuck youuuu!
Hrrr.
Hamburglar mask.
This doesn't make any sense.
[sigh]
Oh, herro.
Oh.
Who are you?
And how did you get into the B@cave?
Oh forgiveness, prease.
The agency just send me over.
My name is Kwon Ri, the Chinese butrer.
Good to meet you, Kwon Ri.
I'm B@wayne ah I'm Bruceman - Fuck!
I'm B@MAN!!!
I'm in a bad mood.
[Alarm]
Oh, the b@ararm, Sir!
You're right. Put it up on the vid-screen.
Very good.
We interrupt this traditional new years eve broadcast of Notting Hill for a special news bulletin.
Less than 30 minutes ago, Gotham square was taken hostage by a force of heavily armed thugs.
Amongst the rogues, some of B@man's most deadly foes have been spotted.
Including Catwoman, Killer Moth, Maxie Zeus and the sad [???] soldier.
Police are trying desperately to rescue the 3000+ citizens being held hostage.
Send in the choppers.
It's [???], Gotham. You're no match for my heat-ray.
[targeting sounds]
Oh.
No, get those choppers out of here! What am I thinking?
I'm such a boob.
Hoah.
But up until now, police have been unable to penetrate the barricade of rogues surrounding the square.
And just 10 minutes ago, we here at channel 7 received this video footage from the rogues ring leader...
...and have been demanded to air it.
I warn you, it is disturbing.
Who can take the sunrise? Ah!
And sprinkle it with BLOOD?
Why, hello Gotham city. It's me - Sweet-Tooth.
- Time for your fate...
- And Two-Face!
Beat it, Two-Face!
Wait, but...
Let's try that again, shall we?
Hello Gotham. It's me.
I'm sure you've notice by now that Gotham square is in my sticky grasp.
But just like a kid in a candy store I've managed to stick a few extra goodies into my pockets when no one was looking.
Let's take a peek at my secret stash, shall we?
Oh, and B@man...
I sure hope you're watching.
Because this is sure to make your mouth water.
The boy-Wonder Ball!
Robin!
Poor Robin.
He risks his life trying to be Gotham's life savior.
And they hate his guts.
But how much? See, I'm dying to find out.
So I've deviced a little - a little - Whatchamacallit.
A deathtrap!
Feast your eyes on - THIS!
My nuclear warhead.
At exactly 5 am tomorrow morning...
...I will lower the warhead into the cities water supply.
Oh, it's going to be quite the fun dip.
Because the warhead will make the water so [???], that anyone who drinks from it...
Well, perhaps I should just show you.
Let's give it a lick, shall we, Miss Rachel Daws?
- No! No, please don't!
Come on, girl! Come on!
It puts the warhead on it's tongue.
Or else it gets the hose again. [The silence of the lambs]
[Nom nom nom]
[-_-]
That's right.
Her head imploded.
Just like all of Gotham's will, unless, hmm...
Skittle me this!
Will Gotham forsake it's heroes or will it's heroes forsake Gotham?
See I've set up a [Friendface] poll and for the next 7 hours I'll be taking votes from the Gotham populous.
The moment the sun rises, I will either lower the warhead into the [???] cities water supply...
...or I will kill Robin.
So it's all for the people of Gotham to decide.
Do I implode your heads - or put a bullet in the Boywonder's?
Alright, I think I gotta [???] your decision.
So that's B@man betrays you all and shows up by Gotham square to save his little nerd...
...then Robin dies at dawn.
[Evil laughing]
[Two-Face joins in the laughing]
Yeah, and simultaneously....
...while that is happening, I - Two-Face...
...will be simultaneously robbing the second Gotham city national bank of all it's two dollar bills.
So collectors of outer print currency beware!
[Moar laughing]
You're coming with me, boy!
[B@man is pissed] No!
Sweet-Tooth!!!
[Robin! No! Robin!]
What do I do?
Do I abandon Gotham city or...
forsake my oldest chump?
I - no, I - I...
I wish Alfred was here.
I am here, Sir.
Alfred!
That's me.
You - you came back?
Thank you!
I never left.
I've always been right here.
What do I do, Al?
Do I choose my city or my friend?
Oh, yes. The classic choice.
Every hero must make the decision.
You know, a long time ago, I was in Bosnia with your father.
This was before the war.
We were helping a squad of [???] refugees to cross the border.
There was a tribe chief there who heard by the name of [???].
[???]
Papa loved rhymes.
That's right, he did.
But he had the unpleasant task of having to execute his own wife.
You see, she was a double agent.
- But she had forgotten. She didn't know who she was working for.
- No.
So old Mac had a choice to make.
Do you give up on someone you love - or do you abandon your sworn duty to protect the people?
It was a choice that would destroy an ordinary man.
But a hero is no ordinary man, is he?
For a true hero, master Wayne, finds a way to choose...
...both.
You're right, Alfred.
I know what I have to do.
Fuck Gotham! I'm saving Robin!
- And I?
- No, I've got to get out of here.
I've got to save Robin and stop Sweet-Tooth!
And I've got to stop Two-Face.
This looks like a job for Kwan Ri.
Oh, good bye, Sir.
I'm borrowing the B@boat.
Good luck, Kwan Ri.
And prepare yourself, Sweet-Tooth!
My most well known nemesis.
Tonight you're taking no hostages.
And tonight, I'm taking no prisoners!