Hey. Have you been watching the news?
I sure have. That nut-chap Sweet-Tooth is gonna poison our water supply!
This is even worse then when the Joker poisoned the water supply.
Or when Scare-Crow poisoned the water supply.
Or when Killer Crock poisoned the water supply.
That's how he died! The poor fool.
Hey, don't worry pal. Kill Robin or risk blowing up our own heads.
It's obvious, what we should vote for.
It's a no-brainer.
You guys better get on Twitter.
[Both]Why?
B@man just tweeted. And I don't think you're gonna like it!
[Both] Huh?
Citizens of Gotham. If you're choosing to kill Robin, then - hashtag -
we can't be friends.
I'm saving Dick. So say good-bye to your heads!
Deal with it!
- I don't believe it!
- B@man really going through with this?
Holy twitt! Gotham has jumped out of the frying pan
and into the fire as B@mans latest tweet has send
the citizen ...[???]... a panic.
Experts are saying that if B@man does save Robin,  Sweet-Tooth
will undoubtedly release the warhead.
Mr. President! Mr. President, we have a situation in Gotham!
Have you guys been watching the news?
Eh, this is the white house! We're always watching the news!
Then what are we going to do? Gotham city has declared a state of emergency!
We'll... we'll send them the national guard.
There's not enough time you're sending the national guard!
Not enough time, before B@man rushes in there and gets everybody killed!
What do you expect me to do, Johnson?
I DON'T KNOW!!!
Nobody could stop B@man, that's why he's my favorite superhero!
There is one man - who could stop him.
Mr. president.
Hand me the phone, please.
[Phone rings with the beginning of 'bad to the bone']
Hello B@man, it's Superman!... I mean...
Aaaah... I mean...
This is... one of Superman's friends.
I'll get Superman for you, hold on.
Yo! Sups!
Ah... What is it... Snoop Dogg?
You got a phone-call, motherfucker...
Woah, another one? Alright.
Hey... hey tell everybody to turn the party down, okay? And ah...
And... and tell Wonderwoman...
that her eagle brassiere can be found on the floor of my bedroom...
And... and that I saw her naked boobies. Hey B@man, it's Superman.
No, Superman, this isn't B@man.
Well then WHO IS IT?
This is the president of the united states of America. Barack Obama.
[annoyed] Huh...!
What do YOU want, Mr. president? And make it quick, I'm expecting a phone-call.
Superman, I don't know if you've been watching the news.
But there's a whole heap of trouble brewing over in Gotham city.
And I need to ask for a super favor.
You see, folks out there are scared. They're scared of a man, who's dressed up like a bat.
- B@man?
- You guessed it, Superman.
They are afraid about what he might do.
You see, if the B@man saves the bird-boy, then that candyman is gonna destroy the whole city.
And that's not sympathico.
So I want you to fly over there, and I want you to bring this B@man-fellow in.
You want me to arrest B@man, but - he's a hero.
Oh, I'm not so sure about that, Superman.
You see, you and me, we got a lot in common.
We're both fighting for the american way best we can.
But that B@man, he's a different breed.
He don't seem to give a ...[???]... for the law or the country.
[sigh] I don't know... I don't know, Barack, I ah...
I don't think he's gonna let me take him in alive.
Any means necessary, Superman.
Hey! I knew I could count on you. I'm a huge fan.
I follow you on the Twitter and everything.
Oh really...
Yeah, you should tweet at me some time.
My handle is 'The real Barack Obama', 'cuz some smart-ass named Bruce Wayne
took the name 'Barak Obama' and he just tweets about how dumb I am.
[sighs] Well, good luck, Superman.
Tell Snoop Dogg I say hi, and then go give that B@man one for the people by the people.
[Reference to: Speech of Abraham Lincoln to the end of the war northern vs.southern states ofamerica to end the slavery. Just turned over.]
Show him, that our way works.
Yeah...
The american way.
Truth and liberty
and justice all are in jeopardy
tonight
All we cherish here
and all the values that we hold dear
are in the balance tonight.
'Cuz it's America
and we're american
And in America we do what's right.
The firetruck's here for the kitty in the tree
Oh, the american way!
And if the cops can't come, you can always call on me
That's the american way!
Because I can,
therefor I will.
I'm coming for you tonight, B@man.
We could have been friends, but this is what happens,
when you don't return people's phone-calls!
Tonight it's personal,
I'm unleashing my arsenal
To rain blood
tonight
Tonight I'm gonna save my bro
and if all of Gotham has got to go
then so be it!
'Cuz it's America
And I'm american
And in America I do what I like!
If money can't fix it, then I haven't found it yet
Oh, the american way!
Be a born billionaire and have your butler building jets
That's the american way!
Because I can -
save my friend
I'll do what I have to
I'm my own boss, man!
Tonight we're taking back the town
We've got a bat-trap set
we're gonna catch the clown
In Gotham - tonight!
We've got a warhead ready in the water supply
Tonight the bat and his bull won't fly
So Gotham, good night!
'Cuz it's America
and we're american
and in America we fight
Never gonna win, 'til your enemies are dead
Oh, the american way!
spreading threat and blowing up their heads
That's the american way
Because I can - dy
do as I please
I'm spreading chocolate
on Gotham's cheese
The letter of the law is a capital 'S'
Oh, the american way!
We're all just pawns in a fucking game of chess
That's the american way
A briefcase filled with two dollar bills
Oh, the american way!
Inharitance trust funds, million dollar bills
That's the american -
not quite canadian -
most of us are mexican
american -
way
yeah!