Commissioner, the last of the squad cars were just blown to smithereens.
And the entire swat team has been rushed to intensive care.
Boy, you feel like I'm really flopping this one up.
No, Sir. Don't you beat yourself up about this.
Well, you tell those troops to fall back.
Abandon Gotham square. We just can't get through that barricade.
[Evil laughing]
Listen to that, would you?
That's the sound of chaos.
Good and plenty.
That's the true nature of humanity, Robin.
I mean, see how quickly I made society crumble.
Brought the city to it's knees.
And all it took was a [Friendface] poll and some guns.
Months of meticulous planning...
several hundred thugs, countless man hours...
a cartoonishly large sour warhead and millions upon millions of dollars.
Not to mention all the money I spent on fucking candy!
Ah but you can do that for free any time you want.
Shut up you idiot! Go!
The point is, Robin...
don't count on B@man coming to save you.
Because he can't.
He won't.
Because nothing can get through my barricade.
I got rogues on the rooftops, rogues on the street, rogues in the sewers.
I got hostages dressed up as rogues and rogues dressed up as hostages.
I mean, face it. B@man couldn't get here even if he tried.
It's literally impossible.
- I have anticipated every single freaking thing...
- [Wosh - Airplane]
What was that? [scared]
Oh, no! Sweet-Tooth, you're new in town, aren't you?
Oh, gasp. But that means you don't know about the plane.
Plane? What plane?
[Boom] Hey, what happened to the lights?
Well, the power to the whole block has been knocked out.
Wait, B@man's got a plane? Where did he get a plane?
Hey!
What is these little... dots?!?
Woah, we're getting shot at by some kind of robot [???].
The wounds aren't lethal but they are crippling.
Sad Bastion, shoot down that plane!
[???] I haven't a clue what to do.
I can't sees nothings.
Do it you dum-dums! I'm taking Robin with me.
Hey, take it down! Take down that plane!
Oh, ah! The bullets are [???] and hitting my knees!
Our weapons is worthless.
It's shooting missiles at us!
- Oh, my rips!
- My spine!
Oh, my tibia!
Argh!
Oh Scott, it's B@man!
Run for your nine lives! [Kiss]
Come back! Come back, you insects!
I'm not done with you yet!
You thought that a barricade could stop me?
Think again!
I'm the god damn B@man!
You!
Where is Sweet-Tooth?
He went that way.
Into the famous fun house candy factory of Gotham.
- Buah.
- Into the candy factory. How predictable.
You're getting stale, Sweet-Tooth.
No, B@man, please don't hurt me! Because...
I'm one of the hostages. Ouch!
- God.
- That's enough!
You!
The national guard will take it from here, B@man.
Like hell, they will.
I'm saving Robin.
And when I find Sweet-Tooth, I'll be the one to take him down.
The authorities can handle Sweet-Tooth.
Who I'm here for - is you.
What?
I've be ordered by the president of the united states to place you under arrest. Ever heard of him?
Ah, yeah.
It ends tonight, B@man.
Or should I say...
Butthead?
[Very high tone]
You're in my way!
Now get out of it, or I'm going through you!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
You wanna fight me?
Well, I can't say that I won't enjoy this.
Looks like we can finally see which one of us...
deserves those Twitter followers.
I am a man of justice.
I am a man of might.
I am a man of vengeance.
I am a man of the night.
You're such a sycophantic suck up.
How can you call yourself a man?
You say you fight for truth and justice?
I say you're working for the man, man.
You line your mask with lead.
But I can see into your soul.
I see a scared little boy.
Behind the cape and the cowl.
Fuck you! I'm gonna kick your ass.
Fuck you! I'm taking you down. Fuck you!
You want to be the man? You've got to beat the man.
I'm gonna show you what it means to be a man, man.
I've learned a lot about life.
Since I got myself a bro.
You mean your tiny little sidekick?
You guys are so adorable.
You're only jealous, man.
It's so obvious, so clear. Ha!
Come on! Me with a sidekick?
That's right.
I've got one for you, right here.
Fuck you! I'm gonna kick your ass.
Fuck you! I'm taking you down. Fuck you!
You want to be the man? You've got to beat the man.
I'm gonna show you what it means to be a man, man.
Hey, hey! Hey, who turned out the lights?
All of your toys amuse me.
The boat, the b@mobile, the bike, the plane.
But you can't grappling hook me.
Can't hit me with your boomerang, naw!
You look cool in your tights.
Thanks.
For an alien dick.
What?!?
How about some kryptonite tonight?
- I'm onto your shtick!
- Fuck you!
Fuck you! I'm gonna kick your ass.
Fuck you! I'm taking you down. Fuck you!
You want to be the man? You've got to beat the man.
I'm gonna show you what it means to be a man.
Fuck you!