[Evil laugh]
Sweet-Tooth! Show yourself!
Life is a lot like candy, isn't it, B@man?
Sure, it's sugar coated on the outside but it's sour at the core.
We both know it.
The only difference between you and me is that I've managed to see the sweet side.
But you just keep trying to take that bite out of crime.
And for what?
For a city that voted to kill the only thing you've ever loved?
The whole world is just meaningless sugary fluff, B@man.
Mama always said life is like a box of chocolates. [Forrest Gump]
So tell me, B@man.
Why aren't you eating...
Huh!
Huh, how did you hold my [???]?
I'm coming for you, Sweet-Tooth!
[???]
Sweet-Tooth!
Hold it right there, B@man!
One more step and the boy-plunder takes a dive into that vat...
- ...of boiling hot chocolate.
- No, Sweet-Tooth!
Put Robin down! Don't throw him into that vat of boiling hot chocolate.
This is between you and me!
You're right, B@man. This is between you and me.
It always has been. I'll let Robin go.
- Oops! Butterfingers!
-Oh!
- Whoa! B@man!
- ROBIN!
I'm falling into that vat of melted hot chocolate!
- Oh, no!
- Greyson Dive!
B@man!
Hold on!
Oh, no!
I'm done for!
Yay!
Argh!
Woah ho ho!
Now he's red-hot!
- Hey, what's that?
- What?
Oh, you're not coming any closer! You're not coming any closer!
- Come on! Come on!
- Argh!
[???]
I'm gonna Crunch you in two!
Oh, come on, B@man.
Give me a break!
Oh, I'll give you a break!
Oh, come on, B@man! What you gonna do? Kill me?
Do it, B@man!
See if the Snoz-berries taste like Snoz-berries. [Willy Wonka]
Argh!
No!
I won't kill you.
But I don't have to save you...
...from that vat of boiling hot chocolate.
Oh, which one?
I am falling into that vat!
Oh, I've got one last treat for you, B@man!
And it's a real Whopper.
Computer, deploy the warhead, please.
Warhead deployed.
- Water supply contamination in 10 seconds.
- Oh, no!
Quick!
Come on, Robin. We're getting out of here.
Well, it's a good thing B@man broke through that barricade.
Huh? B@man, what's happening? Where are we going?
We're going to the b@plane. And then far, far away from here.
But what about Gotham?
Forget Gotham, Robin.
Water supply contamination in 5 seconds.
What?
Because for a minute there, I was worried.
But it looks like everything has been taken care of.
Forget Gotham? No! No, I can't do that!
We have to do something! We have to save the citizens!
Robin, you don't understand.
Those citizens...
they voted to kill you!
To save themselves.
And murder us!
I refuse to believe that.
Water supply contaminated.
Oh, no!
So let's celebrate with my favorite pastime.
Water shot!
- Water shot!
- Straight from the faucet.
Alright, from the faucet.
Okay.
Here I go.
- Yummy, yummy.
-You enjoy your time. Hm!
Oh.
- Commissioner? Commissioner!
- Oh, oh.
What's wrong? Is it the water?
I know, I'll check as well.
Oh, it was the water!
Well it's too late now, Robin. Now, quickly. Get to the b@plane. We've got to get out of Gotham.
Before we get thirsty.
B@man, look!
What?
I pulled up the results of that [Friendface] poll on my iPhone. See for yourself!
Vote ...[???]...
People of Gotham have chosen...
You know. I may think that Robin sucks...
but if B@man likes him, then I'm gonna help him out.
B@man saved my life. And if paying him back means imploding my own head, then fucking yeah!
You can't kill someone to save your own hide.
B@man taught me that.
What's so bad about Robin anyway?
He's just trying to stand up for something.
Yeah! He's just a lone kid like you and me.
No older than my son's age.
You mess with one of us...
you mess with all of us!
They chose the warhead!
Those ragit pinhead puppets of Gotham.
I love them!
You see, B@man.
Gotham is worth saving.
This city just showed you...
that it's full of people...
ready to believe in good.
You're right, Robin.
Gotham has taught me that it's full of people...
who really believe...
in good.
But it's too late!
It's too late, Robin. What have I done?
It may be too late for us.
But if you can put aside your foolish pride...
there is someone who could help us.
Who?
[Ring-tone: bad to the bone]
Uah!
Uagh!
Hello.
Hi.
Superman, it's...
B@man!
Hold on.
This is one of Superman's friends.
- I'll get Superman for you.
- Oh, thanks.
What do you want? This is Superman!
Hi, Superman. It's B@man.
I, uhm...
need...
I need a super favor.
Gotham city is done for. People's heads are imploding all over the place, and...
It's all my fault.
I need you to save the city!
Phh. Yeah, what am I supposed to do about it?
Ah...
I don't know. But - I mean, you can do something!
You're the only one who's...
powerful enough.
Yeah! What does that even matter? Everyone still likes you more then me.
So why should I help you?
You beat me up and you yelled at me!
You made this bed, B@man. Now you gotta sleep in it.
He's really pissed.
Keep going!
Ah...
Look, uhm... Clark.
I'm sorry!
Okay? I...
I forgot...
what it means to be a super hero.
But we're not that different.
You and me. At our hearts.
I mean really all super heroes are pretty much...
the same.
We're all just orphans.
I'm an orphan.
You're an orphan.
Robin's an orphan.
- Spiderman is an orphan.
- Yeah!
Spiderman is an orphan. So is Ironman.
And Cyclops and Wolverine and all of the X-Men. Listen, the point is, that...
something bad happened to us once.
When we were young.
So we dedicated our whole lives...
to do a little bit of good.
That's why we got into this crazy super hero business.
Not to be the most popular.
Or even the most powerful.
Because if that were the case, hell...
you got the rest of us put out of the job.
You can fly.
You can crush things.
With your bare hands!
You've got x-ray vision.
You can see girls tatties whenever you want!
You know, Clark...
I think that maybe the reason that I was such an asshole to you...
I think you're cool, man!
I think you're cool too.
Why the fuck aren't we friends?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
We totally should be friends.
Maybe we can hang out in your cave some time.
Yeah, maybe.
Or maybe we can hang out in your ice fortress.
In Antarctica.
Always cool!
And you've got Krypto the superdog.
- He's cool. Dogs are cool.
- Oh...
Some people think Krypto is stupid.
Fuck them!
You know what? Some people think that Robin is stupid.
But those people are pretentious douchebags.
Because literally...
the only difference between me and Robin...
is our costumes.
Robin's cool.
Krypto's cool.
Antman is cool.
The Adam is cool.
Plasticman!
Argh! Gloves, capes, masks! Argh, superheroes are cool, man!
Helping people is cool.
And you?
You're god damn great at helping people.
So come on!
There's a city right now full of people that need your help.
So where is that man, Clark?
Where's that man who can jump over a building?
Where's that man who's more powerful than a Locomotive?
Where's that man who is faster than a gun?
Where is that Superman?
I'm right here!
I know what I have to do.
I have to fly faster than I've ever flown before.
B@man...
I'll see you on the other side.
[B@man and Robin] Thank you, Superman!
I made it to space.
Well... Here goes nothing!
I've got one last treat for you, B@man.
And it's a real whooper!
Computer, deploy the warhead, please.
- Warhead deployed. Water supply contamination in 10 seconds.
- Take this, rogue warhead carrying robot!
Son of a bitch! What do we do with the warhead?
Sun of a bitch!
That's it!
Back to outer space!
Well, good bye.
Good bye, earth.
Good luck, Superman.
Thanks, Venus.
Hey, Captain Marvel.
It's Superman!