[Both] Thank you, Superman!
Superman!
I did it!
- Oh!
- What?
- How?
I flew around the world -
[whispered]What?
until it went back in time -
I grabbed the warhead -
then threw it into the sun!
And that's -
why they call me Superman!
[Both] Wow!
That's amazing!
Yeah, yeah...
It's a pretty neat trick.
Too bad I can only do it once -
Bruce.
- Yeah it's sure...
- Oooh!
Wait! How do you know my secret identity?
I just followed you home after the first day we met.
Well, there you go! [laughs]
I'm Dick Grayson.
Hey, everybody! Look! It's B@man! He saved the city again!
[Cheers]
Now, now! Calm down, everybody. I didn't save Gotham.
In fact I very - nearly let you all to your doom.
Oh!
I saved my friend.
But it was Superman. He's the one who saved Gotham city.
He's the real hero today.
Well, B@man's just being modest. Let's hear for that other guy.
Three cheers for Captain Marvel!
- Guys! Say...
- Cheers! Cheers!
come on, stop. I'm not used to this kind of attention, I...
Alright...
You know, Clark, we should work together more often. God, that would be cool! Imagine it:
You, me, Robin, a couple other cool guys...
We'd be like a league for justice.
Hey! Yeah, I like that, but, I mean...
How would we call ourselves? I mean what do you call a league for justice anyway?
I have the perfect name.
The superfriends!
- Yeah!
- Ooh!
The superfriends!
That's great! That's great, I gotta tweet that! Where's my phone?
Hey guys. Got room for one more?
SPIDERMAN!!!
[Sounds of agreement and surprise]
He's agile as hell!
He sure is!
Help him up! [four times]
Spiderman, you wanna join the superfriends?
That's right.
- Cool!
- Wow!
Hey! Maybe now we can fight some of your villains for a change!
Yeah, I mean not a lot of people know this, but my villains are actually pretty cool.
[evil laughing]
Now the world shall tremble before the might of Mr. Mxyzptlk!
Here we go again.
Yeah!
Alright.
Nice ...[???]...
Hey guys, what did I miss?
The green Lantern!
This guy!
Now we're talking.
It seems so funny as I look back on the folly of my way
I climbed as hight as one can climb on the ...[???]...
I scaled the highest mountain, did a pirouette at the tippity top
but when you gotta get down, gotta get down, gotta get down you need someone to count on
Some mark their friendship with bracelets and lockets
Some measure their friendship with silver and gold
Some mark their friendship with matching tatoos
We forge our friendship by saving the world
I wanna be your friend forever!
I wanna be a modern dancer!
What a super queer thing to say! That came out of nowhere.
I wanna be your friend forever!
Pass me the cup of kinship
Meet me at my place: The fortress of friendship
I wanna be your friend forever!
I wanna see the Eiffel tower
With the power of the superfriends you're never alone
I wanna be your friend forever!
I wanna play Nintendo
Who needs Nintendo
when you got a friend? Yo!
Like a bat in the sun I'm losing my guano
Aaaaaaah
I've only known darkness all my days
Aaaaaah
Dude, it's cool, it's chill, we're totally here for you
Will there still be scary times?
Yeah!
And sad times?
Cool!
Tequila times
I've got the limes
I wanna be your friend forever!
I wanna meet the Dali Lama
With the power of the superfriends you're never alone
I wanna be your friend forever!
I wanna learn to play the banjo
Who needs a banjo when you got a man show
I wanna be your friend forever!
Finally, I've found a friend, I've finally found a friend
Super friend
Super duper friend...
One Man
many friends
going down a road that never ends
superfriends
super bros
super hearts with super souls
We're like long lost brothers
who found each other
and love each other
like family.
Long lost brothers
who found each other
and love each other
like family.
Long lost brothers
who found each other
and love each other
like family.
Long lost brothers
who found each other
and love each other
like family.
Rogues are we
no more dark, sad, lonely
B@man!
Poor master Bruce, poor Mr Wayne
lonely caboose on a one car train...