You're late!
Late?
What's it matter?
Look at this mornings Prophet...
"The boy who lived does it again!"
"The dark lord dead for good!"
I knew it!
We've backed the wrong side...
again!
Calm yourself, Yaxley!
All us Death Eaters are going
to Azkaban now!
No!
No! No!
Do you have what I sent you for or not?
Yeah, I got it.
I had to break into the ministry for it,
but I got it.
Excellent.
...(???)...
The dark lord not dead more than a day
and they've already got
the wizardcops out after us!
Damn those wizardcops!
Well, non of that matters anymore
as long as we have this.
Who do you think you are?
We don't stand a chance
against the wizardcops!
Not even you, Lucius Malfoy!
Don't ever tell me what I can't do
I'd watch my tongue if I were you
for all we know, you-know-who
could be watching us
He can't be!
He's dead!
That never stopped our plans before!
You've no idea what I have in store!
D'you really think that you'd be at my door
if we had nothing to discuss
He may be gone,
but that is just as well...
So come inside, don't you fret
for it's not over yet!
Evil plans!
We are making evil plans!
Evil deeds with evil hands!
We love making evil plans!
Lucius Malfoy,
why have you called us here? Raw!
What do we do, Lucius?
There's nothing to do. The dark lord is dead,
Harry Potter wins, end of story!
Yes, I know, I know!
He marries Ginny.
They live happily ever after.
There was literally no way
to move foreward from this point!
Then why are we all here?
I was just getting to it.
Harry Potter!
We're in this sorry state because of him!
And I think of all the chances
we had to destroy him!
Why, if we had destroyed him
at his first year at Hogwarts,
we'd be ruling the world right now!
Yes, Lucius.
No one is arguing that. Raw!
But what does it matter?
We can't change the past ...(???)...
Oh?
I know it seems impossible,
we've been thrown off our track.
But if we can't move forward,
why shouldn't we move back?
Friends and companions of evil and sin.
Think not of loss,
but a new way to win.
For what is present without a beginning
to start it all?
Go on...
There is a boy that everyone knows
The plan is simple
I propose that we choke the weed
before it grows up
and ends it all
Do you follow me?
No.
The Dark Lord would have survived,
had they never met...
Wait, wait, wait, so you're saying
that he wouldn't be destroyed?
He'd be alive, what don't you get?
Still not understanding...
With Potter gone, the future will be set!
Aaahhhhhh!
So it's not over yet!
Evil plans!
What a brilliant evil plan!
Malfoy, you're an evil man!
We love making evil plans!
So it is decided!
We shall use this timeturner to go back in time
to Harry Potters first year at Hogwarts!
We'll destroy him before he ever gets
a chance to destroy us!
My friends, I think we're going back!
Who's with me?
Our history is nothing more
than what the losers settle for
So look alive, and don't forget
that it's not over
It's not over,
No, it's not over yet!
Platform 9, platform 10.
Nothing in between.
Someone ...(???)...
to get to platform 9 and three quarters?