- Hey, what's up my best friend?
- Hey Ron!
Who's this guy?
I don't know, he was here when I got here,
he's asleep and I think he‘s homeless.
Gross.
We kinda got separated at the
train station and ah...
you forgot this.
You know man, everyone
in the wizarding world loves my scar.
Why don't you keep it?
Really?
Wow!
Looks good, man.
Thanks!
- Damn it, now I wanna give you something...
- No, it's okay...
Uh! D'you wanna rat?
No! Aaaah!
It's...
- it's my rat.
- Oh, your rat...Hi...
His name's Scabbers
and he's been in my family for like...
a hundred years.
In fact I think my parents found him
the same night your parents died.
Weird...
I know, weird.
Hey, d'you wanna Berty Bott's
everyflavoured candy bean?
Sure!
They have every flavour in the entire world.
They even have a poopy flavoured one,
but it's so rare
you'll never be lucky enough to get it.
What'd you get?
Broken computer?
That's gross...
I can't even remember the last time
I got a candy flavoured one.
What have you got?
Toffee...
Well, I give up on these...
Hey!
What if we wash these beans down with some
of the greatest snacks in the entire world?
Red Vines!
And I got them right here in my bag, ahm...
Crookshanks!
Oh! Bad ...(???)...
Sorry!
Sometimes he just crawls
into the darndest places...
It's okay.
But just next time...
Oh my god! Night Troll!!!
I'm not a Night Troll!
I'm a little girl!
My name's Hermione Granger.
Jimminy Crickets!
You're Harry Potter!
Oh, yeah! Weird, right?
Oh! I'm such a big fan!
Say, would you sign my petition?
No! No, he doesn't want to!
I'm collecting signatures
for house elf sufferage.
You see, I just think it's awful that some creatures
in the wizarding world aren't treated equally,
just because they were born as ugly sickly
little creatures with big dump noses.
And I think that we -
I mean the elfs -
are just as good as anybody.
Not to mention the world
just isn't made for those little guys.
Did you know over sixhundred house elfes die
in entirely unrelated incidents every year?
Stop talking.
I‘ll sign it, just don't send me an e-mail.
Oh no, I won't!
- Thanks, Harry!
- There you go...
Hey, are we the first people you've asked?
There's only one other name on here...
That is my name.
Oh! Well then, there you go...
Her-my-ONE...
Wow!
So Harry Potter,
did you really grow up
in the muggleworld?
Yeah. Found out that I was
a wizard like two minutes ago.
Yeah. I grew up in the muggleworld too.
My parents are Muggles.
Muggle-dentists.
Candy from the trolley?
I'm ever so excited
to finally go to Hogwarts!
Yeah, it's ‚‘caus Hogwarts is
the best place in the entire world...
Well, yeah.
And we'll be/to be tought by so many
great witches and wizards like Albus Dumbledore.
Who's... who the hell is Albus Dumbledore?
He's only the bestest,
most bravest...
Most wisest, most talented...
- ...beautiful...
- most beautiful wizard that ever lived.
Candy from the trolley?
And my dream of dreams
is to some day graduate top of my class.
Candy from the tro....!?!
Candy from the trolley?
Yes!
At last!
My parents say that candy's
bad for your teeth.
Avada...
Aaaah, expelliarmus!
Take that, you bastard-ass!
Oh god, damn it!
At least I still have a...
Oh! No...what?
Where did it go?
Oh!
Shit!
No/Well, that's piss.
Wait, was I drinking piss?
You must be Harry Potter!
You just k...
Why did you kill the candylady?!
No, kids!...Kids! Stop it!
Kids! Don't be afraid of me!
I'm not dangerous
and I'm not homeless - anymore.
My name is Remus Lupin.
I'm your new defense against
the dark arts teacher
and that so called candylady
was a deatheater.
She was about two seconds away
from killing you, your little friend
and his pet Night Troll.
What's a deatheater?
What is that?
It's a servant of You-Know-Who!
I figured a few might show off when they heard
that Harry Potter was added (was headed) to Hogwarts.
They can be real hardass dickheads!
What's the matter with you, guys?
Oh, shit!
You guys are kids!
Better watch my damn mouth around
you little bastards.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Shoot.
I gotta watch my damn mouth
around you little guys.
Hey! Looks like the train stopped.
- We're here!
- That‘s sudden.
Harry.
Come here.
Listen, this year...
I don't want you to be worried
about deatheaters or that Sirius Black or...
or werewolfs or anything else
that could kill you right now.
Alright?
Because as long as you're at Hogwarts with me
and headmaster Dumbledore there to protect you,
you're perfectly safe.
Trust me, Harry...
No one in Hogwarts hates you.
What the devil is going on heeeeeere?