Hey, what (the devil) are you doing here? Get off the train.
Why Remus Lupin?
Severus Snape.
That’s snape.
He’s evil!
Get off the train!
Not you boy!
You sit!
So you must be Harry Potter.
I can tell by just not talking to you that you’re a
no good good-for-nothing-nobody like your father.
You know what?
Just leave the poor kid alone, okay?
God, you haven’t changed at all since our shool days in Hogwarts!
Hey, Harry:
don’t pay any attention
- to Sour grape Snape.
- How dare you speak that name?
I said it before snape
and I’ll say it again.
You always have been
and you always will be
a butt trumpet!
You know why?
Cause you’ve got a trumpeting butt!
No, I haven’t!
Yes!
Stop it!
Hey, guys. I’m Snape. Come on!
Harry it’s not!
That doesn't sound anything like my butt!
Ha, who looks stupid now?
You do!
All right.
We’re both adults now.
I demand you stop acting like a child
or I’ll tell Dumbledore
and have you expelled.
I don’t think so Snape.
Cause I’m a teacher now.
You can’t expell me. I’ll expell you!
In fact...
You’re expelled! I just expelled you!
What? That’s absurd!
You can’t expell me!
We can’t expell each other.
Can we?
I won’t pretend to know.
Well...
than I will.
Snape... vanished!
Wow!
What a jerk!
Yeah.
But listen, Harry.
Don’t let him bother you, okay?
You’re finally where you belong.
At Hogwarts.
The place where -- your parents spend
the best years of their lives.
So go on Harry.
Go and find what you were always meant to be.
In the home you never knew you had.
I’ll see you, Lupin.
See you in class.
Home.
I've heard the word before,
but it never meant much more
than just a thing I've never had.
A pleace. They say, "Hey, know your place!"
But I've never had a place to even know,
or a face that I could go to
if I needed someone there...
I'm laughing
it's hard to hide a smile
My god, it's been a while
since I have had a reason to.
To think
it's been here all along
somewhere to belong,
and a reason,
a something-to-believe-in
I've finally found it,
a place where I'm wanted...
This must be how it feels
to have a home
I used to dream about it
but never schemed or counted
on fantasies or wishes
it breaks a man to see what he misses
And so many nights I'd pray
for a better life,
a better day
but I never thought that it'd come true
now that it's finally here,
I don't know what to do
don't know what to do
and I'm trying not to cry
Hey Harry.
Let’s go get sorted!
This must be how it feels
to have a home
I've finally made it
I've hoped and I've waited
and for the first time in my life,
I don't feel so alone
My heart starts to heal
to know this is real.
This is how it must feel
to have a...
- home!
- Gryffindor! Gryffindor! Gryffindor!