Good morning, Gryffindors.
Morning miss Chang.
Carry your books for you?
Charms sucks! Potions sucks! Transfiguration sucks!
The best class is definitely satanic rituals.
Hey, guys. Where are we heading?
Woah, woah, woah! No, no, no!
Harry and I are going to Quidditch try-outs.
Quidditch? But you can’t try-out for Quidditch!
My parents say that sports are bad for your teeth.
I don’t care.
Why don’t we try-out for an extra curricular activity
that is intellectually stimulating and teeth-friendly?
We could try-out for wizard chess club or wizard-debate.
Okay. Listen, why don’t you go and to that lame boring stuff.
Ron and I are gonna do the fun dangerous stuff.
Yeah. Or we could do something together.
No, Hermin. We can’t.
Because Harry and I wanna have fun and get girlfriends.
And we can’t do that with you just sagging along all the time.
So, why don’t you go hang out with Moaning Myrtle?
Cause she thinks I’m annoying.
You know, maybe I’ll just  try-out for Quidditch.
I mean, it’s not like you can kick me off the field.
[cough]
I [???] my guts out.
Hey guys, who invited Boo Radley?
Get the hell of the field, Hermin!
I’m not kidding! -- Beat it!
Alright. Guys, who’s ready to win the house cup?
Wooh!
That’s what I like to hear.
So, what do we got here? -- Quidditch.
The most ancient and silliest of all wizarding sports.
Some of  you may know, the Gryffindor PeeWee
team hasn’t won a match in 14 years. But:
I think that with me as your coach and you little stallions as my team
there’s no way we’re losing to Slytherin or Ravenclaw or Jigglypuff.
Alright. So, who here has ever played Quidditch before, ha?
That’s okay. That’s okay. Am, how about – how about
riding a broom? Anyone ever ridden a broom before?
- Just stretching.
- Oh!
Alright. Am, has anyone ever thrown or caught a ball?
Something was thrown at me once.
Yeah, it was!
[???] Thomas, Finigan.
- [???]
- 'What up, boss?
Alright. I want you guys  to take these and practice
hitting each other with it, okay? You guys are beaters.
Is this right?
Yes Dean. That’s good. That’s very good.
Ron, you’re keeper!
Alright.
Harry! Harry.
Yeah, coach?
Listen, Harry. You’re really the most important guy, okay?
See this thing? It’s called the snitch. Now, during the game
it's gonna sprout wings and fly all over this giant stadium
and it’s your job to catch it.
Sounds easy enough.
Alright. You’re the seeker, Harry. Just like your dad.
You knew my dad?
Yeah! I know him. He and I used to play Quidditch together.
I don’t know if you know this, Harry.
But – I was your dad’s best friend.
Oh, I thought the traitor, Sirius Black,
was my dad’s best friend.
No. Who… who told you that? Did you dad tell you?
Uh, I didn’t get a chance to talk to him after he died.
Good. It’s probably just Sirius said that.
Alright, let’s play some Quidditch!
Get on the broom, Harry. Get on the broom there
and ah make my best friend proud!
- And who is that? Hagrid?
- No, it’s not Hagrid. Snape!
What are you even doing here? Gryffindor
has the field today. I reserved it weeks ago.
Not according to my shift rules.
Slytherin has the field – so that we may
try out our new seeker: Draco Malfoy.
Alright. Listen, that it impossible, okay?
I’ve got a slip from Dumbledor.
Maybe… maybe he accidentally signed
the field out to both of our teams.
That’s absurd!
You’re absurd!
What? Say that again to my face!
- You’re absurd!
- That’s absurd!
- Arrgh!
Let’s see this slip from Dumbledore if it really does exist.
Fine, if got it right here.
[Crookshanks: Miow!]
[Snape and Lupin: Arrgh!]
Keep that… keep that thing out of my thing! Okay?
Sorry! I’m  sorry!
What was it even doing… uh!
Alright, here!
Why? This is preposterous! I demand
to see Dumbledore at once.
Fine. Let’s go!
Alright, Let’s go!
Well, I think they're gonna be a while. I might
as well take this time to buzz out a funky tune.