Hey! - Potter!
Hey, Potter!
Potter! – Potter!
What Malfoy?
I drew a picture of you.
Okay.
Let’s see. – What?
You see what’s happening to you in it.
It’s you getting hit in the head with a Quaffle.
Oh ho ho…
Don’t you feel foolish?
Look that’s me. That one. That’s me.
And I’m in the background laughing and pointing at you.
We are having a right good time, aren’t we?
Pay special attention to the shading on your sweater. It’s -- it’s rather good.
It’s actually -- quite good.
It’s probably -- it’s probably the best I’ve ever done.
Actually...
Can I have that back? Wait! No!
I’m taking it!
What do you think of that, Potter, ha?
I’ve stolen your favorite drawing.
Look: what do you think of this? -- Uhhh!
- Goyle, paste it!
- Uhhh!
Now look what you’ve done, Potter!
You wait ‘till my father hears about this!
He’ll say:
Draco -- you god damn little poofer.
Why don’t you stop your whining and
learn to use the potty like a normal human.
And then -- and then he will pull down my diaper...
...and scold me for the mess I’ve left in it
and spank my cheeks as red as cherries.
That really sucks, Malfoy.
But: I just can’t believe you still wear a diaper.
All respectable wizards do.
How -- how do you expect me to use a potty?
I could fall into that monstrosity.
At least I can draw!
You know what, Malfoy? Leave Harry alone.
I mean it’s not like your drawing is that good.
Oh ho ho. Uh...
Not -- that -- good?
Let’s see you trying to draw something better you little mudblood.
Hey!
Yeah, Hermin! Let’s see you draw some right now in front of everybody!
- [Others:] Yah!
- [Goyle:] Come on! Draw something! Come on!
Guys, guys! Stop! Stop it! This is no way to go about this, okay?
Maybe I just...
Hermione can’t draw.
Hermione cannot draw!
She only reads books,
so she cannot draw.
Even if she’s reading a ‘how to draw’ book.
Hermione can’t draw.
...
[???]
What the hell is going around here?
Stop dancing like that! Guys!
Stop! Hey, this song isn’t even that funny, you know.
Oh yeah? Let’s see you sing something right now in front of everybody.
- Let’s sing anything...
-Lupin can’t sing.
- Yes, I can sing!
- Lupin can’t sing. Lupin cannot sing.
I’m Remus freakin... alright! I – that sucks! Hey guys!
[???] Everybody Hermione can’t draw together!
[Draco:] Oh yeah!
Hermione can’t draw.
Hermione cannot draw.
She only reads books,
so she cannot draw.
Even when she’s reading a ‘how to draw’ book.
[and so on...]
Granger, don’t you have somewhere else to be?
Yeah!
Do I have somewhere to be?
No!
All my dreams
I'm chasing after,
they don't need
all this laughter...
I take a grain of salt,
stiff upper lip.
It's not their fault
I'm not as hip.
Wake up kid, you know you're more than this...
I'm the smartest person
that I've ever met.
So why do I allow myself to
possibly forget:
There's so much I know how to do,
so much more than all of you.
The only thing I wish I knew
was how to make them see
the girl that I can be....
I am
the coolest girl in the whole wide world
I know it
but can't show it at all.
I am
sick and tired
of low, not higher
places, where I should belong.
It's about time I proved them wrong...
Give me a shot
to show what I've got!
I'm a helluva whole lot more
and this frizzy hair,
these frumpy clothes I wear,
though I rock 'em like nobody you've seen before
'Cause I am
the coolest girl in the whole wide world
I know it
below it all.
I am
done with losin',
on with choosin'
the coolest girl on the face of the planet,
the coolest bitch on earth, god dam it!
The coolest chick you've ever seen or heard!
So you can try to break me down,
but sorry guys, I'm stickin' around!
I've thought about it, and I've found
that I am
the coolest girl!
Yeah!