Attention all Hogwarts students!
In Celebration of [???] eve we’ll be taking you for a trip to Hogsmeade.
Please go over in the courtyard with your signed Hogsmeade permission form.
Students without their permission form will be killed.
No! But they won’t be allowed to go, that’s going to be a whole lot of fun!
You know, Goyle...
...using the potty is not so bad.
I don’t know why I was afraid of it all those years.
I – I think I was concerned about falling in, but -
I have found, that if I climb on top of the potty, right?
And I put one foot on either side of the potty hole rim...
...I get a firm footing and I’m actually quite safe.
And you know, using the potty is a great time to socialize.
You simply - you look over to the stall  next to you...
...and you so have a right chat with your neighbor: Oh, hello there, good sir!
First time using the potty too, ey?
Good luck, my man!
And then simply squat...
...like so, and I do my business...
...in my diaper as usual...
...and then I undo the sidelatches and let the diaper simply fall into the potty!
Yes! Father will hear of this!
Permission form to Hogsmeade...
Have fun at Hogsmeade.
Ah, no... I’m Harry Potter!
[Umbridge is laughing - Harry joins in]
I’m sorry! I didn’t realize that I was in the presence of royalty!
Oh my god, everybody look!
It’s  Harry freakin' Potter!
-- Yay!
Oh my god, he is so dreamy!
And so rich and famous!
Mister Potter? Mister Potter? Would you play me a little song on your guitar?
Oh, wait, wait! Mister Potter? Mister Potter?
Will you sign my boob?
Oh write right over here!
OH!
I wonder what happened if I just -- broke your fingers!
Because then you wouldn’t be able to play the guitar anymore.
And then all your little friends would just leave you alone...
...and then you’d be just like Umbridge.
Except Umbridge can kick your ass. [whispered]
Now you’re a rulebreaker, Potter. And it’s time for your punishment.
- What punishment?
- Oh, it’s nothing too bad.
You just gotta take this knife...
...put it upright on a chair...
...and sit on it, patsy!
- Excuse me, Ma’am...
- Who’s disrespecting Umbridge?
-You’re gonna die, Shlongbottom!
- N-no, Ma’am!
I just came to deliver these!
What are those? Speak boy!
F-f-flowers f-f-f-for you!
F-f-f-lowers f-f-f-for me?
This must be some kind of mistake.
N-n-n-no mistake, ma’am. I was told exposely to bring them to you.
Put them on the ground and back away quickly!
Woah! Woah, woah!
They don’t seem explosive -- not poisonous...
...they smell absolutely delightful...
...and they’re snapdragons! Oh my god
that is my favorite! Who could have known that?
- Why don’t you read the card, ma’am?
- Okay, little boy!
It says: Dear Umbridge... -- That’s me!
I thought you might like these, cuty. -- Oh my...!
May I ask who the Gentleman [???] is?
Sure! It’s signed big D.
I wonder who that could be...
- Thank you, little boy!
- Aaaah!
Oh! Potter! -- ahm...
What was I saying?
You were telling me to sit on the knife.
[laughing]
That’s right! Ha, ha, ha.
How silly of me! Well, it sounds like your
mama got a little bit carried away with herself.
But she’s not an unreasonable mama. In fact -- she’s pretty cool. Right?
Right!
So what do you girls say we’re all going down
to Hogsmeade and have a little bit of fun, ha?
- Hogsmeade! Hogsmeade, everyone!
- [cheers]
Have fun in Hogsmeade.
Have fun in Hogsmeade...
Not you, Potter! You still need a permission form!
Well, I’ll tell you all about it. It’s probably gonna suck!
Bye, Ron.
What’s the matter, Malfoy? You’re not going to Hogsmeade?
Certainly not! It’s beneath my dignity.
Whatever.
Dear papa,...
...I am writing to enquirer about my Hogsmeade permission form.
I sent it to you on the very first day at school and I am
anxiously awaiting its return with your signature on it.
But- bu but don’t rush, daddy!
Missing out on trips like this allows me more time to write letters to you.
Yes. Things at Hogwarts are going quite swimmingly.
I’m the most popular boy at school [???] even Harry Potter likes me.
I’m also the darling of every classroom and the
favorite of every professor who has any sense.
Oh! Oh, most importantly I have mastered the use of the potty!
Yes, yes, I admit I was a late bloomer, but...
...you can imagine my pride as I strolled into charms class and said: Oh!
Hello gents, professor Flitwick, sorry for my tardiness.
I was -- just learning how to use the potty.
Oh, how the children laughed with me in celebration!
I like making people laugh.
I also like the potty.
I know you haven’t done so all year, but you can feel free to write me any time.
Hugs and Butterfly kisses. Your Draco. -- Oh, P.S.: ...
Tell mama to bugger off!
Hoot, hoot!
Seamus Finnigan!
Letter for Seamus Finnigan!
Hey, you there! Bird!
Yes, Malfoy?
Do you have anything in there for me, perhaps from my daddy?
Oh well, let’s see here -- hm...
No, sorry kid. Nothing from Lucius Malfoy.
Hey, cheer up, kid. D’you want a Toys ‘R us catalog?
No!
I just want to know why my daddy won’t write!
Listen, kid.
I don’t have all the answers.
I don’t even know why I can talk, really.
But as another talking animal once said:
[Splinter]
All fathers care for their son.
So hang in there, okay?
Thanks. Good bye, Hedwig.
Good bye. Cocoo! Cocoo! Cocoo...
Hey, Harry!
Harry Potter! -- Hi.
Wanna go to Hogsmead or not?
More then anything!
Well then feast your eyes on this.The Maraunders Map.
What?
It shows the current location of everyone inside Hogwarts and also
has all the secret passages out of the castle. Here. Take it.
- Wow! Who made this thing?
- Well, I certainly helps...
No, but it was me, your dad, some other guy and -- Sirius Black.
You mean my dad‘s traitor best friend?
No! NO!  I am your dad‘s traitor best...
I’m your dad‘s traitor – no!...
I am your dad’s best friend! Okay?
Don’t forget it!
- Hey Lupin. Want to go look at the full moon with me? Ha ha zombie!
- Snape!
Alright, Harry I -- I gotta go. Listen: just stay out of the shrieking shack, okay?
I’m a werewolf in there.
Wait what...?