All right, children. Have fun in Hogsmeade!
Yeah!
Oh, and don’t get killed by Sirius Black.
Pww. Mama sure does have some issues with those scamps, doesn’t she,  Big D.?
In case you were wondering: the ‘D’ stands for my weiner.
Dumbledore! You’ve send me the snapdragons, didn’t you?
- Oh yeah.
- That was so sweet.
Well, I am the headmaster. It’s my job to make all the faculty of Hogwarts feel at home.
So what do you say, Umbridge? How about we hop
on the good foot, head down to the three broomsticks,
and I would treat you the traditional
welcome to Hogwarts body-shot .
Uh, Dumbledore! Do you really do body-shots of all the new teachers?
Only the handsome ones.
Uh. Dumbledore! (You’re) making me blush!
Oh yeah? I bet
you're the one who gets
all of the boys to buy you things.
I'm sure
that you get all the girls
to beg you for their wedding rings.
- What?
I like your twisted humor!
I like your mystic rumors!
I'd say we can assume we're gonna get along!
You're not
like average Joes,
or Jims or Tims or Johns.
...And I'd wager
that you'd never run from danger
with those muscles made of bronze!
I can safely shout
without a doubt
that it won't take very long...
... Before we're getting--
--and not regretting--
ever setting on gettin' along!
Right this way, Umbridge.
Oh my! What a fancy place.
Oh, look at these strapping  young gentlemen. What will it be, Dumbledor?
Oh, just a welcome to Hogwarts special.
Ah, two body-shots. Coming right up!
Dumbledore, this is so crazy.
Uh, I’m full of crazy ideas. Hey, by the way, Umbridge.
Have you ever tried Gillyweed?
We can have some of this and take a dip in our hidden swimming pool.
Hidden swimming pool? Where is that?
On cloud nine, baby! On cloud nine!
You are a beautiful sample!
For example,
my gosh-- you're so strong!
- What's the matter with me?
- Now you're just flattering me!
...Oh, how we're both just gettin' along!
I've never felt this way before...
- Felt how?
- Um, intimidated.
You have such prominence and poise.
Oh, that ol' thing--
Baby, it's just me, Dumbledore.
So just try to relax,
face the facts:
You feel just like one of the boys!
- One of the boys? I do?
- Oh, you sure do baby!
Dumbledore!
Yes sir,
you're the one professor
that'd II'd want detention from!
Umbridge-
you're the handsome wizard
that'd I'd want an extension from!
-And I'd give it to you!
I'll get the door!
Oh, you'll get much more!
Either way we can't go wrong...
With how shamelessly
and how famously
we're both just getting' along...
Dumbleore? Before we go any further-
- there’s a confession I’d like to make.
- Oh yeah?
I’ve never been with a man before.
Well, your first time with a man can be very scary.
Mine certainly was!
But Grindelwald just took my hand and said: relax, dumby!
Be cool and – go with the flow, you know?
Dumbledore! You know just what to say to make me feel – magical.
Most guys don’t understand me at all.
Oh, well ah: I think we understand each other perfectly...
MISTER UMBRIDGE!
Oh we're get, get, getin.
We'll be get, get, gettin',
get, get, gettin',
gettin' along!