So, you guys ever hear the one about Sirius Black and Flitwicks little brother?
So Flitwicks little brother is walking down the
streets of London and Sirius Black is in this storm drain...
...dressed as a clown...
.. and he's like: Yay! Hey Flitwicks little brother!
Down here in this storm drain! It's me! A clown!
And Flitwicks little brother is like, Yeah chap? What d'you want?
And Sirius Black is like: Oh, Flitwicks little brother, you gotta
get down in this storm drain with me 'cuz you're missing out.
We've got a carnival down here! We've got loads of
cotten candy and balloons and the kid practically flips.
He goes: I gotta get down there!
That sounds like a right treat that does!
So: He reaches down his arm right?
But Sirius Black he grows his mad teeth
AND HE BITES THE KIDS HEAD OFF!
And two days later -- that kid died!
Man! That is the biggest piece of bullshit I ever heard.
I Think that’s pretty scary, but have ya‘ll
ever heared of the shrieking shack?
The shrieking shack?!?
My brother Fred says it’s...
...[gulp] haunted.
That’s right, it’s the most haunted place in all
of Great Britain. And it’s right over ya’ll there!
No man! I hear they got monsters up in there.
Yeah? Oliver Wood lost the quaffel in there once.
He went in to get it -- AND HE NEVER CAME OUT!
Why don’t you go check it out?
Are you nuts??? No!
Come on ya’ll all Gryffindors, where’s
your sense of Halloween adventure?
I got a right mind to stay out of that place on Halloween.
Okay, how’s about this: I will give a big fat kiss whoever
is brave enough to go up there an ring the doorbell.
I’ll do it!
Hermin?
I’m not afraid of the shrieking shack!
Everything  I’ve ever read tells me those urban legends are just old wifes tales!
Yeah, but see, here’s the thing I’m not kissing you, Hermin.
I don’t want a kiss from you, Cho.
- I want something better!
- Better then a kiss from Cho Chang?
I want you to carry my books for the rest of the semester!
Okay. Well, if we are raising the stakes
now ringing the bell just won’t do.
-You have to go in there and draw us a picture of the monster!
- What?
But you know that I can’t draw!
Without a pad of paper!
Just so happens I have a sketchpad right here!
- Well, this is useless without a pencil.
- Well, you’re lucky I came so prepared.
Oh, do I get a flashlight or something...?
-Lumos!
- No, hey, I know, she could shine
it up to the back of the paper and trace it!
No tracing, Hermin, I’ll be able to tail!
All right! Well, here I go...
Oh, Hermin! Hermin... Herm... inino...!
Wait, wait. Ahm...
You don’t have to do this. What’s it gonna proof?
That maybe somebody in this school cares if I live or die!
[singing] I wouldn’t count on it...
[something is howling]
Bloody shit! -- What is it?
Let’s get outa here!
Hey, wait! Hey -- what’s going on? What’s going on?
Wow! Hermin went into the shrieking shack
and the monster that lives in there is pissed!
Well... hey, Ron. Ron! We gotta go save her!
- But...
...bu... Harry, she’s... she’s not even our friend!
Ron! Come on, man.
Uh, Hermany?
Hermon...Hermona...Her....Hermoingle boingle....
Hermanda am banana.....Hermono....Hermononucliosis?
[All three are screaming]
- It’s just Hermin
- Hermin, you’re the monster?
[howl and screams]
Quick! We gotta get out of here, there's another
monster in here and it's probably not as friendly.
Oh good, let's go. Hey, what's this?
- What’s up?
- It’s Lupin's brooch!
But why is it in the shrieking shack?
Yeah, especially since he told me to stay out of here.
- Grrr!!!
- Ahh!
Harry... it’s a... it’s a ... A Vampire!
- Harry what d’we do?
- I have my wand in my bag!
Just get it out [???] something.
Oh! Hey! Hey! You like this? You want this?
Then go get it!
No! No, Crookshanks!
Quick! Let’s go while he’s distracted!