Let’s go hiding in the wood.
Woah, woah, woah, woah! That’s the forbidden forest.
All sorts of creepy creatures live in there.
Look: it’s either here or shrieking shack. So let’s go!
I can’t believe it. We’re going from the scariest
place in the world to the scariest place in the world.
Ah. Let’s take cover behind this fallen tree here.
Are you alright, Hermin?
Yeah. I’m alright.
Are you alright, Ron?
I will be. -- After a Red Vine.
Listen – Hermio.
- What?
- Why did you go in the shrieking shack if you...
...if you knew there’s a monster in there?
Aren’t you the one that’s always telling us not to –
go out and do dangerous stuff and have any kind of…
- Fun?
- Yeah!
Oh, yes.
You know, I just thought that if for once I did something
crazy then maybe you guys would like me.
Yeah? Well, you thought wrong.
Okay. No, no. Listen! Hermione...
You - you said my name right!
- Just now? Did I, Hermin-monster…
- Yeah.
That is close enough.
Listen: you don’t need to pretend to be
something you’re not just to get people to like you.
-  I mean just look at me.
- Yeah, but you’re Harry Potter!
Yeah… yes. But maybe in the wizarding world that’s true.
But in the muggle world… I’m just a
I’m something called a douchebag.
A what?
A douchebag, Hermin.
I play guitar when everybody is supposed to hang out.
And – I make weird covers of Disney songs, who does that?
See? Muggles hate that shit. To them I’m just...
I’m just a douche bag. I’m like – I don’t know. I’m like...
Justin McCarthy.
I’m like Justin McCarthy.
I’m Justin McCarthy’s douche!
I’ve got a confession to make too.
Back home – around my brothers.
I’m kind of a douchebag too.
Like Shia LaBeouf.
The prince douche.
But, hey. That’s okay. Because at Hogwarts
it’s cool to be who you are. It’s cool to be unique.
That’s alright. So hey: maybe you’re not very pretty...
...like Cho Chang. Maybe not as fun as Ron.
Or cool, like Snape.
You know what? You are smart.
Like Hermione.
And I for one would love to have a friend
who could do my ancient runes essays.
- You mean it?
- Yep, cause it’s due tomorrow.
Harry! Ron! Uh, come here!
- Oh my good you’re so soft.
- Thanks.
So you guys really like me!
Ah, well just some things in life you can’t go through
together without becoming friends afterwards namely
one of them being taking on a 12 foot vampire.
- Argh!
-Ahhhhh!
Oh, We're dead as shit, we're dead!
I regret nothing!
I'm in love with you both!
[neighing]
None shall harm Harry Potter [???].
Back! Back, you cowardly thing!
Run you creature of the night and know that
these woods belong to the centaurs and their kin!
Do not worry, Harry Potter and co. The beast is gone!
Who are you?
Rise! Call me Firenze. It in the Centaur tongue means: friend.
Thank you. -- How did you...
Know to save you?
The leader of my tribe is a wise and powerful being.
He has seen the future and has charged
the centaurs with your protection, Harry.
For you are destined for great things.
I’ve heard that the centaurs were close to extinct.
But I never thought I’d get to see one in real live.
It is true.
We centaurs are a dying breed.
Due to a magical plague many moons ago,
all females of our kind have perished.
We have long searched for a human mate.
But none have ever survived.
Survived what? Www what survived?
Survived coitus, Harry.
What’s coitus?
[whisper -- explaining]
Oh, they died because of your giant horse gongs!
Ah, that’s... that’s funny.
Yes, it sounds like a funny problem.
But it’s actually not.
Oh. I’m... I’m so sorry.
It’s alright.
Listen: -- we’ve got to get you kids back to Hogwarts castle.
Harry, unless the stars are mistaken you’ve got
a Quidditch game that you must be well rested for.
Oh, wow. Thanks Firenze, you’re so cool!
I sure am!
Well, get on my back!
To Hogwarts!