Good morning wizarding world. Rita Skeeter here reporting to
you live from the Hogwarts school of witchcraft and wizardry.
It’s dawn out here on the Quidditchfield as we prepare to bear witness
to the epic battle between PeeWee Gryffindor and Slytherin teams.
Today dear readers it will decided which team deserves to be remembered
as champions and who will forever be disgraced as eternal weenies.
Why what do we have here?
You there! Nerd!
What can you tell us about this gruesome sight, young man?
Well that’s our coach, professor Lupin. It appears he
has killed a beautiful doe in some kind of -- blood lust.
Huh? Woah! Oh god help me! What the...
...what I kill?
Good morning mister Lupin. My name is Rita Skeeter,
I’m a reporter for the daily prophet.
Oh, hi!
Care to explain what’s going on here?
Well, I think everybody is just getting excited for a nice game of Quidditch.
I know my team is ready to go.
No, I’m referring to the slaughtered doe and the fact
that your entire person is soaked in blood.
Ah, well...
Well ah...
It’s tradition!
Yes it’s... it’s tradition that every game before -- before the match,
the -- the Gryffindor PeeWee Quidditch team kill a defenseless doe.
And devour it! Ah...
...in – in doing so, we are able to observe the power and ferocity...
...of a doe.
That’s pretty – that’s pretty cool, ha, Shlongbottom?
- That’s Bambi’s mum!
- Okay.
Ha ha. Just eat the doe, Shlongbottom!
I couldn’t!
Eat it! Nom nom nom! Nom nom!
It’s good!
Mmm Mister Lupin. Mister Lupin.
It’s widely rumored that you are engaged
in a heated quarrel with a one Severus Snape.
What do you make of the allegations made
by professor Snape that you are – and I quote:
...unfit to teach children, are a danger to yourself and others,
have never graduated Hogwarts and are a washed up -- looser?
- That’s bullshit!
- Huh!
- I mean: those are half-trues. Yeah.
Listen. You can... you can tell Snape that he is a Jerk.
And you can quote me on that.
My dear readers. I am starstruck. Entering the scene is
none other than Harry freakin’ Potter the Gryffindor seeker.
- How is it hanging, daily prophet?
- Harry, kid. Good luck on the game, huh.
Now it’s time for spectators to take their seats. For what’s
shaping up to be a truly remarkable game of Quidditch.
Rita Skeeter signing off.
Severus! What’s the goofiest thing you’ve ever done?
Because I bet I just topped it!
I doubt it. My actions led directly to
the death of the only thing I’ve ever loved.
This is probably twice as funny as that. Severus,...
I was just at Hogsmeade treating professor Umbridge the
traditional welcome to Hogwarts body shot, you know?
- Of course.
- And the two of us really hit it off. There was this
little song, little dance – to make a long story short:
- ...we ended up going home together.
- Oh, headmaster!
Severus, let me finish!
So Umbridge slipps out of that hideous outfit and
would you believe it? Professor Umbridge -  get this...
- ... is a woman!
- No!
- Oh yeah!
- What did you do?
Uh, the first thing that came out of my mouth was:
Ahhhhh! [high pitched]
And then I did the only thing that would make
the whole situation less awkward for everybody.
- And what’s that?
-  I disapperated.
- Oh yeah.
- You didn't!
- I did!
Oh, headmaster! I told you you have to deal with these things.
It’s like that one time I made out with professor Grubbly Plank.
She got -- clingy.
You have to confront them. Tell them they
don’t have what you’re looking for.
Severus, these things just tend to blow over. It was like
that time when everybody was complaining: hey, Dumby.
You have to expell Tom Riddle from Hogwarts, ‘cause he’s evil.
And I just told them to stuff it. Eventually everything just worked itself out.
Just like that, you know?
[mobile is ringing]
[???]
Oh god, damn it!
- What?
- It’s a text from Umbridge! It says:
We need to talk. Colon, right parenthesis. Oh!!!
[Snape is laughing]
Oh I do not envy you!
[mobile is ringing]
Oh, sorry. That’s me.
- What the devil?
- What?
It’s a BBM from Umbridge: "Are you with Dumbledore? Did he get my text?"
Now you’ve dragged me into this?
Just ignore it! Maybe - maybe she’ll just go away.
- Did you get my text?
- Oh, yeah!
Yeah, ye - yeah.
You didn’t text me back!
And you left so quickly last night that I didn’t get a chance to say...
Well, about that, ha ha.
The last night was the most amazing night of my life.
Oh yeah?
I love you!
Ahhhh! [high pitched]
Yeah, me too!
Oh god, I can’t watch this! Listen, Umbridge.
The headmaster is terrible with confrontation. What he is
trying to say is that -- well he’s just not that in to you.
What?!?
You don’t know a god damn thing about our magical
night together, you f***ing little snape in the grass.
He loves me! He’s the only man who loves me.
We can be happy. And you’re gonna die!
Umbridge, Umbridge, Umbridge, stop! He’s right! He’s - he's right!
What?!?
I don’t wanna be with you.
I was only hitting on you because I thought you
were a sexy man. Maybe if you were a man, I --
No!
No.
I’m proud to be a woman.
I’m a strong -- woman.
Hear me smash...
Umbridge, I’m sorry! I just made a big goofy.
I’m sorry if I got your hopes up and I’m sorry if I ran
around telling everybody about our sexual exploits.
I only did it because I thought it would make them laugh.
I mean, they did laugh, a lot!
I mean, come on, it’s funny! Ha ha...
No! No what are these?
Tears? No. Umbridge, you don’t cry!
Umbridge don’t cry!
You don’t cry!
Yes, you do cry!
You do cry, you chubby little [beep].
That’s what I am, just a chubby little [beep].
Oh god, are you crying? Is she crying?
She’s laughing. I mean it is pretty funny. Ha ha ha.
[Snape and Dumbledore are laughing]
Whaaa!
I will destroy you!
I will grind your bones to make my bread.
I will erase everything that you ever were.
And I will have your job!
Mark my words, Dumbledore!
I’ll have your job! Whaa!
Ah, Severus. Ah, who do you think is going to win the big game, ha?
- Gryffindor, sadly.
- Oh, good.
Draco is such a little shit!
Tell me about it!
- Hey, Lucius!
- Hey.
Why Lucius Malfoy.
It’s been a long time, Severus.
Woah. [both]
I didn’t expect to see you here. I received a letter saying
you’d be too busy to attend any games this year.
Yes, I am, - in a way.
But you know how I love Quidditch. I never miss a game!
Especially one whose outcome means a great deal to me.
Oh yes? And what’s so important about this particular Quidditch game?
Let’s just say:
I’ve made a large wager that weights heavily on the outcome of this game.
Which is why I hope you won’t object. I’ve made
some last minute replacements to your team.
- Replacements?
- Yes. Let me introduce you – Yaxley!
Hey, coach!
Here they are. All new transfers to Hogwarts
and all exceptional Quidditch players.
Hi!
Yes. Now why don’t you run along and tell
your team they’ll be sitting this game out?
As you wish, Lucius.
Now, boys. Remember:
Do whatever you can to knock Potter off his broom!
Make sure the fall is fatal!
- And don’t forget that when we get on that field...
- [gasp] It’s my Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy, you came to love me! Woo!
Point your toes! [???] chin up!
Dad... daddy! Look! I drew you a picture!
It’s me on the potty!
Th..That’s you in the background
and you’re saying: that’s my son.
And then the potty, it says: Thank you Draco.
Even Potties need to eat!
I like that shading on your hair.
Best I’ve ever seen.
- Who asked you?
- You didn't trace this for nothing?
No.
Wow! Take a look at this, fellows.
Look at this right here with the paper.
- Is this a cross hatching I detect?
- Yes!
Silence!
Get out of here you cretins!
And don’t forget to kill Harry Potter.
- Can I hang on to this?
-Keep it!
And you!
You listen to me, you little poof.
You better not screw this up! Huh!
I won’t! I won’t, daddy. I won’t!
You’ll see you’ll love me after this.
I’ll catch that snitch. Mark my words!
[singing] When I’m on the – hey!