Let the games begin!
Somebody's goin' down,
It ain't gonna be us!
Somebody's gonna lose,
Somebody's goin' down,
We're gonna kick your ass!
It ain't gonna be us!
You're goin' down, goin' down!
Somebody's gonna lose,
We're gonna kick your ass!
it ain't gonna be us!
You're goin' down, goin' down!
[whistle]
Come on, Gryffindor!
[score -- whistle]
[whistle]
End of half one.
Moo moo moo.
Package for Harry Potter. Mooo...
You there, bird. What have you got there?
Urgent package served for HP. Receive it?
Oh, I can sign for it. I'm a family friend.
Oh, thanks buddy. You're really helping me out.
I'll make sure he gets it.
- Ho hoot!
- NOOOT!!!
Let's see. What have we got here?
Oh! A ho ho.
I hate to ruin christmas, Potter. But this
is one package you won't be getting.
Hey, that belongs to Harry Potter!
So what if it does?
What make you think i'd give it to you?
Oh, I know you! You're that filthy little...
- Jelly-legs-jinx!
- Woah!!!
What the hell was that?!?
You guys are making me look like an idiot out there!
Yeah man, it's those Slytherin dudes.
They are just too fast!
I give up!
No. NO! You are not allowed to give up!
I give up too.
- I give up three.
- Harry, no!
I'm sorry, man! If I could catch up with those
assholes like for maybe two seconds...
...maybe I could catch the snitch but it's like
Dean said, they are just -- too fast.
Well I will go tell madam Hooch that we quit.
- Dean!
- Sorry, coach.
Dean, please. Give us another chance!
Guys, wait. Dean -- wait!
Look, this package just came for Harry. And
trust me you goona wanna look what's inside.
Gather around, chums!
- Oh, Harry!
- Bloody tits!
-I ain't seeing this!
What is it?
Harry, this is a FIREBOLT!
The gretest present in all of kiddos.
That's the fastest broom in the world that is!
They say that when it takes off even
wizard god himself can't follow.
Ah, guys --
I think we're still in this game.
What do you say, Dean?
- Alright!
- Yay!
Here we go, we've got Dean!
Please, Hermione. This is for us!
Alright, team cheer on three. Ready?
One, two, three. Go Gryffindor!
Good luck, Harry. And ahm, good luck to you too, Ron.
I think you're a really great keeper.
Okay, bye.
Bye. Ow! Bye.
Alright, boys. Let's get up!
Ahhh!
What? What?!? No way!
-Ah!
- Ou!
-Ouuu!
Oh, the snitch!
Kiiiilll Hiiimmm! Kiiiilll Hiiimmmmm...
Avada --- uahmmm!!!
Nooooo!!!!
Ahh, get out of here!
Take this!
Uh, oh!
I'm bleeding!
Haaryy!!!
Caatch thaaat snitchhh!
Harry Potter has caught the snitch. Gryffindor wins!
[Yay -- cheers]
Gryffindor, Gryffindor, Gryffindor, ...
[Lupin is doing the butt-trumpet]
Who looks stupid now? You do!
Remember this day, professor Lupin. -- Slytherins, retreat!
Harry, you did it!
Three cheers for HP, y'all!
Cheers, cheers, cheers!
Ah, Harry!
Harry. Your dad would be so proud of you.
But more importantly: his best friend is proud of you!
You mean Sirius Black?
Ha. Ha ha! Just beeing out here with all you kid
makes me -- makes me feel like a kid agin.
Oh, do you want a Berty-Botts-every-flavour-candy-bean?
Yeah! Sure! Aww -- that really takes me back!
Well, if it isn't the man of the hour, mister Remus Lupin.
- Yap.
- Mister Lupin, ...
...how does it feel to have coached the
Gryffindor team to their first win in fourteen years?
Well, ah -- let me just say -- that it hasn't been easy.
I've had a lot of hard times.
Some people -- have even tried to make me look like a fool.
But it's moments like these --
moments like these right here that I just [uah]!
What?!?
Uah! What is this?
[he's about to throw up]
It's getting worse! Why is it taste this way?
I just ate shit!!!
I just ate shit!
Wha ha ha! Come on! Party in the Gryffindor tower!
Yay!
Gryffindor, Gryffindor, Gryffindor, ...
No, no, no!!!
Who knew the counter course was just unjellyfy?
Well, daddy. Looks like we lost.
However, I do think I would have caught the snitch
if Yaxley hadn't blundered into my path.
And I think the most important thing
here is: I've had a lot of fun!
How daaare (you)?!?
You couldn't stay out of the way for
twenty minutes, could you, you little poof?
Why, I ought to...
[Draco whispers: that's my...]
Ha!
You're not my son!
This place is really gone to the dogs!