Hello boys!
Hey Hemione.
Erm, well, I'm heading home for a winter holliday for a few weeks,
but ahm, before I go I -- I'd just wanted to give this to you guys.
- Oh!
-Happy christmas!
- I wonder what it is.
- I wonder, what this could be...
- I hope it's a puppy!
- Puppy!
Puppy! Puppy! Puppy!
- A book?!?
- Yeah!
Gross! Merry christmas, Ron!
Yeah!
Wait, no! No, wait! It's not just any book!
It's a scrapbook! I made it of all of our
memories of our first semester in Hogwarts!
Oh... oh yeah...
See, here's... ah... here's tickets from the hogwarts express,
and ah... here is a clipping from the prophet about that
Quidditchgame that you guys won last month.
A yeah... Remus Lupin eats shit. Gryffindor wins.
- Hey!
- Merry christmas, Ron!
Merry christmas to you...
Oh wow...
Hey! Hermione, why is here a... a clipping
in here from the prophet about Sirius Black?
Because they mentioned Harry in it.
Oh!...ah...Oh!
Before his escape from Azkaban Sirius Black went on
the record saying: I'm wanna find Harry Potter - that's you -
...and I wanna drug and kill him!
Are you nervous, Harry? He IS a murderer.
Not really. I mean, I live at Hogwarts!
And it's an impenetrable fortress.
I really don't think any of us have to worry any old thing about...
Sirius Blaaaaaack!
Sirius Blaaaaaaaaaaack!...
Oh! Check mate! Sirius Blahahahahack!
What about him?
He was spotted by the paintings on the third floor!
The dogs playing poker peed on the carpet!
The screaming man has never looked more terrified!
It took the entire last supper to calm him down.
Sirius Black -- has broken into our castle!
[screaming]
Quiet! Quiet! Quieeeet!
When you yell it only makes Sirius wanna kill you faster!
Now prefects, escort these kiddies
to their dorm to tuck them in!
The teachers and I will search
the entire castle for Sirius Black.
Siruis Black! Sirius Black! That bastard!
I'm gonna find him and I'm gonna throw everything --
everything I know at him! I'm talking about:
...lumos, alohomora, jellylegs jinx, everything...
Harry, you're better then that!
- I'll jellylegs jinx him!
- [scream]
Harry, that almost hit me!
I'm in a rage!
This is the maddest I've ever been!
'Cuz Sirius Black took everything away from me,
he took my parents, my whole life, everything!
I'm gonna find him!
With this. -- The Maraunders Map!
Let's go!
Okay. I think Sirius is in here, but it could be wrong.
This is very complicantiomatic.
[??? complicated schematic ???]
I don't know about this, Harry. This room is really forbidden.
Harry... I'm full frightened.
Wait! D'you hear that?
Hear what?
I know you.
I've seen you in a dream,
an old familiar scene, from somewhere...
And you know me.
There's glowing in your eyes,
I know and recognize, from somewhere...
Those voices,
singing out,
"La, la, la, la, la..."
[Lily & James] La, la, la, la, la...
[Harry, Lily, James] La, la, la, la, la... la.
Who are these people?
Can't you see them?
No.
All I see is myself and I'm inside
Willy Wonka's chocolate factory.
Hermione is turning into a blueberry and I'm eating her.
I see myself turning into Cho Chang ya'll...
What is this thing?
That is the mirror of erised, Harry.
It shows you nothing more or less, then the
deepest most desperate desire of your heart.
Those are your parents, Harry.
Harry! Harry, watch out, that's Sirius Black!
Take this, you bastard! Alohomora!
- Kids...
- Jellylegs jinx!
- Unjellify!
- Oh! ...
Harry, he's too much for us!
I 've got one more thing. Lumos!
Expelliarmus.
Harry, just let me explain...
What do you wanna explain?
- How you betrayed my parents and killed them?
- No!
I didn't betray your parents and I've never killed anybody!
I was framed!
I loved your parents, Harry!
Your dad was my best friend!
Why should I believe you?
Because, Harry, ...
...when I look in that mirror I see them too.
I see them.
They were people that I loved,
you were barely old enough
to be there.
But I know you.
You have your mothers eyes,
beneath your dad's untidy dark hair.
Those voices,
ringing out,
"La, la, la, la, la..."
[Lily & James] La, la, la, la, la...
[Sirius, Lily, James] La, la, la, la, la...
But I would never do
anything that could hurt you!
They were both my family!
You're all that's left of what I knew,
you must know somewhere it's true!
Do you understand me?
Yeah, I do.
those voies
reaching out,
"La, la, la, la, la..."
[Lilly, James] La, la, la, la, la...
[Harry, Sirius, Lily, James] La, la, la, la, la...
[Harry, Sirius, Lily, James] La.