Harry, it seems so unfair that I got to spend so
much time with James and Lilly and you so little.
I don't know, Harry. -- Can we really trust Sirius Black?
Yeah, what about that daily prophet article,
where YOU went on the record saying...
- ...you want to find Harry and you want to drug and kill him!
- That's a lie!
I was magically misquoted by that dumbass Rita Skeeter.
What I  actually said was: ...
...I want to hug and kiss him!
I believe him, guys. He saw my
parents in the mirror and, well, ...
- ...you can't fake that.
- No, you can't.
Okay.
- What are you doing here, Sirius?
- Yeah, I mean if you don't want to kill Harry,
then what's the point of coming to Hogwarts at all?
Well, I was rotting away in my
prison cell in Azkaban, I ah...
...received a package. And attached to it was this note.
It reads:
Dear Sirius Black, inclused is a tool that you can
use to escape Azkaban and sneak into Hogwarts.
Please hurry! Harry Potter is in grave danger!
Signed: Little d.
Little d?
-Little Dumbledore!
- My thoughts exactly!
It was nice to know that the old man still believed in me.
Anyway, I opened the package and inside I found this.
It's your fathers old invisibility cloak.
Ha ha ha, we used to use it to play jokes on Snape!
And we went solve mysteries and shit, but...
...here. Your dad wanted you to have
this -- when you're old enough.
Wow! Thanks. Hey Ron, am I invisible?
Who said that?
But Sirius, I don't think I'm in any kind of grave danger.
Oh, Harry! Jesus!
Looked like you were in danger
during that quidditch match.
It's good thing my package made it to you on time.
You really put it to good use.
You sent that firebolt!
- I sure did.
- Harry! Harry, on the map!
Someone's coming!
Quick! Get under the cloak! If you guys are seen
helping me you'll all be in really big trouble!
No, no, no, no, no! But if they find you
they're gonna send you back to Azkaban!
It's fine. It was all worth it as long as you know the truth.
Now quick! Get under the cloak!
- No. no!
- Alohomora!
What the devil is going on heeeere?
Nothing?
Lies! You can't do nothing!
You must be here for something.
Or for someONE!
Do you know what the penalty is for aiding a fugitive?
I'll see you all expelled!
- But we weren't doing anything!
- Shut up, Potter!
Your arrogance is insufferable
just like your dead-beat father.
And like him it's going to get you killed!
Now, until I find Black, I'm going
to make your life miserable.
You'll wish you WERE expelled!
Leave them alone!
You -- butt trumpet!
[Sirius is doing the butt-trumpet]
But, but this isn't anything like it!
[More butt-trumpet]
Expelliarmus!
Ha ha ha. Sirius Black!
I was hoping I'd be the one to find you!
Yeah, well, you did.
- So leave the kids out of this.
- He's innocent!
I'll be the judge of that, Potter!
Through all these years, ...
...you're still a no-good weinerjacket!
You just can't stand that she picked James -- over yer!
Give me a reason! Give me a reason, I swear I'll do it!
- I wish Dumbledore were here!
- I am here, Night Troll!
And so am I!!!
Sirius Black!
Oh, I've been looking for you a long time!
He broke into the castle using this!
What the hell is Potter doing here?
Nothing important. I believe Black
has confounded the children.
Ha! I think maybe you're the one
that's been confounded, Snape!
Look at the name on the tag! Potter!
I knew you were guilty from the moment
I layed my eyes on you three little turds!
And now you and your loser friends
are gonna come with me to Azkaban!
Stop! Stop! It's impossible!
Harry didn't help Sirius break in, because...
...because I did.
Headmaster, how could you let
this criminal into the castle?
Especially in THAT outfit...
Scarfy, my reasons are my own.
Oh, this is just -- too -- good.
I told you I was gonna destroy you, Dumbledore.
And now you're dead!
- Unless...
- Unless what?
I make you a deal, Dumbledore.
You can either kiss the dementors...
...or you can kiss -- Umbridge!
[No-cryings from nearly everybody]
I'm not worth it!
I choose...
I choose neither!
Snape it's time to show where your true loyalty lies!
Take care of the children for me!
Well, -- looks like we're out -- again!
Disaparate!
Ah, magic!
What!?! Where d'he go???
He disaparated!
That's bullshit, Snape! You can't disaparate
inside of Hogwarts, right?
- Right.
- Right!
Damn it!
You got lucky, Potter! But I know you're guilty too!
And I'm gonna get all of you!
Because with Dumbledore gone -- guess
who gets to be the headmaster now...
- Me?
- Snape?
No! Me! Your mama! Umbridge!
And from now on we're gonna be
doing things around here MY WAY!
We're gonna be doing things
THE UMBRIDGE WAY!
[-- End of Act 1 --]