Educational decree No. 28.
By order of the ministry of magic -- Dolores Jane Umbridge
shall replace Albus Dumbledore...
...as headmaster of Hogwarts school of witchcraft and wizardry.
Teachers are hereby forbidden from giving out any information
not strictly related to the subject they are payed to teach.
All student teams, societies, clubs
and activities are henceforth disbanded.
This is bullshit!
Bloody bitch! Dean, get a load
of his mornings daily prophet.
Albus Dumbledore named public enemy No. 1 after it was
discovered he had been aiding dangerous fugative Sirius Black.
Dolores Jane Umbridge has now been
appointed headmaster of Hogwarts...
...to bring order to the school
and repair the curriculum.
Repair the curriculum. Is that what
she calls ruining our bloody school?
Are ya'll talking about the horrible things that are going
on here since Umbridge was named headmaster?
I...i... it's awful! It's just awful!
Damn straight!
Yeah. She's cancelled quidditch, got rid of
the trips to hogsmeade, [???] the feast, ...
...painted over the paintings and now she's got the ghostbusters
breathing down Nearly Headless Nicks Nearly Headless neck!
Not to mention she has cancelled the annual valentines day
feeler-up dance and replaced it with a nasty old abstinence ralley!
How am I supposed to stay abstinent
when I've got a reputation to maintain?
Professor Flitwick is gonna fail me now!
I just wanna die!
Yeah. And every takes their frustrations out on me!
Aaaaaaaaah!
Calm down, friend!
No one gives Goyle detention!
ME HATE UMBRIDGE!!!
You guys hate Umbridge too?
I thought you guys would've gotten along seeing
that she's a bitch and you guys are dicks.
That's what we were hoping for, but no such luck.
Well, do you know, what I think? I think I
need some camomile before my slumber.
That was too close for comfort.
Oh, who made Cho cry? What is that?
I don't even care who did it.
You're gonna die, Shlongbottom!
Yeeeeeaaaaaah!
STOP! Look guys, I know things are getting bad
around here, but we can't turn on each other!
That's exactly what Umbridge wants!
She wants us to eat each other to survive!
Dean, let me see that prophet!
Sure thing, HP.
Oh! This is so bogus! Look at this: ...
...Dangerous criminal Sirius Black apprehending is
momentarily held at Hogwarts where he waits the sentence and...
...heroic witch, Dolores Umbridge
recommends the maximum sentence.
Dementors Kiss!
That's rough, buddy! What are we gonna do?
There's nothing we can do. The only other person that
knows he's innocent is Dumbledore. And he's on the run too!
We're in a real puzzle. Red Vine?
For the first time in my life...
I don't want one.
Harry, you...
You can't mean that, ahm...
...you just open up and I'll put it in...
I DON'T WANT A RED VINE, OKAY?!
I don't want one!
I'll take it, Ron.
We best leave Harry alone.
Alright, gang. I'll ignore that some of you were late, ...
...if you ignore, that I'm the latest.
What the hell?
Why don't you guys laugh at my joke?
What's going on here, why all those long faces?
Man, it's Umbridge!
She is ruining our lifes!
And Hogwarts!
It's not a school. It's a blooming prison!
Like Azkaban!
Yeah, and she's the Dementor sucking out my soul!
I see.
Well. I tell you what, ...
...If you guys think that this place is like
Azkaban and you're worried about dementors, ...
...why don't I teach you a spell that can ward them off?
It's called a Patronus.
Uh... but... professor, the Patronus is a very
advanced spell! And we're just first years!
Ah, bullshit! I mean baloney.
[Uh!]
It's easy, okay? The only thing you
need to make a Patronus...
...is a wonderful thought!
Any happy little thought?
[Reference to Walt Disney's Peter Pan]
Not just ANY happy thought.
Alright? Dementors live of fear and misery.
So in order to beat them you gotta have something
that's stronger, then they are! The happy thought...
...has gotta be something, that when you
think about it you can't help but cheer up!
So come on, guys! What makes you happiest? Cho?
Ah... Well... well...
Hey. It can be a memory, a person, a fantasy, anything!
Just as long, as the emotion is real.
I pretend that I'm out at the valentines day feeler-up
dance and all the boys can't keep their hands off me!
Good! Hey...
Who... who knows, maybe that's a...
...maybe that's a thought we can make happen.
I'm kidding!
Or am I?
You decide.
And let me know...
Neville! What have you got?
I think I'll be an indian brave!
Sounds good! Hey, Ron!
What are you thinking about? Maybe a...
...snack or a frumpy little girl?
No. NO!
I... Um... I'm thinking about Harry!
Oh cool! I was thinking of me too!
Good work, guys, good work. Alright.
Now that you've got your happy
thoughts you got to hold on to it, okay?
And then say the magic words: expecto patronum.
Alright? Now watch me.
Uh, Professor, what will you think of?
I'm gonna think of the man, ...
...who considered me to be his best friend.
Hagrid. That's a good one.
No! It's not Hagrid.
[mumbles to himself]
EXPECTO PA...
Hold on!
What the spell is going on here?
Remus Lupin.
Sounds like you're about to teach this bunch childrens...
...a patronus. Snaaape!!!
Oh.
Yes?
Tell me, Snape: Is the Patronus even on
the curriculum for chubby little first years?
Why no!
Oh! Is that so?
What do you want, Umbridge?
Well, I was just walking round the school...
...observing teachers and their classroom environments...
...and I heard some pretty terrible
accusations about you, Remus.
Cho, I said I was joking!
I heard that you don't even use the
proper textbook in your daily lessons.
Oh Umbridge, that textbook's like a thousand years old!
It still refers to Dementors as Ringwraiths!
So... so you're smarter then whoever wrote this book?
- No.
- You're smarter then... Merlin???
No!
I don't approve of your hands
approach in the classroom, Remus!
Again: Cho! I was joking!
And then there's that daily Prophet article that said that...
You eat shit?
That was a candy bean that tasted of shit!
[Uh!]
I mean poopie, guys! Please!
Well Remus, ...
...the point that I'm trying to make is that -- your ass is fired!
What?!?
Dumbledore may have taken pity on you
because you're a worthless little piece of poo, ...
...but there is no room in my school for
a washed up little toilet turd like you!
You've got twenty minutes to get out of my castle.
What? No...
[everyone's complaining]
Who's disrespecting Umbridge!?!
Bye, professor...
Too bad you were joking, professor, 'cause
I could have been your greatest adventure.
I'll get the door for you...
You must be happy now, Snape.
Look at my face, Remus.
Do I look happy to you?
Lupin got fired! Lupin got fired!
Stop! Alright, SNAPE! Listen.
You win, okay?
Just take care of the kids for me and...
I'm sorry that we made fun of you for all those years.
Yes, well so am I.
Well, see you.
Bye!