Now girls, ...
...now that we got rid of that no-good Lupin, ...
...guess who gets to be your new
defense-against-the-dark-arts-teacher...
-Me?
- Snape?
No! Me! Your mama!
[she is laughing]
And I'm gonna teach you real good.
With the help of this.
[sounds of fear]
What is that?
Oh, this? Well, I like to call this
mama's little Love Hand.
I use it to give tough loving to all my childrens.
You childrens are gonna learn your lessons
twice as fast with the help of mama's Love Hand!
Stop! You can't do that! It's abuse!
Why, if you hurt anyone I'll...
I'll...
You what?
I'll tell the wizardcops and you'll be fired!
Show off!
You know what?
You're right.
You're right!
I'm sorry!
You know what I think?
I think that maybe you should be the headmaster.
Is that what you think?
D'you wanna be in charge?
D'you wanna be the mama?
You want my job?
No, I'm just a little girl!
I don't like you, Granger!
I don't like the way that you don't like yourself.
Because, do you know what I see when I look at you?
I see myself at your age.
Oh god...!
Pathetic, ...
...lonely ...
...ugly!
You're calling me ugly, girl???
No!
You're the one that's ugly!
You're the one that's ugly, not me!
Not mehehehehe!
I'm gonna help you, girl.
I'm gonna help you!
I'm gonna suck you right up into my
womb and then I'm gonna spit back out.
As a little red hot titanium baby...
...with diamond teeth.
But before I can recreate you, ...
...I must destroy you.
Now lift up your skirt...
...so your mama can love your bottom until it bleeds!
- Leave her alone!
- Yeah, you old bat!
[crys of protestation]
Stop it! STOP it! Why are you
guys being so mean to me?
Alright, alright, that's enough!
As much as I would love to see some of these bastards beaten...
[pointing at Harry]
...it's against the rules.
Besides, it's time for potions-class!
And I've made a fun-lesson we can all enjoy.
Come one everyone!
Let's go to the dungeon!
[Everyone except for Umbridge]: Yay!
Fine! But this whole class has detention!
Thanks Hermione! Urgh!
Oh, Potter!
You hold up a second.
I wanna have a word with you.
Have you gotten any letters from big D?
I don't even know who that is.
Don't toy with me, boy! It's Dumbledore!
I know you're helping Sirius Black, ...
...and I know you're helping Dumbledore!
So I'm gonna ask you one time:
where is he hiding?
I don't know! Even if I did...
I wouldn't tell you!
Well, you're just a Dumbledore-man true true, aren't you?
Yeah! That's right!
You think the school is bad now?
I haven't even started.
I'm not afraid of you!
You're a teacher, you can't hurt me!
Ha. Do your worst!
Oh, I will!
[Breaks her finger]
See you in hell, Harry Potter!
Lupin!
- Hey Lupin!
- Hey Harry!
Hey! I'm sorry about you're getting fired.
You('ve) still so much to teach us!
Oh... It's alright, Harry. My last lesson...
...was how to get yourself fired.
Jesus! Have you been drinking
these whole past two minutes?
Yep.
It's part of the lesson.
Oh god...!
Damn it!
Ahm... Well, if it's any consolation:
You were always my favorite teacher!
I know!
That's probably why she fired me, you little creep!
Aaah! Harry, ...
...sorry. It's not your fault.
(I'm) probably everybody's favorite teacher.
Alohomora!
Listen Lupin: This place is... the
whole place is just gone to the dogs, I...
...what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Oh! You want me to say something. Ahm...
The important thing is that you always
stick by your friends, no matter what!
Oh, maybe you should go visit YOUR friend,
Sirius Black! Let him explain what's been going on...
NO! NO! Listen!
Sirius Black is NOT a friend!
He's a traitor! Alright?
Well, my time's up.
Hey! Oh no...
Well, ...
...guess you can have this old thing back.
Thanks, Harry. Gonna use it as a blanket or a house.
Now that I'm unemployed and homeless.
You take care of yourself, Lupin. Okay?
Hey Harry, hey! Harry!
Hey, you take care of yourself too, okay?
Alright, hey, Harry.
We've a full moon come up, so stay indoors, alright?
Or I'll eat ya.
I'll eat ya!
See ya!