This is my office now. Team Jacob headquarter's complete.
Tell me sorting hat, are you team Edward or team Jacob?
[Reference to Twilight]
I'm team Dumbledore!
What?
Dumbledore ain't a fictional character.
You know what? You old hat, you old hat, ...
...you know what I'm gonna do with you? I'm gonna stick you
in an old hat box 'cause that's what to do with an old hat.
No! No! No! Tell scarfy: I love him!
Oh, I will...
NOT!
[Laughing]
Pheew! Gosh!
What a day!
Being a mama sure is tough work, isn't it Jacob?
Especial when all your childrens are just so misbehaving...
Why have the gotta be so mean to their mama?
I'm just trying to love them.
And that Harry Potter!
He's just the worst of them all!
Playing that little guitar, ...
...making fun of his mama!
That made me so sad!
So very, very sad hungry!
Oh! A cheesecake!
I wonder where that came from.
Oh, that's right. It's from my induction
ceremony as headmaster of Hogwarts.
But I gotta do that away.
I'm not allowed to eat cheesecake.
Just protein shakes, falcon eggs and rocks...
Well, I guess a little bite wouldn't hurt anybody...
Dolores!
Huh?!?
Who said that?
Dolores Jane Umbridge!
Mama?!?
Dolores, you put down that cheese--cake!
Mama, what are you doing here?
I thought you were dead!
Dolores, I came down...
...from heaven above...
...to help you straighten out these children.
What?!? I...
I don't need your help! This is my house now,
I don't want your help!
I hate you!
Hate me?
You're just like me.
I am nothing like you!
I'm cool!
Oh yeah?
Them little childrens don't seem to think so.
I heard that Harry Potter saying behind your back...
...that you was a chubby little [beep]!
But I am a chubby little [beep]!
Dolores!!!
You listen...
...to your mama now!
Now get up, girl! Get on up!
Now, the only way that you
gonna fight these childrens...
...is with love!
Do you love them enough to scold them?
Yes. I love them so much!
Do you love them enough...
...to [eff] their little bottoms?
Yes, mama, anything!
Do you love them enough...
... to kill them?
Well...
Yeah!
I think I do!
Well, It might strighten that Harry Potter out.
He might even be better off.
Yeah! You're dead and you're just fine!
Why didn't I think it up before?
Because it's crazy.
Yeah...
Ugh!
Oh oh! I'm crazy now, aren't I mama?
I wouldn't be here if you wasn't.
But how do I kill the children?
I don't wanna hurt them.
Oh, there's lots of way...
Yeah...
You mean like with this axe
that I've been sharpening all day?
I don't remember doing that, ...
...but I must have...
...yeah!
I'll kill Harry Potter, ...
...and then my boyfriend Dumbledore
is gonna see how powerfull I am!
And then we'll probably got married!
Atta girl, Dolores.
You make me some grand babies
and we'll straighten them out too.
Okay, mama! I will!
[Mama Umbridge is laughing]
Bye! I hate you!
[she is laughing too]
Bye!
What the devil is going on here?
Oh, hey Snape.