Why have you called me out of bed with this m...
Where did the poster of headmaster Zefron go?
I don't care for Zac Efron. Taylor Lautner is my man.
What do you want, you [???] bitch?
Well, Snape, ...
...it's Potter.
I think he knows where Dumbledore's
hiding and he's not telling me.
And there's this stupid rule that won't
let me discipline the children.
I just wish there was some way
that I could get my boyfriend...
...and kill Harry Potter.
Are you suggesting that we kill a student?
Of course not, Snape! That would be crazy.
We can't have crazy people running this school.
But maybe if someone who also hated
Harry Potter could kill him for me...
Don't look at me!
No! Look at ME!
Lucius Malfoy, what are you doing here?
I couldn't help but overhear your conversation.
And I wanted to know if you were interested in
a role in the evil scheme I've just choreographed.
Well, what's the part?
It's a meeting supporting villain role.
Go on...
You say you want to find Dumbledore and have
unspeakable things happen to Harry Potter.
Well, I can give you those things
for a very small price.
I'm listening...
First you'll let my deatheaters into Hogwarts.
Our presence here must remain an absolute secret!
Next you'll lure Harry Potter
some place where I can have him alone.
He must be alone!
That is of the utmost importance.
I would have done this myself already, if he went anywhere
without that ginger and that filthy mudblood girlfriend of his.
Fine. That takes care of Potter.
But what about Dumbledore?
You say Potter knows where Dumbledore is hiding.
Well, before I finish him of, I'll use
every torture imaginable to loosen his tongue.
Yeah! And then I'll get my boyfriend Dumbledore!
He's probably out buying me presents. He's really sweet!
I'm gonna find and crush that criminal!
Yes... And once you have Dumbledore, Potter is mine!
Fine, it's a deal!
Oh, this is all so illegal!
If anyone were to report this sort of business
to the ministry you'd both go to Azkaban!
Well, that's why no one is gonna report it.
Right, Snape...?
Come now, Severus!
You better then anyone know
what kind of people the Potters are.
Their arrogance knows no bounds!
Something simply must be done about them
or there will always be guys like Potter!
There are so many douchebags in the world.
Yes, so many douchebags get the girls
who deserve more than absolutely anything
that any charm or potion could ever bring.
But men like that, they have her on a string,
and they don't care,
For there will always be guys like Potter.
To realize tears in your eyes because he got her.
She'll never ever know how much you'd have brought her...
If you'd only done
something more for the one,
back when you were young...
Hey! Sour grapes!
Expelliarmus! Impedimenta!
So how did the exam go, ...
...butt trumpet?
Leave him alone!
Lilly Evans!
What has poor Severus ever done to you, Potter?
Well, it's more the fact he exists,
if you know what I mean.
You think you're funny, James, but you're not!
You're just an arrogant, ...
...bullying...
...douchebag!
Ah,  I tell you what, Evans:
I'll leave Snape alone...
...if you go on a date with me!
Argh, you're such an asshole!
And so charming...
Well, I think I have a date then.
- Okay.
- We can hang out with my best friend, Sirius Black.
You're lucky Evans was here, weiner-jacket!
I don't need help from a filthy little mudblood like her!
Fine.
I won't help in the future.
Come on, James!
No, wait! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!!!
So many assholes in this place.
So many assholes in my face!
Why can't they leave me alone--
To love princesses, maids, and queens?
They wouldn't ever be in between...
We'd treat them nice and never be mean.
And we would care...
But there will always be guys like Potter.
Who'll quench the flame like it's a game with drops of water
He'll never ever think her perfect as you/I thought her...
... But now you're alone,
left to pout and moan,
'cause you were totally pwnd.
Alright, let's do it!