Kids! Kids, take a look at today's prophet!
No, no! No more prophets! Enough of that shit!
- Oh no!
- What is it?
- Gather around, y'all...
- No. Harry, you not gonna wanna see this.
Ministry of magic sentences Sirius Black
to Death by way of the Dementor's kiss.
Bogus! Mondo bummer!
That's not the worst of it.
Anyone read the next few sentences?
To administer the kiss, a force of 1000
dementors will be sent to Hogwarts, ...
...where after carrying out the execution,
they will remain a new permanent security force...
...under the direct control of
Headmaster Dolores Umbridge.
This is the absolute worst!
Umbridge done turn the school into a prison!
It's over. She won.
Attention all Hogwarts students:
This is Umbridge.
Will all those nasty little first years
who have dention this evening, ...
...please report immediately to the owlery.
Your duties this evening will include
restocking the bird seeds supply, ...
...getting eggs from the meanest, angriest owls...
...and scrubbing bird shit off the floor.
Bring your toothbrushes.
Failure to attend detention will reserve in
some serious though love consequences.
So get moving everyone!
Everyone except for the famous Harry Potter.
Potter, your detention will be held with me tonight.
So please report to my office immediately!
Alone.
All right, that's all. Bye! Have fun!
[laughing]
Harry, I don't like the sound of this.
Why does she wanna meet you alone?
Yeah, why don't you have to clean up
bird shit like the rest of us?
No, I mean what if she does
something horrible to you?
Oh, she can't, she's a teacher.
Besides, maybe I can talk to her about Sirius.
You can't just sent someone to death who is innocent.
But I don't think she cares if he's innocent or not.
She has to. Any sane, reasonable person would.
Besides I don't know what I'll do if I won't be able to hug
or kiss Sirius Black, my best adult friend, ever again.
I have to try!
I'll see you, guys.
- Good luck!
- Be carefull!
[Snape is singing "Hedwig's theme" drunk]
Oh, Potter! Potter!
Yes. The the one I wanted to see. Sit down, dude!
Listen, I ... I gotta go to Umbridge's office.
Right now? Can't you wait?
- Ah, there's a...
- Harry Potter, I'm a teacher. You have to listen to me!
You.. you have to listen to me or I'll expel you!
I'll expel you now!
Sit down!
Want a beer?
Uh, no. That's okay!
Oh, no! Come on! Man, don't
make me be the only one drinking!
Alright.
Hey, those are mine!
Listen, Potter, ...
[babbeling]
I haaafeadelemon.
[more babbeling]
I have a dilemma.
What's your dilemma?
I promised Dumbledore, that I'll protect the school.
But the thing is, Potter:
I hate you!
I hate you so much!
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I hate you too, Snape.
But it's not fair, really. 'Cause -- it's your dad is who I hated.
And I was in love with your mum.
But I had a butt trumpet.
My butt went -- boop, boop. Boop, boop. Boop, boop.
And she choose him over me.
- You know how that is?
- I don't know what your're talking...
Well, what pisses me off! I mean, really...
...[beep] pisses me off, ...
...is that I was there for her, you know?
Like when she needed someone, I was there.
Waiting like a tool.
Saying: are we gonna snog now? No? Okay. Now?
What about now? Always! Always forever, like a tool.
And just once...
Just one time...
I wanted to take your mum's...
...boobies...
...and put them on my face.
And go... BURRRRRRRRRRrrrrr.
I don't know what you're talking about. I...I don't
wanna say any sayings. I'm just gonna let you pass out here.
Wait, Potter! What I'm trying to say is that I'm torn up.
And if... if you go in there, you gonna be in big trouble!
Whatever, Snape.
Butt trumpet!
Oh, forget you!
Professor Umbridge?
It's me, HP. You asked me to come here.
I wanna talk to you about something.
Hello?
- Hello, boy!
- Oh, hi!
Stupefy!
Argh!