Alright, y'all. That's good. Keep up the good work!
My pleasure, miss Chang.
Cho, could you please help too?
Why, I am. I gave my toothbrush to Dean and
now he's working twice as hard, bless his heart.
No, Cho. We all have to do an equal share of work.
Well, that doesn't seem very fair.
You HAVE turned into a little Umbridge, haven't you?
Gimme that!
- Do you want a Red Vine?
- No, thanks!
What?!?
Does no one want a Red Vine?
Has the world gone insane?
God!
You're not like Umbridge, if that's what's bothering you.
Oh yeah? We're both ugly, we're
both bossy and nobody likes us!
Hey, so what?
So you share some similarities. Hmm?
That ah... That's like saying:
Spiderman and Venom are the same, ...
...because they have the same
powers and the same costumes.
No, no, no, no! No! But Venom...
...let his bitterness and hatred of the world
turn him into an asshole long time ago.
Spiderman...
...would never do that.
You know Bugle's always written
all this crap about him and...
...Iron man was so just so mean to him.
Sandman killed his poor uncle Ben, it's like...
Spiderman is so full of...
...uhm of love, ...
...that he would never let any of that ruin him.
And that -- red-head -- Mary Jane...
...she cares a lot about him.
Even if he is just a nerdy potato-faced looser.
And she knows...
...deep down, ...
...miles beneath those...
...enormous breasts of his, ...
...that he is something special.
Yeah, ...
...he's like my second favorite super hero.
Second?!?
Gwark, gwark! Miow!
Message for Hermione Granger!
Oh, birdie! I'm Hermione Granger.
- Oh, here you go!
- Oh!
Pwwp!
You missed a spot!
Thanks!
What's it say?
It says: "Harry Potter is in grave danger!"
Oh no!
"Meet me by the divination class as
soon as you can." Singned, litttle d.
Little d...uh! Little d?
Little...
Dumbledore!
I knew Umbridge was gonna hurt Harry!
Well, we have to go right now!
Okay.
Here we are. Professor Dumbledore!
Dumbledore! Where is he?
I don't know, the note said he'd be here.
Where are you ''little d''?
In case you were wondering.
The d stands for my wiener.
Malfoy?!?
What are you doing here?
Come to turn us in to Umbridge, huh?
No.
Why would I do that, after I went to
all the trouble to bring you here, ...
...friends?
Wait, little d!
Little Draco!
- No, I don't get it.
- Yeah, we're not friends.
Maybe not...
...yet.
Listen:
the Draco Malfoy you know and love
is currently bedridden.
With heartache in Slytherin dorms.
The Draco Malfoy that stands
before you today you may love...
...but you hardly know.
Get ready!
I'm about to blow your minds.
I'm from...
...the future!
WHAT?!?
Yes! The distant future of 2009.
That's one year from now.
But how, and why?
How and why indeed, Miss Granger.
It turns out something very important
happens next year. I can't tell you what!
But as consequence my father...
- Lucius Malfoy!
- The very same!
It turns out my father has traveled back in time.
With a gang of deatheaters.
And their mission?
To kill Harry Potter!
When I found out of their evil plot, I stowed away
in my fathers fanny pack so I could stop them.
Oh yeah? Why do you want to help Harry all this sudden?
Because -- in the future, ...
...I'm really nice now!
I'm the most popular boy in school
and, even Harry Potter likes me!
Haven't you noticed how I've tried to help you all year?
I mean first I managed to track down Harry's invisibility cloak, and I sent
it to Sirius Black, so he could escape Azkaban and come to Hogwarts...
That's right! He had a note from little d!
It looks like Dumbledore wasn't
helping Sirius, he was covering for us!
But wait, where have you been all year?
I've been living in the forbidden forest.
Hiding amongst the centaurs.
When they learned of my knowledge of the future,
they made me their leader and worshiped me...
...as a new god!
You're the leader Firenze talked about!
- You sent him that night to save us in the forbidden forest!
- Indeed, I did!
I worked hard to keep my presence
in the past a secret for fear of...
...disrupting the space-time-continuum.
[Reference to: Back to the future (all three parts)]
But -- my father has captured Harry Potter.
And I had to seek help.
I'm going to combat him with every -- second year spell I know!
We're talking squoushy-touchy-charms,
tickeling hexes and maybe, ...
...if I'm feeling especially cruel, ...
...a bubblehead-charm!
Well, if Harry's in trouble, we're there!
I don't know.
I mean the Draco we know always has an ulterior motive.
That's strange!
I've no ulterior motives.
Harry's in trouble! We have to think of a plan!
I'll try to think of something! Come on, let's go!
Oh, and Draco:
Thank you!
You're very brave!
Got a problem, Weasley?
No...
No?
Looks like you had a little one.
You may be entire jealous.
Maybe because I'm an older, more mature man,
who can use the potty and everything?
Or maybe...
...maybe this will make you jealous.
Yes. It is a crayon-drawing
of Hermione and mine's wedding!
Why...why are you guys wearing space suits?
And why is the priest a talking lion?
Those are - mature things. You wouldn't understand...
Yeah... Whatever...
Just so you know:
In the future, ...
...you don't get her!
So don't even try, Weasley.
Two things, Draco.
One:
You may be trying to help us.
Two:
You're still full of shit!
You have a poop-nose now!
- Get it off! -- Get the poo off me!
- Yes, you do!