Alright, Yaxley. Now when Harry Potter wakes up,
you're going to stand in the window between...
...these two and you're going to do that ahm...
...stiff arm-movement that you're so fond of, ...
...and you two, you're going to do this.
Yes, it's gonna feel goofy, but it's gonna
look so [peep] good! So make sure...
Oh! Shh! Places, places, places, places!
[HP is waking up.]
Oh, what the...
Where am I?
Hello, Potter!
What a marvelous display! I'm very impressed!
Hey, Lucius, where do you want
these boxes of torturing supplies?
Ah, just stag them right in here, thanks!
Woah! Wait...wait a second! What?!?
Torturing supplies? Who are you guys???
We are men who have lost a
great deal because of you, Potter!
I am Lucius Malfoy and we are the deatheaters!
Woah, listen, look...I know I beat your
Dark Lord or whatever when I was a baby, but...
...don't you think it's time you guys got over it?
This isn't about anything you've done, Potter.
It's about what you're going to do!
That doesn't make any sense!
Maybe not to you it does it.
But where I come from it makes perfect sense.
If I had my way, I'd finish you off right here, right now, Potter!
But I made a deal and you've got information I need.
So I'm going to use every torture imaginable
to make sure that... [cellphone]
Oh! Hold on, that's me!
Oh my god! Umbridge, stop texting me!
Did you get my text?
Yes!
Well, you didn't text me back...!
Oh! Looks like you found Potter.
Umbridge! Of course you're behind all of this!
Has he spoken yet?
We were just getting started.
Well, hurry up. And make sure
you keep your end of the deal...
...because I gave you your
little boyfriend and now I want mine!
I gotta go.
Oh, --  and Potter, ...
... I thought that you might like to know...
...that Umbridge has a whole army of
dementors on the way to the castle right now.
And they're gonna give your friend
Sirius Black a big fat wet kiss good bye for you.
And then maybe he can say hi to your parents!
[She's laughing (evil)]
- Oh! It's alright, it was my fault.
- No, excuse me!
Ron, I'm scared...
- This will never work, Weasley!
- Trust me!
Hey there! Who are you guys?
Oh... us?
We're... the backup deatheaters.
The union sent us over.
Curious.
What union?
The one for deatheaters.
Hmhm...
- Hmhm, I'm familiar.
- Oh...!
Well, they said before you'll torture Harry Potter
here you're required to take a ten minute break...
...ah,... so they sent over some pizza.
Deatheaters work hard.
But when we break, -- we break!
Give me some of that pizza, new guy!
What kind of toppings you got on that thing?
- Oh, you know, like your favorites,
mushrooms artichoke hearts, red peppers...
- ...and a knuckle sandwich! [boing]
- Ahhh! Ouch!!!
Ou! -- Look what you did!
Lucius, the new guy punched me!
I have the feeling these
aren't new guys -- at all.
Hey!!!
What happened to all the pizza?
Did it fall through the hole?
More like new children!
[Ron & Hermione: sounds of fear]
Come to see your friend get tortured, did you?
Well, you'll each have your own turn, you meddling little stinkers!
Well, ...
...looks like you caught us
And we were saving this...
...to celebrate saving Harry.
Well, I guess you guys can have the real pizza...
You don't mind if I do...
There's nothing worse then gettin' your hopes up for pizza
and then when you gotta get the pizza you get punched in the face!
[second boing :-)]
Phase one complete! Now phase two!
Untie Harry!
[Hermione is relieved]
Not so fast, Potter!
Deatheaters clean up those boxes!
Surrender yourself, Potter, or I'll torture your friend!
No! Daddy!
Daddy, it's me!
Would you really torture your own son?
Draco?!?
Surrender yourself, Potter, or I'll KILL your friend!
Leave Malfoy alone, Malfoy!
I do hate Malfoy, but he doesn't deserve to die.
Except we got no other choice.
I'll turn myself in.
Well, that's absuuuurd!
Bat-Boogey-hex!
Jelly-legs-jinx!
Snape!!!
Severus! You traitor!
You'll pay for this!
Put it on my tab!
- Stupefy!
- Woah!
Snape, you came to save us!
I sure did!
I made a vow to Dumbledore, I'll protect you kids.
Besides, I couldn't let the last trace of Lilly Evans be destroyed.
You have her eyes, you know?
Her eyes and...
I have to go!
Go on, kids, I'll fend them off!
Come on! Come on! We gotta get out of here!
Alright, but first:
Let's take that piece of garbage down!
Yeah!
Alright, guys, ...
We gotta go find where they're holding Sirius!
- Yeah! Alright!
- And there's just a whole lot of
dementors on the way to kill him!
They're gonna kiss him! They're gonna finally and kiss him...
Ron, man! Come on!
It's... It's stuck on there with magic...
[laughing - an onstage blooper]
That's okay.
Don't worry about it!
Aaaahm... we gotta... wait a second! Wait aaahm, ...
...aaahm, what the hell is Draco doing here?
Oh! Right. Harry, this is Draco from...
- ...the future!
- Future.
- What?!?
- Yeah!
He's really nice now! And you know what?
We couldn't have saved you without his help.
We mustn't lose them!
Quick, hide!
Where d'they go?
[threatening the audience with his wand]
I think they went that way!
No, you idiot! There they are!
- Geez! What a dumbass!
- Yeah...
- Whatever, let's go save Sirius, guys!
- Alright!