Sirius: Sirius! Yeah! Yes!
Oh! Ah... looks like they got a
Taylor Lautner poster in here too...
Yes, they are everywhere...
in every single room...
What are you kids doing here?
We've come to break you free!
Yeah! But Umbridge is coming with
a whole army of dementors and...
...and they're gonna kiss you!
Stand back! Alohomora!
Ah, magic!
Sirius!
But if you're seen being helping me
you'll all be in really big trouble!
We don't... we don't care! You're innocent!
I know, but who's gonna believe a bunch of kids...
...and a no-good washed up loser like Malboy?
And me, the most wanted criminal in the world, I mean...
...god, what kind of a dumbass will believe this bunch?
This dumb... --This dumbass!
[troubles with opening the door ;-)]
Lupin!
Lupin, Sirius is innocent!
If you just let me explain...
Harry, there is no need to explain.
I know that he's innocent and I've got proof!
WHAT?!? How?!?
This! The Maraunders Map!
I was on the Hogwartsexpress when I began
to get chilly and I decided to use it as a blanket.
That's when I noticed a name on there
that shouldn't have been there.
The name of a man that I believed to be long dead.
Peter Pettigrew!
That rat-bastard!!!
Who is that?
Harry, Long ago your father was friends
with Sirius and best friends with me, but...
...he had -- another friend.
What? It's impossible. You can't
have more then two friends!
It was a fatal mistake.
Peter Pettigrew betrayed your parents
and killed all those people!
- Then he set me up and disappeared!
- Until now.
'Cuz he's in this room!
What?!? Where...
Looks like...
...there!
Me?!?
Ron, how could you? You traitor!
I'll kill him, chaps! And then she'll be all mine.
No!
I... something's wrong, I'm not Peter Pettigrew!
The map's never wrong, Ron.
Or should I say Peter?
No! No, wait! Wait! If you look at the map,
Peter Pettigrew's name is on top of Ron's!
That must mean that
Peter Pettigrew -- is on top of Ron!
Scabbers!!!
He must have magiced himself into a rat!
That totally makes sense!
Die!!!
Stomp him!
Well, he put up a fight, but he is dead now.
The nightmare is over!
Wait, that's... weird.
The map says Peter Pettigrew hasn't moved,
but... it must be wrong...
No, the map is never wrong.
Whahahahahaha!
It's... it's... it's...
Peter Pettigrew!!! Aaaaaaaah!
You finally figured it out.
Expelliarmus!
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna drug and kill you!
How could you betray
James and Lilly like that?
I know. James was my best friend.
But I was his best friend...
But the Dark Lord, he can be very persuasive.
He offered me a robot hand.
And all I got was this lousy T-shirt.
You're never gonna get away with this. Now that we found you,
Sirius is gonna be free and you're gonna go to Azkaban!
Oh... I've got a better idea.
How about I'll kill all of you
and get away scot-free...
Oh... ahm, really... no, no!
You should go to jail.
- Yeah.
- We could vote on it.
Vote? Why don't you VOTE on
what's gonna be on your tombstone?
Red vines!
That's it! Red vines!
Hey! Poster-man!
Wouldn't killing us taste better with a red vine?
'Course!
Everything tastes better with red vines!
Well, here.
Why don't you have one?
Alright, Weasley.
I'm gonna trust you this time.
You can...
But I don't want to see any funny tricks!
No tricks, just treats...
I just want you to hold out that delicious...
...red stick of candy...
It's gonna be right here...
- ... and I want you to... just stay right there
so I can put my mouth around it.
- It's gonna be right here.
Alright, here I go!
Yummy yummy yummy...
Stupefy!
Red vines: What the hell can't they do?
You did it, Ron!
Ron! That was....Great!
Your poster-boy days are over, Peter.
You're going to jail. Crucio!
Well, Ron, we're sorry about your rat.
Yeah. Sorry.
It's okay.
He's been dead for years.
Sirius, ...
...I'm sorry that I doubted you for all those years.
How could you think I would betray
James and Lilly like that, I mean, I was his best friend!
What the hell am I?!?
You thought you were his best friend?
Yeah...
I tell you what.
There's only one way to settle this.
From this moment on...
...YOU and ME will be the best friends!
That's all I ever wanted...!
Touch down!
Come here, Lupy!