Oh Lupin, it feels so good
to hug and kiss you again.
I know. But d'you know who
deserves the kisses? These kids!
You're right.
Ah, Hermione.
You did some amazing  back there.
You really are the cleverest bitch of your age.
Thanks! That makes me feel really special.
Good. And you! Ron!
The guy who's always helpin' out!
Thanks for helpin' out.
- Hey, no problem.
- Cool!
And you. Little Dracula Falmoy.
You're little d, aren't you?
Sure am.
Get over here.
To you I owe my freedom.
What can I do for you, count Dracula?
Well, there's this girl I like but...
...I'm not 100% positive she likes me back, so...
...shall I tell her how I feel, perhaps in a...
a letter or... ah drawing?
Or an angry e-mail?
No, no ,no, no. Rule no. 1, boys:
You never tell a girl that you like her.
It just makes you look like an idiot.
Okay.
And you. Harry.
While I was rotting away in my cell in Azkaban, ...
...you know what happy thought
kept me going, got me through it?
It was you.
So thanks for saving me, Harry.
I had to, Sirius, you...
you're the only thing that I have.
So what are we gonna do with Peter Pettigrew?
Well, we'll take his ass back to the ministry...
...and I'll get my charges dropped!
- You're gonna be a free man.
- Sure will.
Alright, gang.
[Lupin is Laughing]
- Let's hop on some brooms and head back
to the ministry on the double, okay?
- Alright.
- Let the beautiful full moon light our way!
- Yeah...
Damn it! I mean... Shit!
Aaaaah!
Ah, my transformation!
Lupin, my best friend.
Did you take your potion tonight?
What's happening?
Whaaaa!
Lupin! You know the man you truly are!
This heart is where you live!
This heart! Right here!
Transforming in the full moon?
Lupin must be a... a...
A gremlin!!!
[screams]
Go long, and so long!
No! No, he's... he's getting away!
No! We need him to prove that Sirius is innocent!
Well, that's not gonna matter if I'm dead!
Remus! It's Sirius!
Your best friend! Remember...
[knock out]
- [Howling]
- We're done, for it!
[Another howling]
What... what is that?
What's that noise?
Hey! Hey, where is he going?
Where is he going?
Werewolfs respond to the call of their own kind!
The forbidden forest must be crawling with them.
Oh yeah! Like the one that chased us on Halloween!
The one that stole Lupins brooch.
Lupin, that reminds me of his best friend Sirius...
Sirius!
Is he dead?
- Almost.
- Come back to me, Sirius!
You mean: Come back to Umbridge!
Aaaaaaaah!!!
I [peep] caught you red handed, Harry Potter!
I caught you helping Sirius Black!
And now you're not childrens no more!
You're CRIMINALS!
And you're all gonna get the dementors kiss!
Harry, look! It's Dumbledore!
Umbridge, stop! Your beef isn't
with these sexy boys! It's with me!
Dumbledore!
Did you get my texts?
Yes, I got your texts! I got all ninehundred of them!
You've been clogging my inbox for long enough!
Well, you didn't text me back...!
Dumbeldore, she's gone completely crazy!
- She's working with deatheaters!
- She's tried to kill Harry!
I know, kids. But the buck stops here!
Umbridge: I've tryed to be nice.
Tryed to be fair, but there come to time,
when you have to lay down the law!
This is my school and these are my chillings!
And it's time for you to leave and never come back!
Dumbledore, this is just our first fight.
And it'll be our last.
Oh my god, Dumbledore!
Why d'you be such a lousy boyfriend?
Will you get it, you crazy bitch?
I'm GAY!
Well, choose not to be gay then!
Umbridge, if you don't stop, I'll be forced to violence!
Nuh-uh!
No Way, no how! A man
does not threaten his woman!
[breaking Dunbledores wand]
- Woah!
- Oh...!
There goes the elder wand...!
What's the elder wand?
Oh, it doesn't matter now, Harry, ah...
- Umbridge, ah... maybe we can work something out, Huh?
- No!
No! You're too late!
Why, D...Dolores, I'll be your boyfriend!
NOOOOO!
[Echoing]
Remember that time?
When you wouldn't talk to me?
No you wouldn't talk to me
yesterday.
We were gettin' along!
We had that little dance-y thing!
Well here's a song I sing
my way,
It was gonna be fine.
But you didn't wanna be,
be the man who'd be with me--
no way.
But now you sayin' it's time--
Why you gotta be like that?
I don't like the way you act
around me.
So baby come on, come on...
well don't you tell me to go,
and say "I'm the one,"
d-d-do you think I'm dumb?
Sorry- did I just stutter?
Won't tell you what you know,
but this is the end...
You were never my friend,
you were never my--
you were never my lover!
Remember that night?
When I saw you tremblin' there?
I remembered, "I don't care,"
about you.
I'm rememberin' how
you thought you were at the top,
well I think we're better off
without you!
And I got your number--
and I don't mean in my phone;
would've already just thrown it out,
if I'd known about
the way you'd bitch and moan,
remember that way--
when you were way outta line?
Well now you're way outta time!
So tell me what you want on your tombstone!
Come on, come on...
Well, don't you tell me to go,
say "I'm the one,"
d-d-do you think I'm dumb?
sorry, did I just stutter?
Won't tell you what you know,
but this is the end...
You were never my friend,
you were never my--
you were never my lover!
I, Dolores Jane Umbridge, ...
...hereby sentence you, Sirius Black, ...
...to death by the way of dementors kiss!
Umbridge, listen to reason, for god's sake!
It's too bad you a loser.
Too bad you waste my time.
Good thing that I'm around
to keep your ass in line!
No! No! Stop it! Let him go!
Leave him alone, you bastards!
[trying to fight the dementors off Sirius, fading out himself]
You were never my--
you were never my lover!
[Laughing]