[Moaning, waking up]
Oh, wipe out part two...!
- Oh, Harry!
- Harry, you're alright!
We thought we lost you there
for a second, good buddy!
Yeah, the dementors almost kissed you...
Where... where is... S...Sirius!
- Where... where is Sirius?!?
- Well, Harry, there were hundreds of dementors.
It took all my skill to grab you kids and escape!
But we gotta find him! We gotta go save Sirius...
Harry, Harry! It's too late!
- What?
- And Umbridge is too powerful.
Oh, Professor! What do we do?
You four stay here. You'll be save here!
And I'll see if I can find some help, inform the ministry..
But Umbridge works for the ministry!
- Weasley!
I gotta find someone who can help me save this school
before Umbridge turns any more dementors on any more kids.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Disaparate!
He's left us! He's LEFT us!
Well, we... we can't just let Umbridge destroy
the school whole, what are we gonna do, Harry?
There's nothing we can do.
What?
Don't you get it?
It's over, we lost, okay?
Sirius is dead, Umbridge won,
the school is ruined! It's over!
Hey!
The Harry Potter I know wouldn't just give up!
That's 'cuz the Harry Potter you know
is a twelve-year-old superhero!
And I'm just an eleven-year-old child!
How can we do anything, if there's no time?
Time...
Hold on to me, friends!
What? Draco, what are you doing?
Alright, everyone.
I hope, you're wearing your diapers.
You sure gonna shit your pants!
Aaaaaaah...
Draco, what did you just do?
- Where are we?
- Why did I shit my pants?
Thats merely a side-effect of
negative-lightspeed-travel.
Quick, hide!
...and go...BURRRRrrrrrrr
Oh my god, who's that? I think I'm in love!
Wait, Potter! What I'm trying to say is I'm torn up.
And if you go in there you're
going to be in big trouble!
You can't bee seen!
Oh, forget you!
Oh, Potter! What really pisses me off...
Snape, can I... can I say something for a second?
Sure!
Listen, ...
...I've realized something, okay?
You lead a pretty thankless,
ah... selfless , miserable life...
...and despite to how much everybody hates you...
you stick by Dumbledore and...
and you take care of his kids.
I never said this, but...
...you're a great guy!
Thank you.
Harry Potter...!
You're a hero!
I was going to let those
deatheaters murder you, ...
...but now I'm gonna sober up and save you!
Thank you, Harry Potter,
Figment of my own guilt! Huh!
Potter...! What, where you trying
to lead us straight to fally?
One more hot, sharp move like that and you
could have raptured the space-time-continuum!
What are you talking about?
Where were we exactly one hour ago?
Ahm... I don't... know, I think we were...
...pretending to deliver a pizza.
Get down!
Then I'll punch him in the face!
I don't know about this, Ron.
Who the... Is that US?
In a way.
That WAS us from one hour ago.
That was our past selfes!
I used my father's time-turner to travel back in time.
That's why we shit our pants!
Yes. But, don't you see, Potter?
Now we have time!
- Time to...
- ...to save Sirius!
No, no, no, no, no, but...
...we can't beat Umbridge. She's still so strong!
She's working with a band of dementors!
Yeah, but we can use the patronus-charm,
that Lupin taught us!
Yeah, but when you use the patronus,
you have to have a happy thought!
Okay? And every time we get
near those dementors, I'm just super sad!
There's absolutely no way we can win.
No way?
You listen to me now, ...
For eleven years I was just
a douchbag under some strairs.
But this year I found out I'm a wizard!
I'm famous! I can fly, turn invisible...
...and I just traveled the [peep] back in time!
[peep] you, Draco, how's that for a happy thought?
So there's absolute NO WAY,
that there is no way, you hear me?
My mind is racing, but my heart, it beats faster.
I'm in control, commander and master.
Lady Fate, kept creating disaster--
but she ain't the boss of me!
A head-on collision with a catastrophic setback
makes you either wanna get lost, or get back.
I choose the latter; let's not forget that
we hold the cards this time,
so there's no need to bitch or whine!
There's no way
I'm gonna take another option,
no way I am gonna settle with a loss!
No way I'm gonna sit around and watch,
there's no, no way...
There's no way
you're gonna find me in the background,
no damn way you gonna see me satisfied!
No way they're ever gonna make me back down,
no, no way...
Home field advantage,
the upper hand is ours,
so the game is on!
The clock ticks,
but we've got our tricks
to fuss with and fix what wrong!
Let's wake up and go, guys,
take out the bad guys,
break out your mad eyes--
YEAH!
We'll take it on together,
we're stronger and we're better
and if there's a problem--
--Whatever!
There's no way
we're gonna leave it up to chance,
there's no damn way we're gonna go without a fight!
No way you gonna see us on our ass,
There's no, no way...
There's no way
we're gonna settle with sorrow,
leave right now if you think this ain't real!
Today, not waitin' for tomorrow!
No, no way there's no way,
[3 times]
there's
no
way!