So there is absolutely nothing that
can get in the way of us saving Sirius.
No you idiot, there they are!
Aaaaahhh!
- Got you, Potter!
- Holy shit!
Forget Umbridge and her deal.
I'm killing you right here right now, Potter!
No, papa.
You're not.
Draco...
...you danced!
I finally taught you something.
No.
The centaurs taught me that.
Body-bind-hex!
Oh, no!
Yaxley, ...
...how would you like to work for me now?
Yes sir, mr. Malfoy.
Alright. Awesome. Alright.
- So I suppose you'll audition for the men now.
- No.
I'm auditioning for the wizard cops.
- Damn!
- And how does this sound?
You're going to jail!
It sounded forced.
Coward!
If you were any kind of real man
you'd finish me off yourself.
Come on, friends!
- Let's turn in this belly-rumbeling-curr!
- Yeah!
Don't you want to know
who your REAL father is?
What?!?
You were never my real son.
How could you be, you were always
such a horrible disapointment to me.
Draco, don't listen to him!
He's just trying to trick you.
- He's a liar!
- He's an asshole!
- Yeah!
Tell me who my father is or
I'll hex you, you wiener-jacket.
You do have some Narcissa in you.
That tramp mother of yours!
She choreographed an affair
with someone behind my back.
Someone I trusted.
Someone I may have even loved.
- Olivander?
- Filch?
- Regulus Black, Sirius's Brother?
Me?
No!
Dobby!
My former house-elf.
No!
Oh, yes. It explains a lot, doesn't it?
Your irrational fear of the potty.
Over 600 house-elves die in toilet-related incidents every year!
They fall in.
Why else would you have such a little d?
It's so small...
IT'S 'CAUSE YOU'RE A [peep] ELF!
Oh, Dobby!
And now I lament all those times that I...
...I beat him senseless within
an inch of his live and then, ...
...oh yeah, that one time, when I
drowned a little of his young, my --
-- brothers?!?
Now you know.
Could you imagine the scandal if that got out?
"Lucius Malfoy's wife beds Smeagol!"
So I had to take you in.
You should be thanking me for raising you
and sending that traitorous creature away!
So he's still alive?
Perhaps.
But now I see that banishment
is far too merciful a penalty.
Yours shall be far steeper!
-Crrrrr...
- No! He's just a poor little elf!
- Crucio!
- Ahhhh!
- NO!!!
- Hermioneeee!!!
Oh, does that upset you, boy?
Aww! Crucio!
Nooo!!!
I'm going to finish you off, one by one!
Starting with her.
And Draco, you'll watch your friends die!
And then I'll do what I should
have done twelve years ago!
[Grrrr]
Avada....
- Lupin!
- [Grrrr]
Wait, ah...
It's a robot!
- Kill him!
- Kill him, kill him!
No!
[Screams and Grrr]
Yeah!
Woah, well...
-  Let's go save Sirus!
- Right. Yeah. Alright.
- No, Yaxley. I thought you said
you were our friend, this way.
- Oh.