- Aaaahhh! No!...
- [Umbridge is Laughing]
Umbridge, for the love of wizzard-christ! pull them off!
Kiss them all! Kiss the children!
There we are.
Pure magic!
Harry, ah...
Let's go, boy!
Wait! Get them! Get them!
Fine, forget them, we'll get them later!
Dementors, I order you to kiss Sirius Black!
The only person that's gonna kiss Sirius Black is me!
- And me!
And I'll kiss him too!
Potter? But...
...but I...
...but you just went...
...but I saw you... go... but...
duuuuuah...
Fine. It doesn't matter.
Dementors, I order you to kiss all the childrens!
- That's the time to put the patronus to the test.
Get those happy thoughts ready.
- Yeah!
And don't cross the strings!
[Reference to: Ghostbusters]
Expecto Patronum!!!
NOOOOOOO!
Where are all my friends going???
Now for you, Umbridge:
You terrible horrid bitch!
You just want everybody to be as miserable as you are!
You're so focused on your past, that you can't appreciate the present.
That's no way to live.
How can you possibly move foreward if you're always looking back?
Oh my god.
How come, I never saw it before?
Umbridge, ...
...there's always time to make commence.
How come, I never saw --
--  what a little fairy you are, Potter!
Weapons! Now!
Ain't there more behind your back?
Now for you, Potter:
I think it's time for that  long overdue punishment!
I'm gonna pop your head off with my bicep!
I swear to god, I am going to kill you, mama!
[neighing]
Not if the good Firenze has anything to say about it!
It's Firenze, our centaur-friend!
It sure is.
And you, you biatch, ...
...unhand HP at once!
Fine.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm gonna pwn this pony!
[cheers for Firenze]
This must be the emotion you humans know as blood.
I'm bleeding.
Bring it, you [peep]!
My chest!
I'm gonna get you! I'm gonna get you!
Silence!
No! No! No, this is impossible!
I'm invincible!
Wohoa! What marvelous strength!
What a virtuous day!
Finally I may have found someone powerful
enough to survive coitus with the centaurs!
Yaaaaaaayyyyyy!
What?!?
I shall take her back to my treevillage...
...and tonight the centaurs will make celebration.
With dancing, song, music and much coitus with this one.
Yaaaaaaayyyyyy!
Thank you, Harry Potter!
You've saved my people!
Wait! No! I can't have coitus with a bunch of centaurs!
I have a boyfriend!
Help me! Help me! Help me! Help me!!!
Yaaaaaaayyyyyy!