We did it, guys!
Harry, Harry, what happened
to Umbridge and the dementors?
Oh, it's okay of all that. I have a funny feeling
we're not gonna be seeing Umbridge again.
Ever!
Well, chocolate-frogs. Harry Potter did it, y'all!
Yay!
Uh, my aching head!
- Bloody [Eff]!
- It's Sirius Black!
No, no, no! Shh shh shh!
Ahh! Quick! Somebody call the ministry!
Oh, Arthur!
Oh, that's me, isn't it? I'm silly!
Everybody, it's okay! Sirius is our friend.
Yeah, he's really nice now.
It's true, everybody. He was framed...
and he's cute too.
Yes. But I'm afraid there's no proof.
How much no proof is there now?
Argh!
What you're looking at is the corpse of Peter Pettigrew.
The man thought to be killed by Sirius years ago.
Can I get a time of death on this, please?
I'm no coroner, but ah...
...looks like he was killed 10 minutes and ah...
- ...36 seconds ago.
- Thanks, Neville.
How could Sirius have killed him years ago, ...
...if he's only been dead for 10 and a half minutes?
Yeah, why does he look all --
freshly bloody and mangled?
Yeah, how did he end up like that, Lupin?
Yeah, Lupin?!?
Yes, ...
...probably the work --
of that infamous Hogwarts jaguar.
Makes sense to me!
Yeah, yes! The ah... the Hogwarts jaguar, ...
...responsible for so much propriety damage
to Hogwarts this year, especially...
...in my office.
Uhm, uhm.
"Lupin shouldn't have to pay for that!"
[Behind the back of this hand - voice altered]
Yes, who said that?
Probably that jaguar plus his...
...soft adorable paws that he trips over
when he's running too fast.
Well, in light of this new evidence, ...
...I on behalf of the ministry of magic, ...
...hereby absolve Sirius Black of all crimes.
Yeah!
Oh, Ronnie! Over here, Ron. My son!
Kids, come here!
You saved me! Thank you so much!
'Course Sirius. Hey, listen. I was wondering.
Maybe this summer, instead of going back
to the Dursleys, I was wondering if maybe I could...
...stay with you.
Harry, I am homeless.
Can I live with you?
I don't think the Dursleys would like that very much.
So were to you gonna go?
I don't know, I mean, ah...
I've been in prison for so long.
I thought I may just travel the world.
I've always wanted to see Venice.
If you're gonna be gone for a while, --
I want you to take this with you.
Accio broom!
Thanks, Harry. Your firebolt.
Listen, Sirius. Do you...
Do you need some ah... money or something?
Aw no, no! I couldn't possible...
how much do got on your purse right now?
I'm just gonna take it all.
God bless you!
You're coming, Lupy?
Sure am, Sirius.
Lupin, aren't you gonna stay and be our
defense against the dark arts teacher?
No, Harry.
I've quite literally taught you everything that I know.
My last lesson was how to get your self fired.
In fact, Dumbledore just fired me.
Yep.
Even after my -- fake jaguar story and everything.
Well, there you go.
Oh man, I'm gonna miss you guys!
Hey, don't you worry, Harry.
I'm sure we're gonna see plenty of each other
next year. Isn't that right, Draco?
- Oh, rather not say!
- Alright.
- Hop on, Lupin!
- I'm taking front.
- Take the captain's.
- There we go.
Well, ...
Bye!
Uh, my head. I'm so magically hang over.
What did you do last night, Severus?
Well, I broke a couple of my own rules, I suppose.
Confessed my love for Lilly Evans, ...
...I saved Harry Potter...
...and I made out with Grubbly-Plank again.
Severus, you're too cute!
Well, Hot-damn. It certainly has been
a remarkable day, hasn't it HP and co.?
I'm going to write an article all about it.
Perhaps it could make the prophet's front page.
YAY!!!
Come on down to the great hall, kids, for a wicked party.
[cheering]
5, 6, 7, 8...
Hermione can't draw.
Hermione cannot draw...
[Hermione is singing it too]
Hey Draco, aren't you comming?
I reckon I'd run into my past self there. So... no.
Oh, alright. See ya!
- Hey Draco?
- Yeah?
I was wondering, if you and your dad
really came back in time then...
...how was our first year at Hogwarts
really supposed to go?
Oh, well.
Looking back on it was supposed to go exactly like this.
Just makes a lot more sense to me now.
I guess we were always supposed to come back.
Well, I have to go into the forest and wait
to catch up with my own time, so...
...good bye, miss Granger.
Bye.
- Miss Granger!?
- Yes?
I know past me might say some awful things,
but I hope you can forgive him.
No, I can't forgive him.
But I think it's about time that I forgave you!
Oh!
Hermione, I... I have something to tell you.
Yes, Draco?
You're the -- prettiest girl in the entire school.
Really?
And I'm actually quite fond of you.
Oh, Draco what are you saying?
I didn't come back just to save Harry.
I guess what I'm saying is that...
...every time I look into those --
beautiful boobies of yours, ...
...I can't help but feel that I'm in danger of...
- ...falling in love with Hermione --- Granger.
- Oh, oh, oh!
Aw, oh!
Nooo!
No.
What?
Draco, I know that I have the lowest
self esteem out of anyone at Hogwarts but...
...but I think that I can do better.
Right. Sure, no problem.
No kisses for little d, it's fine.
- I'm an asshole.
- No, don't.. don't feel bad. You're...
Listen:
You're always gonna be a stepping stone
on my journey to feeling good about myself.
So thanks for being there, --
for me to step on.
Bye!
Yeah, no problem!
See ya!
What a bitch!
Why, my best friend and leader, little d.
Why the long face my king?
Oh, nothing.
Just bitches ruining my life.
Oh, little d.
I've seen you grow up so much
over the course of this past year.
You're brave now.
You're courages, ...
...you're artistic, you're heroic.
Little d, -- you're cool!
[cellphone rings]
Hold on, that's me!
It's a text from Umbridge.
What did she say?
"Where do you go?"
"I miss my little pony."
"Less than three."
[ <3 ]
Ha, oh a heart.
I rather like this human.
Well, little d, we should get going
back to centaur tree village.
You're right.
No sense sticking around here.
This place has really gone to the dogs.
Well perhaps next year you'll be transfered to Pigfarts.
You know about Pigfarts?
Oh yes. There's an article
all about it in this weeks Quibbler.
- Care to read it with me?
- Oh, ...
...I don't need to read an article to know about Pigfarts.
I can tell you all about Professor McGonagills, the flying fish or...
...Syltheris Snake and his vendetta
against Growles Rumbleroar.
I'd like that.
I'm Luna Lovegood.
Oh, right.
- You're that girl who was mysteriously
absent from our second year.
- Yes.
Would you like to come live in the centaur village with me?
Sure!
Good thing I brought extra diapers.
You wear diapers too?
All respectable wizards do!
Neither of you are riding on my back!
Let's walk.