Glad to know things are finally gettin'
back to normal around here.
It's good to have you back, Zefron.
It's good to be back...
Oh Sorty, I missed you like the dickens!
Scarfy, ...
...I've had a lot of time to think and... well...
I never want to be apart from you again!
Will you make me the happiest hat alive...
...and be my magical enchanted accessory for life?
[gasp]
You call that a proposal?
Oh, Sorty... you're hopeless.
But yes!
Yes! Wizard god, yehehes!
Congratulations, you two!
Could I be the best man?
Oh, Dumbledear...
Hey, professor Dumkbledore!
Oh! Hey, Harry!
I was just stopping by to say good bye
before I went home for the summer.
Oh, that was very sweet of you, boy, but while you're here,
I think I have something that belongs to you.
Harry, I don't know if I can ever thank you enough.
Not only did you help save me, but you helped
save the entire school and Sirius Black!
Harry, we are cool. I mean from now on, boy:
you and me, we're tight.
- Really?
- I knew it ever since you were a little
baby and I left you with the Dursleys, ...
...that one day you grow up to be a
great Gryffindor just like your mom and dad.
I'm sure they're very proud of you, where-ever they are.
- Dumbledore, about my parents and the Dursleys...
- Yeah...
How come, I had to grow up in the
muggle-world where everything just kind of sucks.
How come, I couldn't have grown up in the wizarding world,
where everybody is... I don't know, really cool and treats me like...
...worshiped you? Treated you like an idol? Not like a little boy?
Harry, it ain't much to grow up
in a world where all of this wasn't special.
Because it's our time away from Hogwarts
that makes these seven short years so precious.
It's like with Ron and Hermin.
Surely you're not gonna see them for a while now, but Harry:
You've got these days of summer to remind you how much you really love them.
Yeah, I guess so!
It'll all make sense when you're older,
now get out of here, little scamp!
I've gotta go interview our new
defense-against-the-dark-arts teacher.
Got it down to ah,...
Gilderoy Lockhart, Mad-Eye Moody
and some fellow named ''Squirrel''.
I don't want anybody dangerous,
so I think I'm gonna go with the squirrel.
I'll see you next year, boy.
I'm gonna miss you, Dumbledore.
I will miss you too, kid. I love you!
Disaparate!
Alright Harry, see you next year, mate! Bye!
Have a good summer, Seamus!
Peace, my brother, my brother!
Oh, Dean, get out of here, you crazy son of a bitch!
Harry Potter!
I thought you might like this.
It's a picture of your mother.
The last one known before she died.
Thanks, Snape!
That's really nice of you.
You really are a great guy.
I said you'd like it, not you could have it!
It's going back into my pillow, where it belongs!
Geez, Snape is such a dick!
Hey! We haven't to worry about that now, Harry, because...
well... because it's summer!
Yeah!
We've got these days of summer
to remind us of each other...
The time we have to spend apart
will keep us in each other's heart...
I'm hoping that the good ole' days are
something I will dream about at night...
Don't matter if it's soon or later,
I know that it's gonna be alright!
I don't wanna see you go,
but it's not forever, not forever!
Even if it was, you now that
I would never let it get me down.
You're the part of me
that makes me better, wherever I go!
So I will try
not to cry--
but no one needs to say goodbye...
I don't wanna see you go,
but it's not forever, not forever!
Even if it was, you now
that I would never let it get me down.
You're the part of me that
makes me better, wherever I go!
So I will try
not to cry--
but no one needs to say goodbye!
Harry can you believe that we only get seven years at Hogwarts?
Yeah, but that's what makes it so special.
Sure we have to go back home for summer.
But imagine how... how totally awsome going back's gonna be.
'Til then I gotta go back to the muggle-world.
They're gonna try and tell me that this wasn't real
and none of this happened, but you know what?
It WAS real, and it DID happen!
We've spent time here, we've made
friends here and... that's a part of us.
'Cuz Hogwarts is... it's bigger then any of us,
it's bigger then any of it's founders.
And it's gonna be run long after we're gone.
Maybe we'll see our kids come here one day.
That's the thing about Hogwarts.
No matter how long you're away from it...
well, there's always a way back!
Back to witches and wizards and magical beasts,
to goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts,
it's all that I love and it's all that I need
at Hogwarts, Hogwarts!
Back to spells and enchantments, potions and friends,
to Gryffindors! Hufflepuffs! Ravenclaws! Slytherins!
Back to the place where our story begins
at Hogwarts, Hogwarts!
"I'm sorry, what's it's name?"
Hogwarts, Hogwarts!
"I didn't hear you kids!"
"Man, I'm glad we went back!"