Once upon a time
In a far away land, there was a magic kingdom
that prospered through it's commitment to two simple ideals:
Duty and Devotion
The two Ds.
For many years the kingdom stood as a shining beacon for artisans, craftsmen and storytellers
who all flocked to the land with the dream to uphold the sacred two Ds.
Through their hard work a glorious golden age came to the kingdom,
Followed by a second, even greater than the first.
Then came the dark times.
The kingdom fell into the hands of an evil sultan and through his negligence the kingdom fell to ruin.
Huh!
The happiest place on earth became the crappiest place on earth...
Despite the efforts of one man.
A man with the dream to restore the kingdom to it's former glory and to bring about the prophesied third golden age.
A misunderstood man.
This is his story.
The untold story of a royal Visier.
I look around the kingdom and see the desperation
And the devastation that persists,
no matter what I do.
But today could be the day
I finally make a difference!
And all the grateful citizens will say to me...
Fuck you!
[reference to: Walt Disney's Beauty and the Beast(bonjour)]
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you, Jaffar.
Oh, good morning, baker.
Where are you off to today, you no-good piece of shit?
Raw! Piece of shit!
What did you just call me, you bastard?!?
No friend, I said nothing! That was my bird.
He has the ability to repeat words that others have spoken.
Hm. Well, in that case maybe you should teach him these words:
Fuck you, Jaffar!
Marie! The baguettes! Hurry up!
Why don't we have enough to eat?
Why are we dying in the street?
Why does my baby always cry?
Why did my mummy have to die?
Mine too!
Mine too! Mine too! Mine too!
The answer here
is crystal clear:
Jaffar, that ugly old Visier!
Yeah!
He's the reason for our many woes
Though we're upset
We shouldn't fret
We mustn't let ourselves forget
the saying ever child raised within the kingdom knows
You've got to dream a little harder.
When life won't go your way, simply dream a little harder
Trust me when I say, that when you dream a little harder
you're sure to muddle through
'Cause if you're good and you're attractive
no need to be proactive
Good things will just happen to you!
I've come to return the book I borrowed.
Oh, Jaffar.
It took you long enough, you shit eating dog!
Well, I couldn't put it down. It's one of my favorites!
The story of a misunderstood witch, who's really not wicked at all. She's just green.
[reference to:the musical 'wicked']
But she still gets blamed for all the kingdom's problems.
Oh, so you think you're better than me just 'cause you can read?
Well, get out of my bookstore!
We don't like your kind in here anyway!
What about the book?
Keep it. And may the rats ejaculate upon you!
Thank  you!
Why is the kingdom plagued by theft?
Why are there no more good jobs left?
Why does the sun go down at night?
Why is everyone in the kingdom white?
[talking across each other]
Jaffar?
Jaffar!
Jaffar! Jaffar!
No man who's just
could ever trust
a face that triggers such disgust!
His twisted features give me such a chill.
So let us pray
that one fine day
that evil man will go away
'Cause if we want it bad enough, he will!
For if you dream a little harder
you'll get what you desire.
Dream a little harder, when things are looking dire.
If you dream a little harder, success is guaranteed!
If you are sure of your intension,
some magic intervention
We'll give you the extract you need!
Oh! Pardon me, Ma'am!
Oh, that's alright, just try to keep your fat face out of that motherfucking book.
I know, that I'm no prize
I'm m not so easy on the eyes
I can't rely on looks to get me by.
But ugliness permits
a man to use his wits
'Cause pretty people never have to try.
I hear the people whisper as I walk about the streets
I know they call me:
Ugly old Jaffar!
What I call planning, they call scheming,
what I call delusion, they call dreaming.
Why am I the only one who sees things as they are?
wish a little stronger!
I need success!
Why not buy some?
I want to fly!
That's unrealistic!
Think a little louder!
I want to be a cat!
-What?
-Fuck you!
Whistle while you swallow a spoon full of sugar and your dreams will come true upon a star!
[okay: reference to: Disney's: 'Snow White' 'Mary Poppins' and 'Peter Pan'.]
Dream hard enough, my friends!
Jaffar will meet a violent end.
He could be ...[???]... by a sailing ship.
Or hanged in tangled jungle vines!
Or eaten by hyenas!
Or he'll plummet until his death from a castle!
A clock!
Or a cliff!
And if we dream a little harder...
Our impatience and honor
Will rid us of that ugly old Jaffar!
Wonderful! That was wonderful! Thank you!
Bird, sometimes I feel as if you are my only friend in this world.
Raw! Fuck you!
Right...!
No, my book! It's covered in mud! Oh *sniff* No!  Wait, is that shit?
That smell is me, Jaffar.
You would not believe the morning I've had.
Why is my captain of the royal guard covered in shit?
Well, my men and I just jumped from a window and into a cart of crazy Hakim's discount fertilizer.
Why?
We were chasing a man.
No.
A devil!
A thief, who ever day robs from the common folk.
Bread,
Laundry off of cloths lines and ever watermelons.
We try to catch him, but he's always just one jump ahead.
Today things got a little out of hand and a lot of good people are dead.
E-explain!
Well,
the sword swallower slit his throat from the inside, when the thief's pet monkey riped the sword right out of it,
you know the guy that sleeps on the bed of nails?
Yes.
A fat guard fell on him.
Now he's dead.
Then when we fell form the window and into the cart of manure,
Kabal snapped his neck on the impact, two more choked on shit...
All this for a loaf of bread.
Abdullah, you're alive? I thought you choked on shit!
Did we get the loaf of bread back?
Oh no, I'm sorry, the thief got away wi-
Yes.
Yes, Abdullah, we got the bread back.
Praise...
...Allah!
This is all your fault, Jaffar!
My fault?!? How is this my fault and not that thief's?
There wouldn't be any thieves if you fixed the social economic inequality like you promised!
Why do you even bother visiting us commonals any more, you AristoCat?
[reference to: Disney's 'AristoCats']
There's a very important prince coming into town today from one of our vessel kingdoms.
The land of Pixar. I've come to welcome him personally.
[Is there a reference needed? Pixar vs. Disney]
Another suitor for the princess?
No, if only, captain! He's here because the trade agreement between his kingdom and ours has expired
and I've got to extend the contract or our kingdom is doomed.
That's why I've pulled out all the stops to make this prince's visit a happy one.
We've arranged a character breakfast with our princess
giving him a two day park hopper pass
and a lanyard for souvenir pin collecting.
Everyone must treat this prince with the utmost respect.
Ha! I saw that very prince riding by on his horse earlier.
No!
He was being accosted by the same thief we just spoke of.
What!
The street rat threw a whip in his face! He told him that he'd never seen a horse with two rear ends.
Now, I'm not sure if the thief meat that the prince had a big horsey ass or a horse ass for a face.
Either way, everyone laughed and the prince was furious.
Oh. I better go back to the palace and make sure his breakfast with the princess goes well...
But Jaffar, isn't she known to sick tigers on visiting princes?
Oh, shit...!
You're right!
I sure hope, you haven't goofed this one up, Jaffar...
No, no, I haven't! Why don't you go apprehend the thief, what's his name?
There are whispers, rumors only. They say he's called... Aladdin.
Then we must find this one. This - Aladdin.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Look at this mess.
Dead bodies in the street...
The state of this kingdom...
It's no place to raise a monkey.
Come on, monkey, don't be scared. Yeah! It's just a dead body.
You can have fun with him.
Look, you can kick him,
you can eat him!
Most importantly:
You get to loot him!
Ah, there it is! Look at that.
Hey! That looks enough like you. That'll get you in the bars.
Those guards should have just let me take this bread.
Don't they get it?
I'm not a bad guy.
I steal only what I can't effort.
And that's everything.
Want food, but got no money
I'm screwed, or so it seemed.
That's why I came up with this brilliant scheme:
Just steal everything!
Alright, monkey, let's feast!
ugh! Raisin!
I hate raisin.
Hoah! Hey, little orphan kids! 're you guys hungry?
You want some bread?
We do, sir!
Fetch, you fucks!
For real, I'm not that picky
I'll steal whatever's in sight.
Don't judge,'cause you don't understand my plight.
Hey, my crutch!
Nah, nah, loser! I steal everything.
Bread!
Bread for sale!
Very reasonably price for these hard times!
Hey there, friend-o!
Not you again!
Please, you just stole a loaf of bread from me this morning!
Yeah, and you gotta stop putting raisins in them, man! I hate raisins!
I was talking to monkey about it and he thinks we should just kill you.
But I was like: No, monkey, that's crazy!
But now I'm kind of thinking:
Yeah...
No more fuckin' raisins!
No! No, please! I ... I'll bring you some more bread tomorrow with... no raisins!
You're the best! I'm gonna tell all my thief friends about you.
But you owe me one!
Did you know this barbaric country?
They'll only give you money if you work.
Thanks, but no thanks - the man.
I'll keep steeling all I can
instead of being a fashist yuppi jerk!
Hippie! Fucker! Slacker! Sucker!
Who would seek employments,
when life offers her enjoyments?
Anything I get I can get for free
Besides, the economy's shit
So I make haste for making exits.
Get chased by a murderous mob
Hey man, still he's getting the job
Am I right?
Oh, getting in trouble a little early today, aren't we, Aladdin?
We're only in trouble if we get caught.
Aladdin?
Huh, I'm in trouble!
After this night we spent together, my belly grows big with child.
And my father says that you must marry me, or I'll bring dishonor to my entire family!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow!
I can't give up all my dreams and settle down, just because your dad's being a dick.
Oh...
Besides: If I do marry,
I want it to be for love!
Oh, Aladdin!
I understand.
I knew you would.
You're such a special girl, Jezebel.
Who's Jezebel?!?
Oh-oh! Busted!
Yoink!
Asshole! Oh, wow! Douchebag! Hey now!
Just one question: Why, man?
'Cause you stole my daughters ...[???]...
That's completely fair, but in my defence: Dude, your daughter's hot!
Yeah!
I feel that it's my duty
to steal, 'cause stealing's an art
I'll steal clothing and shelter, whatever I lack
candy from babies, the shirt off your back!
Credit identities, thunder and seams.
and intellectual property, whatever that means.
And if you'll look closer this poor little orphan will steal your heart!