Alright. It's imperative that this prince's visit is a happy one...
and who knows? Maybe he and the princess will hit it off.
Good luck marrying her off.
Oh, prince Achmed, your Excellency!
Is this how your kingdom treats it's guests, Jaffar?
Take a look at this!
Tell me! What do you see?
Your heart boxer-shorts, my liege.
What else?
Your ass cheeks, my lord.
My ass cheeks...
They're hanging out!
And what's this?
Blood!
Blood on my ass cheeks!
Tell me, Jaffar:
How the fuck did it get there?!?
Well, is it because - ah...
It is because your princess just sicked a Bengal tiger upon my ass!
I am lucky that it is so purt and small.
Oh, I am grateful for your tiny ass, my lord.
I can not believe that she thought that she could feed a prince...
...to a Bengal tiger.
And that there would be no political consequences.
This really is an act of war, Jaffar!
And she treated it as if it were a throw-away joke.
As if I were some silly side character, here only to illustrate her reluctance to get married.
Well - not only am I the ruler of a sovereign nation, ...
...but I have feelings too.
And people who care about me.
But you must forgive our princess. She is youthful, but well meaning.
Do not feed me a shit and call it couscous, Jaffar.
This is yet another insult, that your kingdom has heaped upon mine!
But you can no longer afford such arrogance.
Consider your kingdom's greatest exports over the last ten years.
Toys, exotic fish, trash compacting robots and other such incredibles.
[Toy Story, Finding Nemo, Wall-E, The Incredibles]
All produced not by your kingdom, but by mine.
Yes, you produce the goods and we distribute them.
You take the credit for them!
No, we share the credit!
Well. Perhaps we don't want to share the credit any longer.
I had considered extending our alliance.
But now, because of your princess...
...that is completely out of the question.
The next time that I will return to this so called magic kingdom...
It will not be with a lanyard, ...
...or a two day park hopping pass.
...but with an army, Jaffar!
Prepare for war!
Oh no, Achmed! Wait!
No!
Nobody makes an ass of prince Achmed!
Damn that girl! Oh princess. You've got some explaining to do!
Oh no! No, the Indian swallowtails They've escaped!
No! I set them free.
But those birds were imported from a foreign land.
They can't survive here. The hawks will have them within the hour.
Well, an hour free is better than a lifetime in a cage.
Being fed and pampered and cleaned up after.
What kind of a life is that?
Princess, when are you going to learn that your actions have consequences?
That prince you just sicked a tiger on has threatened our kingdom with war!
Oh, it's not a big deal. He was such a joke!
Just like every other swaggering peacock I've met.
But not all of your suitors have deserved a tiger set upon them.
What about that first prince? He was a charming fellow.
I heard he once made out with a girl, while she was blacked out.
[Reference to: Disney's 'Snowwhite']
That's not charming!
That's kind of rapy.
Well, what about prince Eric, the sea-fairing floutist?
[Reference to: Disney's 'little mermaid']
He fucked a fish!
He did not fuck a fish!
He wanted to fuck a fish!
Oh, predator fish-fucker! Will anyone ever live up to your impossible standards?
You know, you have to get married one of these days!
Never! Marriage is a medieval construct that represents the ownership of women.
It's like slavery.
Grapes!
Besides - if I do marry, I want it to be for love!
*Spit*
One of these days you're going to learn that life isn't about dreams coming true.
It's a series of compromises and disappointments.
I was hopping that prince Achmed could fix our kingdom's problems, but now...
...we are worse off than ever and I've got to find a way to clean up your mess!
But ya - you -
*frustration*
Being a princess is so...
...stifling!
I'm suffocating in this palace.
Fan, princess?
Now I'm kind of chilly.
Oh, uhm - shroud of silk, my lady.
I can't wear this!
Did you know they make these things in sweatshops? Where have you been?
Spinning silk in your private sweatshop, mistress.
You actually work in one of those?!?
Yes.
That's supporting a corrupt system.
You're a part of the problem.
Yes, princess.
Am I the only one who wants more out of life?
I just want to be free so badly!
You slaves could never understand this feeling.
Yes, princess.
I'm the most powerful girl in the land
With a wave of my hand, I can give a command
But it's just like - whatever
Cause they don't understand
Look at my life from the outside and sure, I've got servants and tigers and stuff
You're probably thinking, she's got everything
Well it's true
Cause I do
But so the fuck what,
It's not enough
I want a life of adventure
With no orders I have to obey
And dangers galore, 'long as I can be sure
That I'm safe and secure at the end of the day
I've got to escape from this palace
For a life where I'll truly be free
I'll go live somewhere new, just as big with a view
And a few dozen servants attending to me
That's all I'm asking for
I just want everything
And more
I want the moon, I want to live on the moon
And eat it in a pie, and keep it as a pet
And wear it like a gemstone in my hair
And someday soon
The people who say I'm just dreaming
Like father and Jaffar
Will see how wrong they are
As I laugh in their faces through mouthfuls
Of moonbeam pie
I want to make my own choices
I mean please, is that so much to ask
But decisions are hard when I'm being bombarded
Why can't somebody help with this arduous task
The life of a princess is broad with complication
It's enough to make me wish I were lowly and poor
But like - with money
What I wouldn't give
To live in a new situation
Each slave and guard
Makes life so hard
'Cause I'm always barred
From having everything
And more