Alright team, we've got to brainstorm, we could be facing war...
Team?
Hello?
Hey, Jaffar.
Oh! Captain, where is my team?
My assistant Viziers? My think tank...
...that share my commitment to Duty and Devotion?
Has my whole two D department gone missing?
Oh. You haven't heard...
Heard what?
Bad news, Jaffar.
The order's already been carried out.
By royal decree of the sultan and his executive branch: The entire two d department...
... is to be disbanded!
All 150 of it's members are to be sacked!
Hmhm.
We put them in burlap sacks and beat them until they were dead.
But those were men and women of talent and quality! All those masters of craftsmenship just thrown right out the window!
Out of the highest window of the western tower...
But how could the sultan do this?!?
Don't blame the sultan, Jaffar!
This is all your fault.
You didn't have the two D department producing anything of value.
Well, yes, I know.
Well, see you...
To think our kingdom was once a pioneer of art and culture...
...and technology!
How did it come to this?
HOW DID IT COME TO THIS???
[starts to destroy the room in a rage]
Oh...!
Wait.
It can't be.
The necklace!
I haven't seen this in years!
Sands of time
Take me back
Before it all went wrong
When love was but a song
and tomorrow shone as brightly as the sun
Teach me to undo what's done
sands of time
take me back
Sugar dates, sugar dates and figs! Sugar dates and pistachios!
Salam, friends!
And praise Allah for this blessed day!
Salam, Jaffar!
And praise Allah for you, Jaffar!
Today's the day, isn't it?
The day the palace finally gets a good and honest man on payroll.
Assistant Vizier to the sultan.
Well, you'll straighten out those crooked politicians!
I'm sure of it!
Oh, now, now, people. I'm sure the higher ups in the palace should doing their very best.
They just need someone with strong resolve to keep them on the straight and narrow...
I suppose you're right, Jaffar. But how do you do it?
How is it that you are so good to everyone you meet?
My secret is simple, really anybody could do it:
I just follow the golden rule!
And what rule is that, Jaffar?
Why, it's as easy as one, two, three, four:
Follow the golden rule
For life's a two way street
Keep that in mind
and you'll be kind
to everyone you meet
Follow the golden rule
It isn't hard to do
Always treat others
like sisters and brothers
And they'll do the same for you
Before you harm your fellow man
Ask this question first:
How would you wish that he'd treat you
If your fortunes were reversed?
Follow the golden rule
that's how I choose to live
Wow!
simple reciprocity
is always my philosophy
I get back what I give
Stop, thief!
But sir, I'm starving!
Do you know what the penalty is for stealing?
Stop your hand right there, friend!
Omar, what's going on there?
This boy has robbed me!
So you take the law into your own hands?
It is my right, Jaffar!
But is it right?
Before you harm your fellow man
Ask this question first:
How would you wish that he'd treat you
if your fortunes were reversed?
Why take this boy's hand when you could just as easily put it to work?
Give him a job, ey?
And you, boy!
Don't you see that if everyone would steal from Omar's cart, that he would be the one who was starving?
Follow the golden rule
My hunger blinded me and forced me to act like an animal.
We're not animals, we're gifted!
With minds to reason and hearts to love!
Follow the golden rule
So what do you say?
Can you two work together?
Follow the golden rule
For life's a two way street
Keep that in mind
And you'll be kind
To everyone you meet
Follow the golden rule
It isn't hard to do
It's very easy
Always treat others
like sisters and brothers
And they'll do the same for you
Follow the golden rule
They'll do it for you
I think that's about enough fun for one day, huh, friends?
I'd better be off to the palace!
Good luck, Jaffar!
And re-mem-ber:
Follow the golden rule
That's how we choose to live
It's very easy
Simple reciprocity
is always our philosophy
I get back what I give
We get what we give
That's it!
I get back what I give
Follow the golden rule
I get what I give
Follow the golden-
Follow the gol-den-
Oh!
Excuse me, sir!
Whaaaaaaat?
Who dares enter the royal palace -
And disturb the royal Vizier -
as he rests in his royal chambers -
of the royal palace?
You!
Who are you?
Oh, me, sir? My name is Jaffar, sir.
Haha... yes.
The new assistant Vizier.
The coffee fetcher.
[laughing]
Well, I intend to do a little bit more than that, my friends.
Now, I know it's my first day, but
if you'll spare me some patience, I've prepared a list of reforms that the city is in desperate need of.
It's gonna take a lot of hard work and a little bit of elbow-grease.
But I believe that if we just follow the golden rule
that we can all create a whole new world for you and me.
And most importantly:
The great people of this kingdom...!
[the Viziers laugh about Jaffar's words]
Are you finished?
I, ah...
Listen, boy:
You speak of a golden rule?
[laughs]
We have our own golden rule here.
Whoever has the gold makes the rules.
What?
I follow the golden rule
How can a man resist
When the gold in his hand
let's him rule the land
With an iron fist
I follow the golden rule
it's either them or me
The gold that my neighbor
earnes for his labor
is gold I'll never see
Who has the gold makes all the rules
so he wins the game and then
the prize for winning:
More gold!
HaHa!
And the game begins again
Follow the golden rule
Alright, don't be such a fool!
Damn your stupid charity!
We chase our own prosperity
We -
Follow the gold, follow the gold, follow the gold, follow the gold
Follow the gold-
and rule!
And rule!
So,
just keep your mouth shut.
And your palm open.
And you may just get
filthy, stinking rich!
Come, gentlemen.
To the opium den.