Oh what is this palace life?
That'll teach you to sneer at a nobleman.
Oh my dear girl. What's been done to you?
Somebody cut off my ear.
Because they didn't like my face.
But that's barbaric!
Hey, it's home.
[Arabian Nights]
Well, worry not, miss. I am a studied healer.
I may not be able to save the ear, but I can stay the bleeding.
Ahm, it would help if we kept you talking.
You could start by telling me your name.
My name is Shahrazad.
I suppose this will be the end of me.
I'm here only for my beauty and - now that's gone.
Shahrazad, true beauty lies within.
But no scratch could tarnish your heavenly glow.
*Sigh* Your words are like honey, young master.
Oh, Jaffar. And I am master to no man or woman.
I am a servant to the people and therefore your servant.
*Sigh*
Tell me, ahm - what is it that you do in the palace?
I entertain nobels with singing and dancing and...
...stories
Stories? What kind of stories?
Oh, of anything you can image.
Tell me, have you ever heard the tale of the tiger head cave?
Filled with wonders beyond your wildest dreams.
A forbidden treasure. A rug possessed with the soul of a lecherous thief?
And perhaps the greatest treasure of them all:
A common oil lamp!
What?!?
Oh, but do not be fooled by it's common-place appearance.
This is no ordinary lamp.
It is the prison of a djinn.
A shapeshifter who will grant your every wish.
He's also really funny.
Well, there we are. Keep the bandages tight.
Let's the wounds become - gangrenes.
By Allah! Are you a sorcerer?
Oh no! No! Sorcery is a craft for fools and dreamers.
I am a man of science. I believe only in what I can touch and feel.
This cave you speak of: I can assure you it doesn't exist.
I would know because - I apprenticed a geographer
Oh you've just never seen it.
Because the cave remains hidden to all but those who posses the key.
Here, look!
A beautiful pendant.
A golden scarab if I'm not mistaken.
Half a scarab - half the key.
It is said that the cave was sealed by two lovers...
...who were then transformed into one golden scarab.
The cave will only reopen when the two halves become one.
The lovers are united once more.
That's beautiful.
So you see - You say you only believe what you can touch and feel.
Magic does nothing if not touch the soul.
And there's no greater feeling than that.
Wise words.
Perhaps you're right.
Oh! Sorry!
Perhaps I have been touched.
Ah, pardon. You  know many stories, do you?
I know a thousand tales
To fill a thousand nights
But now another story comes to mind
A noble young Vizier - ascends to wondrous heights
He's brilliant as he's handsome
And handsome as he's kind
He is at once familiar and unknowable
To the frightened girl he meets along the way
And to the girl's surprise - something in his eyes
Beckons her to know him and inspires her to say
I want to know your story
I want to know your past
So tell me slowly from the start
Leave out no detail
Savour every part
I want to know your story
So make the story last
I want to know each twist and turn
Tell me all I've missed
I've so much to learn
For when it comes to stories
I thought I knew them all
Now I'm face to face with one I can't seem to recall
The young vizier had come - to help inspire change
But fate had planned an unexpected twist
Within the palace walls he discovered something strange
And found the missing part of him he didn't know he'd missed
She is at once a comfort and a mystery
To the callow man she meets that fateful day
She's beautiful and wise
And something in her eyes
Beckons him to know her and inspires him to say
I want to know your story
I want to know your past
I want to know your future too
Fill my days and nights
With the tale of you
I want to know your story
So make the story last
Make the story-
And linger over every part
Tell it till I know
Every bit by heart
I never cared for stories
Until you entered mine
And now my only wish is that our plots may intertwine
But I forget what happens next
I'm not sure I understand
Remind me how she answers when he asks her for her hand
Took you long enough!
A thousand and one nights with you is not enough to spend
So let's make ours a story with no end
Honey, I'm home. Oh, damn that royal Vizier!
The common man is starving and he feasts like a self styled god.
My land reform bill will never pass.
They refused you again?
I work with the most selfish, corrupt, incompetent old men...
...their mouths aren't fit to hold a donkey's shit.
If I could just speak with the sultan! If for a minute I could have his ear!
As that nobleman took my ear?
Shahrazad, you jest.
I'm only joking, Jaffar.
Now that I have got you smiling, I think I'll give you a gift.
A gift for me? What is it?
*Bird croak*
Oh what a handsome bird that is!
*Croak* Handsome bird.
Oh it speaks our words.
I saw him in the marketplace and I knew he would delight you.
Oh what else does he say?
Anything you teach him.
*Croak* Donkey shit.
Oh, those harsh words are mine, aren't they?
You clever girl. Always finding new ways to keep me honest.
It'll be good for us to have something to love and care for.
It can be practice.
For us!
What are you saying? Have all of our attempts finally bore fruit?
Even when the doctor said it could not be so?
Oh praise Allah! The merciful and compassionate.
Assistant Vizier Jaffar! News from the palace.
Your request for a hearing with the sultan has been granted.
You are to report to the palace immediately!
You hear that, my darling?
My land reform bill being heard by the sultan on this of all days!
We're blessed, Jaffar.
Come with me to the palace and let us never be parted again.
A thousand and one nights with you is not enough to spend
So let's make ours a story with no end