Behold!
The representative of Allah
on earth!
Father of the country!
Shepherd of the people!
Sovereign of the land!
He of the two ladies.
Behold!
The son of Osiris
and ...[???]...!
The divine ruler!
Behold!
The royal
sultan!
The shoes of the savior's of gold ...[???]...!
I never thought I'd see this day!
What do you think he'll say to us?
What wisdom will he impart?
Silence!
The sultan shall now speak in his...
holy voice.
[caughs]
Many years ago...
[stops because the audience is laughing about his meager voice]
I - took - my - finger
And I pushed in my penis.
And it hasn't come out since.
...[???]...  (I will now hear from the court?)
A very wise and enthralling tale, my lord!
We can all learn a lesson from it... I expect...
Hmmmm, where's my opium?
I must have wine, sweetmeats and cheeses.
At once, my lord!
And now my lowly and unworthy assistant Vizier will
presents some issue or other for your holy consideration.
Speak now, Jaffar!
And don't fuck it up!
Greetings, your highness.
It is I, Jaffar. I humbly prostrate myself to you and offer up this bill of land reform. It is essential to our way of life!
Oh! Who are you?
Oh, me sir? I'm Jaffar as I said...
Oh, not you, you jabbering ape.
Her.
Oh! This is my wife.
Ah, it is an honor to be in your presence, great sultan!
Yeah.
She's my wife now.
I must have her for my harem.
What?!?
She makes my withered loins feel live again.
Very good, my lord. She will be yours at once.
No, she's my wife, damnit!
Do you speak against your sultan?
Against your king???
On your knees, boy!
What? No!
What...?
No!
Jaffar!
No!!!
This woman will be bathed and shaved and brought to you harem at once, my lord.
Shahrazad!
Noooohoho!
We can't let this happen! He's stealing you from me, he's a thief!
I won't let you go!
But you must, Jaffar!
The sultan wishes it, and it is our purpose to serve him.
But may - maybe I have a new purpose now!
The city needs you.
You are going to be a great Vizier some day.
That is what your story is about.
Oh, I wish I had the power to rewrite this tale!
Never stop wishing it, Jaffar!
Here!
Take this!
The pendant?
You remember the two lovers?
The key to the tiger head cave?
We will be reunited one day!
And unlock wonders beyond your wildest dreams!
First I lost her to the sultan...
... then I lost her to heaven.
I thought that if I just...
...did my duty I could get her back.
Now I AM royal Vizier.
And powerless to save her OR our city.
Unless...
The cave!
The lamp!
Of the wish granting djinn!
If I believed in wishes
as silly as it seems
I'd find that hidden cave
turn back the sands of time
And save you
If I believed in dreams
If I believed in magic
If I believed in good
I'd be the best Vizier
I'd make our troubles disappear
If I believed, I could
But wishes are dreams
and dreams are pretend
So science and reason
win out in the end
Science says you're dead and gone forever
reason says I'm talking to the air
But something in my heart
some secret hidden part
illogically insisted you are there
somewhere
If I believed in wishes
If I can find the key
perhaps it's not to late
to change the course of fate
'Cause after all I must be pretty great
If you believed in me