Jaffar!
Oh what is it, captain? Can't you see I'm busy?
Bad news. It's the princess. We've checked everywhere but she's nowhere to be found.
It appears she's run away.
All her talk of freedom. I should have seen this coming.
I agree.
This is all your fault, Jaffar.
Well, don't just stand there! Go out and find her! Leave no stone unturned.
I have an errand I must attend to.
Oh princess!
You poor naive girl!
I only hope you haven't fallen to prey to some  - sex crazed ruffian.
Right this way, babe.
I want to thank you again for saving me back at the marketplace.
I can't believe that man wanted to ??? me just for taking some of his apples.
Yeah. Those merchants are real dicks about that kind of stuff.
It's like: Is he really gonna eat all those apples?
[Apple.mov]
And all the once he doesn't eat he's trying to sell.
For money! So greedy!
But you're so generous!
Sticking your neck out for a girl you just met, while expacting absolutely nothing in return.
And then insisting that I stay with you tonight.
No prob.
I do it all the time.
Wow, you live here?
Well, I'm squatting here.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, it's kind of a mess right now.
It's hard to keep a big place like this clean.
Well don't you have someone to clean it for you? Like a slave?
Well, I've got this monkey, but ah -
He only cleans his side of the room, leaves the shower curtain open all the time...
...and he hasn't even started working on our screenplay.
Unbelievable!
This is so unfair!
Poor people need slaves just as much as rich people do.
Maybe even a little bit more.
And you know what the real sad part is?
The people in power are doing absolutely nothing to change that!
Change scares old people.
Yeah!
??? just don't get it, you know.
It's like: Your sixteen...
And I'm...
Yeah, wow...
I'm only 33.
I think I've seen it all but I forget how young I am sometimes.
I love how raw this conversation is.
You are so mature and deep.
Of course it's a free thinker like you who's struggling to get by.
And all because of our totally corrupt class system.
I hate the class system.
That's how I've said: Fuck it! I never go to school again!
So you abandoned everything?
To be free?
That is so brave!
Brave? Me?!?
Yeah!
But I was kinda forced into it.
I had to grow up fast.
My life has just been...
So hard.
I know you think
I'm this perfect guy
But there's something I have to confess
I only hope it doesn't make you like me any less
I got this tragic back story
That's driven other girls away
But I feel like I can trust you
You won't judge me for what I say
The others couldn't handle it
'Cause my story's just too sad
But here I go you outta know
I have no mom or dad
They died.
Earlier this year.
Now I'm an orphan.
All my parents ever did was support me.
Give me a place to stay.
Tell me they love me. No matter what.
They were really bad parents.
How is a 33 years old kid supposed to know how to survive on his own?
You've no idea what it's been like.
I had no one to bake me bread
No one to make my bed
No one to teach me the difference
Between right and wrong
Or to sing me a song
I long to be as strong as I used to be
But I was orphaned at 33
Aladdin, I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
I've got no one to hold me tight
No one to kiss me good night
No one to press their breast up against me and say
It'll all be ok
But hey that's just the way life is for me
Since I was orphaned at 33
They call me a jerkoff, a burnout, a punk
But I can't let that junk in my head
I could've been a contender if not for the fact that my parents are dead
All things considered I think I turned out pretty good
Pulled myself up by my bootstraps and starting
Stealing all I could
Still there's no one to love me now
But I'll make it through somehow
Despite being so sadly and crushingly all alone
But I make a solemn vow
That when I have kids of my own
I'll break the chain
You'll see
I'm gonna live forever
So they'll never know the pain of being orphaned at
Do you believe in love at first sight?
Absolutely.
I've experienced it.
Many, many times.
Oh, Aladdin!
There you are!
They are after me!
They are after you?!?
There she is, guys! Get her! Right there!
Guard him!
Come on!
Princess, I'm so glad we found you before this criminal was able to...
Give me my first kiss?
And you -
No high five!
And you ruined it!
Now, let him go!
I can not.
This man must face trial for his crimes.
But that is not fair!
He's a victim of circumstance.
Victim?!? Tell that to ??? twin brother Abdullah.
He was the victim.
Well, unlike Aladdin, he probably had a family who loved him.
Yes.
Exactly!
This man must face the due punishment for all murdering thieves:
Beheading.
Urgh!
Don't look at me like that!
These are my orders from Jaffar.
This is all his fault.
Jaffar is a monster!