You are late!
A thousand apologies, oh patient one.
You have it then?
I had to slit a few throats, but I got it.
Oh yes. Yes! The other half of the golden scarab.
Now I can finally find the entrance to the tiger head cave!
Wait, wait! What? You've slit people's throats?
I didn't tell you to kill anyone. This is awful!
Ha, ha! Jaffar, no. That is just an expression.
What?!?
Yeah. Means I got that killer deal at the marketplace.
Slit a killer deal.
Oh, duh. So you bought it of a merchant then?
Yeah! Yeah.
A real shrewd businessman too.
But I was not intimidated.
No. I walked right into his shop.
And I fucked his puppy.
What?!?
*laughing*
Jaffar, that is another common expression.
Uhg. That means that I put that merchant in his place.
As if he were a defenseless little puppy.
Oh!
Colorful expressions in the marketplace these days.
Jaffar, you need to learn to relax.
Not take everything to serious, huh?
Well, I beg your pardon. You've done an excellent Job. Here's your payment.
Ah, thank you.
It went great.
Until that merchant realize how bad I screwed him on the price.
Man, did he ever chopped my dick off.
*laughing*
He chopped your dick off! *laughing*
That is a good o-
What the fuck are you laughing at?
You think that's funny, Jaffar?
Maybe you'll like to have a look look, at what he did yesterday!!!
Ahhhh! Ugh!
Asshole!
We've got a kingdom to save and a lamp to find.
The tiger head cave is said to be a treacherous place.
But no matter. I know just the able bodied soul I can risk.
In good conscience.
So let me get this straight.
You busted me out of jail so I could go to a cave filled with mountains of gold.
And the only thing you want is a crummy old lamp?
Precisely. The rest of the treasure is yours. But the lamp is mine.
I love you, man!
'Cause I would have so much gold, I could swim through it.
Like a pool.
Think people could really do that?
No.
But once you have all that money, you can finally leave your live of crime behind.
Run away and never return.
I'm totally gonna do that. I just gotta do this one thing first.
Oh, what thing would that be?
Well, this thing...
Is a girl.
What?!?
Yeah! She's got these eyes, the chest...
And her butt, wow! And her totties, oh!
She's just...
She's just so - so -
Beautiful?
Fuckable!
But she's the princess.
To even stand a chance, I'd have to have enough money to like...
...hire an army of assassins to kill the royal Vizier and all the palace guards.
Then I can sneak inn and you know...
Porkher.
'Cause dude, once I get my mind set on a chick - I just can't move on!
Until I get this nut out.
Well, first you must escape the tiger head cave with your live...
...then you can get your nut out.
Your eternal nut out.
Nice. So where's this place anyway?
I don't know...
...yet.
Oh! It worked! It worked! Follow that trail!
I'll be treated like a hero
All the citizens adore
They'll throw a parade in my honor
With peacocks and monkeys galore
The people will cheer
For the royal vizier
For answering duty's call
Not that I care for glory
I just want a story with a happy ending
For all
I can't wait to be a rich dude
'Cause I've heard it told
That stealing is so much easier when you've already got tons of gold
But I got my eye
On what money can't buy
'Cause that princess is ooh hella tight
I'll be the one who plunders
Her cave of wonders
Get a happy ending tonight
My innocent Aladdin
Please darling don't be dead
It puts a damper on our love
If you don't have a head
I wish that you could fly away
Escape somehow and soar
And take me to a world where we'll have everything and more
Oh there it is! The entrance to the tiger head cave. Go on!
And one day the genie will say to me
Jaffar you're a man of such virtue
I hate to see how your loneliness and your memories hurt you
Shouldn't a man who's so noble
And who's influence so global
Have someone by his side
I know what you're wishin'
So with your permission
I'd like to bring back your bride
And with my wife beside me
My failures will be absolved
The world will be a paradise
With all it's problems solved
We'll retire off to some far place
And share an itty-bitty living space
A humble yet cozy abode
Where we can write our own happy ending
I want everything and more
I steal everything
We'll get our happy ending
Meaning everything
And that happy ending starts
I want everything
I'll steal everything
Tonight
Woo hoo!
Oh, what happened?
Dude, I was swimming through this pile of gold in there, right?
When it all turned into lava.
I'm so lucky I escaped on this flying carpet.
And did you get the lamp?
Well, I got a lamp.
Oh wonderful boy, toss it here!
Not so fast. You said you wanted a common oil lamp.
Yes.
Of absolutely no value.
Precisely, that's the one.
No this couldn't be it. 'Cause this lamp has a magic djinn inside.
He came out for a bit. He's really funny.
Oh I'm sorry. I know about the djinn. I'm sorry that I deceived you. I just needed it to save the kingdom.
Well you lied, dude.
All that other treasure was just lava in disguise.
So I'm stealing this thing.
Aladdin: One. Old fart: Zip-o.
See ya!
No!
Noooo!