Knock, knock.
Oh, you. Aren't you busy?
Ruining my life?
Well, I noticed you weren't at dinner, but I saw you try to poison my wine.
Usually when you do that, it means you want to talk. What's up? Are you mad at me?
Alright.
I've got to go find the antidote.
Where are you going?
There she is. So what's wrong?
Everything!
You ripped out my heart and smashed it into a million pieces.
And don't act like you don't know what I'm talking about!
Aaaaaah?
You know. That innocent boy from the marketplace!
The one that you sentenced to death.
You know!
Al - Al -
Allll-
Aladdin?
Yes! Aladdin!
The name that will forever be burned into my soul.
Well, first of all: I would hardly call him a boy. He was well into his thirties.
He was perfect.
Like - if you cobbled together all the best features from all the best guys...
....and then gave him a tragic back story.
It's like he was designed specifically to appeal to me.
Princess, he was not a nice kind of fellow.
You just didn't know him like I did!
No, you didn't know him like I did!
I know everything about him!
He was my soulmate.
My...
God, I'm freaking out! What was his name?
Ala - Aladdin?
Aladdin?
Uhm hm.
I'm writing that down.
Aladdin, that's weird.
It's two 'l's?
No! No, one 'l', two 'd's.
Uhm hm.
Oh, that looks weird.
Yeah, it's weird.
But princess, all your life I've been your Vizier.
Your tutor. Believe it or not: I care about you.
You're going to have to rule this kingdom one day.
And I'm trying my best to prepare you.
But I don't want to be prepared!
I want to expect the unexpected!
[reference to: Tiny toons?]
So you think you could handle ruling the kingdom right now?
Absolutely!
Oh, then how would you protect the kingdom against prince Achmed?
Should he invade.
Well, we - who?
Or more simply:
How would you fix the socio-economic inequality?
Oh, oh! Oh! I've been thinking about this a lot lately!
And ah - *clears her throat*
And how - how privileged I am and how - because I am the princess...
...everyone has to be nice to me and give me things.
So I think it would solve all of the kingdom's problems...
...if we just made everyone a princess.
Okay, ah -
You know it would work!
Look, you're young. You don't exactly get how things work yet.
And while I don't appreciate any of your ideas, ...
...I do appreciate the fact that you have ideas.
Maybe one day you'll have some good ones.
But I wouldn't give another thought to this Aladdin.
He's just like all the other princes in our kingdom.
Sexual predators, the lot of them.
Just look at their tactics.
They talk at vulnerable young girls...
...and build up false senses of trust.
And then isolate them on magic rides of sort.
And then, when the moment is right...
*whispers* They whip it out!
You know.
Their songs!
Oh! Songs...
Be wary of young boys who whip out their songs!
A song is often a prelude...
...to a dick!
A song is a dick in sheep's clothing.
And if you are ever in doubt, just remember this song:
A song is a dick in sheep's clothing
A song means a dick is on the way
Jaffar!
What is it, Captain? Can't you see I'm trying to import a life lesson?!?
I feel like you only come to see me when there's bad news.
Not this time.
Oh, thank heavens. What is it then?
Horrible news!
Some fool atop an elephant is leading a parade throughout the marketplace.
A parade! With no permits! No clearing of the streets.
What of the apple carts?
They're all turned over!
No!
And it gets worse. The madman's throwing gold pieces to the starving masses...
...and they are trampling each other to get to it.
I counted thirteen dead before the peacocks got to them.
Oh shit!
This is all your fault, Jaffar!
Maybe if you threw a parade every once in a while -
I don't want to hear it!
Captain, let's go! Princess...
...we'll talk later.
It was actually a pretty good parade.
They even had a flying carpet.
A flying carpet!
Could it be...
No! That Aladdin is far to clever to show his face in this city again.
And even if he did, he'd be in such heavy disguise.
Knock, knock, knock.
Did somebody order a prince?
Huh!
Aladdin!
How the fuck you know it's me?!?
Because it is you. You're just wearing different clothes.
Well, pretty and smart!
You're the whole shabang, babe!
But how did you escape being executed?
Ah, I escaped 'cause -
I'm a prince.
You're a prince?!?
But I thought that you were a poor orphan boy.
Oh I'm having trouble believing this.
No! No! I am a prince!
Everything I told you the other night was a lie.
Don't you trust me?
So...
You're not a tragic figure rebelling against the man?
Babe, I am the man!
And you stole all that stuff just 'cause?
Exactly!
Ugh!
Oh no! Okay, uhm...
Now I'm kinda feeling like everything about you that was attractive to me before...
...isn't really there anymore.
Nooo! No!
I'm just being indecisive.
It's still you.
I've just got to get back on that high that I was on before.
Oh!
You wanna get high?
Yes.
Look into my eyes and talk to me some more about the world's injustice!
Sure.
Just let me roll this blunt first.
Yo. djinn. Listen up, little dude!
I know I can't wish for this chick to fall in love with me, 'cause...
...that's against your rules or whatever. But...
I don't want her to love me, man!
I just want her to fuck me.
Can I wish for that?
No?!?
Geez, how many rules've you got, dude?
Funny bastard!
Alright. Guess I'm gonna have to do this the old fashioned way.
Hey! Aladdin here! How are you guys doing tonight?
Cool, cool, cool. Now shut up for a second! I wanna get serious.
You guys know there's a way to get people to think about sex.
Not even talking about sex.
You just gotta do it - subliminally.
Watch and learn!
Hey, babe.
Such a beautiful night. Take off your clothes!
What did you just say?
I said it's beautiful out.
Look at the west tower of the palace and take off your clothes.
What does it look like?
A big - long - shaft...
...with a tiny head on top.
What does that remind you of?
A Giraffe.
Really?
It's not what I see.
No.
Maybe you can (take of your clothes).
Get a good look at it from down here.
What do you say we...
...take a maaaagic carpet ride?
(And your clothes off?)
Oh! Uh!
Let's go to a place...
...that's a bit more isolated. (Where you can't escape taking off your clothes. Take off your clothes! Take off your clothes...)
Oh no, you guys!
Do you thing that Jaffar could be right about Aladdin?
*Audience agrees*
[Guy in audience: I DON'T THINK SO!]
Me neither!
Aladdin is so nice and charming.
I mean, it's not like he's singing or anything.
See that palace of gold
Shining, sparkling, metallic
And a little bit phallic
[reference to: Disney's 'little mermaid']
Take a look and you'll agree
See those leaves on the ground
Spelling something explicit
[reference to: Disney's 'Lionking']
(SFX?) [youtu.be/edtwq4P8jUM]
Don't you blink or you'll miss it
Gently asking you and me
Take off your clothes
So many hidden messages
Subtle, but slightly lewd
But if you're shrewd
They'll put you in the mood
To take off your clothes
I feel compelled subconsciously
I don't know why or how
But here and now
I'm tempted to take off my clothes with you
I want to take off my clothes with you
I feel free as a bird
With no cage and no owner
Look that priest has a boner
[reference to: Disney's 'little mermaid']
No I think that's just his knees
Take off your clothes
What a perfect romance
The universe is telling you
I can't wait till we're married
Each sign is planted there
With loving care
Accept the cosmic dare
And take off your clothes. Don't dare to pretend with me!
And take off your clothes. Princess take off your pants!
Show me your magic carpet
Even the stars above
Reflect our love
They want me to take off my clothes with you
You love me?
Sure!
And you're a prince?
Babe, I'm the most powerful prince in the world.
More powerful than prince Achmed?
Hey, I don't even know who that guy is.
Maybe this is how I help save the kingdom.
By marrying you.
Marry me Aladdin!
If I do...
Will you...
Take off your clothes
Wait not so fast
Let's make this last
At least your top
Aladdin stop
Listen babe, I mean I know you're scared. I mean I am too.
I've never done this before.
Well, until we're married, can't we just sit out here and look up at the stars?
Okay.
Hey: I respect you, you know.
Take off your clothes