[laughing]
But...
...let me ask you this:
Is your penis an inny or an outy?
uuuh...
Inny.
Oh! Mine too.
Sultan! My lord! My liege!
Jaffar can't you see I'm in a mind blowing conversation with this furry man?
What is it?
I was just in the marketplace, clearing up after an unauthorized parade, when I saw him: Prince Achmed is back!
Who?
I prayed that he was just a one-off joke, not to be taken seriously, but...
...he's brought the entire army of Pixar with him and they'll break through our walls! Our kingdom is doomed!
And I...
...have failed you!
Yes.
You have.
Like always.
And like always I've had to rectify your incompetence!
What? How?
Yes, the princess has finally chosen a suiter.
A prince whom she shall wed upon the morrow.
Ah, he will call upon his armies and they will defeat prince Achmed.
Well, who is this man, this hero?
My, the greatest prince in all the world!
Why, he's got 50 elephants,
Lamas galore, bears, lions...
A brass band!
...a brass band!
And horse! Don't forget about all my horse!
You!!! Where is the lamp?
Golly! Please don't hurt me!
Jaffar what are you doing to that prince?
This is no prince!
This is the wanted thief Aladdin!
How the fuck d'you know it was me?
Jaffar no!
Aladdin explained everything to me.
He was just pretending to be a wanted criminal...
for fun!
He's actually a powerful prince.
No, he's a liar, this is the truth!
I took him into the desert in search of a lamp containing a wish granting djinn!
Just - stay with me!
I was hoping to use the lamp to save the kingdom.
But this thief stole it from me and now I suspect...
No, what the fuck am I talking about:
I know!
I KNOW that he used the lamp and wished for this prince costume.
THAT is what we're looking at right now!
I bet the lamp is under that lamp sized hat.
Bullshit!
Why would I pretend to be a prince? Just to get layed? That's not me!
Boy, do the first good deed of your life and hand over the lamp!
You have selfishly squandered it's magic for long enough!
Woah, woah, woah!
Why are you picking on me, Jaffar?
You're afraid I'll reveal your little secret?
What secret?
Does anybody else here...
... ever wonder how this guy just...
... opens his yapper and can talk anybody into anything he wants?
What's he using?
Logic! Reason!
See, I was kind of thinking...
of...
magic!
Sultan,
princess,
this guy...
...  is a sorcerer!
What?!?
Think about it:
How's it that he knows so much shit?
Hey, Jaffar:
Where do hippopotamuses come from?
Africa.
See, you fucking know that, sorcerer!
You are flying by the seat of your pants, boy! No one here believes you!
Yes...
I can't believe it.
I have had a sorcerer in my midst this entire time!
Guards! Capture that sorcerer!
What?!? No!
This is your own fault, Jaffar!
I should have known you were a sorcerer.
You're idiots! You're all idiots, taking the word of that worthless street-rat over a lifelong faithful servant!
How I ever served you for all these years I'll never understand!
I would have expected this from all of you bozos, but princess:
I am very disappointed in you!
Alright, I've heard enough, seize that vile betrayer, off with his head!
[Could be Reference to: Disney's 'Alice in wonderland']
No. I don't want to get my head chopped off!
So I'm going to combine this bottle of potassium chlorate and this bottle of sodium bicarbonate.
It'll create a large cloud of smoke, which I'll use as a cover to make my escape.
It will look as if something magical has happened, but it's simply a chemical reaction. Not sorcery.
Chemistry!
And poof!
[Excitement and coughing]
Wow!
I thought I was just bullshitting you guys, ...
...but he actually was a sorcerer!
Oh, I was in the same room as a sorcerer!
Captain!
Find that sorcerer!
Oh, I can handle this!
I got one wish left.
I was saving it for a bigger dick, but...
Oh shit!
Where's the lamp???
I've gone against my sultan
the highest act of treason
but I had good intentions
I did it for a reason
They'll kill me if I'm lucky
they'll torture me if not
What made me think that
I could get away with such a plot?
it's not too late to bring it back
perhaps I'll be forgiven
but if my crime can help improve
the world we all must live in
am I not bound by duty
to the people of this nation?
How does the golden rule apply
in such a situation?
As a citizen, I think, I would be grateful for the aid
but if I were the sultan I should hate to be betrayed
whichever road I take I'll be incurring someone's wrath
Till now I've always traveled on the straight and narrow path
temptation may have beckoned, but I always have resisted
But which way do I turn when the road's become so...
so...
...twisted?
[reference to: Disney's 'The little mermaid' (Ursula)]
Who are you?
A fellow traveler down the twisted path.
Oh,no! I know you!
From Shahrazad's stories!
Ah, ah, ah!
You think you know me as others think they know you.
But there are two sides to every story.
I used to be the ruler of the ocean
I was benevolent and always kept my word
but my brother held the antiquated notion
that women should be seen and never heard
So he dethroned me
then disowned me
and on top of that re-zoned me
to the outskirts of the kingdom in a cave
took my scepter and my crown
though I tried to take him down
The truth and I now share a watery grave
[cries]
The story lingers on
but the version that is drawn
is twisted
A pain I know all too well.
[Reference to: Disney's 'The lionking' (Scar)]
The pride had never seen a more progressive king than me
both lion and hyena lived in perfect harmony
I brought an end to what had been a senseless age of due
I was prepared for anything except for what ensued
My brother ate my heirs, my precious cubs and stole my throne
returned the segregation and the hateful ways we'd known
though I'd advocate for unity I always was denounced
So when I saw an opportunity to right the wrong - I pounced!
the pride came before my fall
in a fate that one might call
well, twisted
They weren't ready for my ideas.
No. They didn't hate you because of your ideas.
They hated you because of that evil looking scar on your face.
Fortune favors the beautiful.
Au contraire!
[french: on the contrary]
My only crime
[Reference to: Disney's 'Beauty and the Beast' (Gaston)]
was love.
In town there was only she who was as beautiful as me
On the inside.
But then tragedy struck.
She was taken hostage in a castle filled with
demonic furniture.
So I did what anyone would do and I organized a rescue mission.
But how was I to know that she had fallen in love...
...with her captor?
To me that doesn't seem...
...entirely healthy...!
Especially since he's a wolf... bear...thing...
...a Buffalo-monster!
In a cape!
But the heart wants what it wants!
And sometimes what it wants
is twisted
twisted
twisted...
[And so on]
I only wished to reclaim what was mine!
I only wished for equal rights for all!
I only wished to save her!
I only wished to be invited to the party
[Reference to: Disney's 'sleeping beauty' (Maleficent)]
I only wished to improve relations between the races!
I only wished to teach the boy responsibility!
[Reference to: Disney's 'Peter Pan' (Captain Hook)]
I only wished to give the people a voice!
So he wouldn't end up like me!
I only wished to love her!
To help the miserable, lonely and depressed!
To be included!
To live in harmony!
For once!
I never knew my father!
I only wished
[???]
I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished, I only wished,
I only wished to have a coat made out of puppies!
[Reference to: Disney's 101 Dalmatians (Cruella De Vil)]
Ugh!
Just leave!
[Talking across each other (tried to pick a few out)]
Why would you do that?
That's insane! It's insane!
They're babies!
It's an unfortunate situation.
But...
... you do have a choice.
[laughs silently]
What remains of a man when that man is dead and gone
Only memories and stories of his deeds will linger on
And if a man's accomplishments aren't in the tale they tell
Are the deeds that go unheralded his legacy as well?
If a war breaks out tomorrow, we'll all have hell to pay
Why protect my reputation? I'm a dead man either way...
How will they tell my story?
How will they tell my tale?
Will anybody even care?
The question then is whether it is nobler in the mind
to be well liked, but ineffectual
or moral but maligned
I'll never be a hero
who the citizens adore
But if I hide to save my life
what has my life been for?
What has my life been for?
the road ahead may twist
but I will never swerve
I'll give them all the unsung anti-hero they deserve
I've nothing left to lose
so the only path to chose
is twisted
let them twist my words
let the people scorn me
who cares if no one will ever mourn me
Let them bury the sign of the story they'll never learn
Let the truth be twisted
And my life be twisted
I'll be twisted, it's my turn!