Citizens of the magic kingdom:
Your armies have abandoned you.
Your ruling class is corrupt.
And we have come to put an end to your tyrannical rule.
You will never end our tyrannical rule!
Oh, princess. Funny thing you're here.
It is I, Prince Achmed.
Who?
Prince Achmed.
I visited you last week.
I swore vengeance.
I brought my army to ravage your people.
Oh, that's right.
Didn't my tiger eat your ass?
Tiger fucker! Tiger fucker!
Stop it!
No! Your tiger did not eat - or fuck!
My ass!
It is I who'll be doing the fucking today.
That's right. Bring Achmed his tiger and nobody gets hurt!
Shut up!
Stop it!
Ah...
What I meant was that I'm going to fucking destroy this kingdom.
I'm so sorry, Achmed.
You're not fucking destroying this kingdom anytime soon.
What?
We have a great and powerful prince to protect us!
One with an army far greater than yours.
Impossible.
It is said that he faced the galloping hordes.
That's like a hundred bad guys with swords.
Soon you'll be the one surrendering.
Prince Achmed, make way for prince Aladdin!
Aladdin!
Al-
Yeah, Aladdin!
Damn it! Where is he?
[Laughing]
It appears that your prince has cold feet.
Now step aside, princess! It's not you I'm after.
I come for the head of the sultan.
Then you come for my head, Achmed!
Jaffar?
Jaffar!
What is the meaning of this? You're not the sultan.
Yes, I am.
I have been gifted power, Achmed.
And soon I will have the power to destroy your puny army.
Impossible.
Come forth, my djinn! You old powerful and terrible thing.
You who can command the very stars and the moon.
Come forth and serve your master!
Ah, man! Ah!
Woah.
You talkin' to me?
Yes, I'm talking to you! Now get your ass over here!
Here's Johnny!
[The Shining]
Alright, Johnny.
That's the thing, John. When pirates of the Caribbean breaks down, ...
...the pirates don't eat the tourists.
So, I use my -
My first wish to become the sultan.
I wish I had a million dollars. Hot dog!
[It's a wonderful life]
Okay. Calm the fuck down!
Now, I must use your power again, djinn!
Of all the gin joins in all the towns in all the world, ...
...she walks into mine
[Casablanca]
Who?
Rosebud!
[Citizen Kane]
Jaffar, what's going on here?
Who is this very funny blue man, standing next to you?
This is my djinn, Johnny!
I'm Turbo Man!
I'm sorry! I guess his name is actually Turbo Man.
Psst! I'm B@man!
[Laughing]
Just give me a minute!
Listen, I am a mortal man. I don't understand you strange godlike tongue.
You're going to have to work with me, here.
I don't work for toons. A toon killed my brother!
[Who framed Roger Rabbit]
I have got to use my second wish to destroy that army.
And to do that, I have to become more than a man.
I've got to become-
A symbol.
No, no.
A Jedi?
A dick for.
What's a dick for?
Bwaaah!
Noo! I've got to become a sorcerer! Can you do that?
Yeah.
But you're gonna have to ask yourself one question:
Do I feel lucky?
[Dirty Harry]
Well, do you, punk?
Yes, I do feel lucky.
I've got a magic djinn!
But I think he might be a fucking moron!
Hey!
Don't look at me like I'm freaking Frankenstein!
[Austin Powers]
Give your father a hug!
Come, Scott! Come on, Scott!
Get your stinking paws off me you damn dirty ape!
[Planet of the apes 1968]
Hey Turbo Man! My future is about this long right now!
Are you referencing something? Are you trying to make me laugh like...
...like some kind of work of fiction that I'm unaware of?
I was not charmed by the song you sang when you came out of the lamp.
And I'm not charmed by your crazy bullshit now.
You either need to back me the fuck up -
Or shut the fuck up!
Got it?
You had me at hello.
[Jerry Maguire]
Good. Achmed, are you still there?
Yes.
Prepare to die!
Oh, alright.
I make my second wish:
I wish to become the most powerful sorcerer in the world!
Shwing.
Well, don't just stand there!
Charge!
Oh, shit! Oh!
Jesus Christ, you!
Hey! Where are we going?
Monkey!
Monkey, I got the carpet! Where - Ah forget him!
See you in hell, Monkey!
See you in hell, princess!
See you in hell, kingdom!
Aladdin!
I was looking all over for you!
Achmed is attacking! Where's your army?
Ah?!? They're just lost right now.
I'm gonna go meet them halfway, bring them back here, and then -
We don't have time for that!
We're all gonna die!
Right. And what's the last thing you wanna do before that happened?
(Take off your clothes!) Thats right: Have sex!
Hurry, take off your clothes!
I'm not gonna take off my clothes in the middle of a battle!
Why not?
No! No! No! No! No!
Nght!
My skin is melting.
Djinn! Djinn, where are you?
Come and fight me, Jaffar!
Fight me like a man, you cowardly snake!
I am tired of those mothereffing snakes on this motherfucking train.
Djinn! Achmed's forces are too great.
Even with all my power I cannot defeat them.
We'll have to take as many civilians as we can.
Move them to the palace and retreat.
In our moment of triumph? I think you overestimate their chances.
[Star Wars]
Would you stop...
...acting like an asshole - for one minute?!?
Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to seduce me.
[The graduate]
Okay. Okay.
Just move that palace to the top of that fucking cliff...
...over there!
Alrighty  then!
[Ace Ventura]
Come on, babe! You're such a tease!
You're making my balls as blue as my Genie's balls.
I'm not a tease!
I'm just not a freak.
Oh!
Alright. You're like a strong, powerful woman.
So maybe what you need is a strong, powerful guy...
...to go all strong and powerful on you.
Aladdin, stop!
You're pissing me off.
You're making sex seem gross and lame.
In fact - I'm sure - Yeah, I'm never gonna have sex with you!
Huh!
What?!?
You can never say never, babe! (Take off your clothes, take off your clothes...)
Why isn't it working?
What the hell is going on in here?
Nothing!
You got that, Aladdin? We're not a thing anymore, okay?
We're just having our first fight.
Maybe after some make-up sex -
No!
You know what?
I thought you were mature for your age.
But you're just like all the other sixteen year old princesses I've dated.
Except you're forgetting one thing.
I'm a thief!
I take what I want!
Get back, old timer! One step and the little girl gets it!
Alright. I'm not moving. Just be cool!
You don't need to tell me to be cool, motherfucker?
I'm getting out of here!
We're making a clean get away back to my apartment.
And little princess is coming with me.
No! I won't let you take her!
You have no idea how much that girl means to me. I love her!
Oh, you love her?
Dude, she's like half your age. You're a total pedo!
No! Not that kind of love, you shit for brains!
You don't understand!
My wife was with child when she was taken by the sultan.
She died in childbirth.
And then the princess was coincidently born around -
the same time.
By Allah! How could I have never seen it before?
The sultan inverted his penis years ago.
He couldn't have children.
Aladdin, please. Don't hurt her!
I love her, like a daughter.
Surely even you have felt this kind of love before.
Oh yeah. Ha ha.
I loved my parents.
But that didn't stop me from doing what needed to be done.
Wait, what?
Yeah, dude.
Remember me?
You...?
You're the guy who killed my parents!
Where've you been, man?
In your reflection.
I live here.
No, I live here.
No oh oh ho!
You're just squatting here.
W - w- w - wait!
If I'm you...
Then that means...
I killed my parents?
But I didn't want them to die!
Who are you kidding?
You wished for it every god damn day of your life.
They were gonna kick you out of the house!
They were, weren't they?
Make you get a job.
I don't want one of those!
That's why...
They had to die.
Wow.
I guess you're right.
I guess I should be thanking you.
Yeah, I think a thank you is in order!
Well thank you.
You're welcome.
Ah, time to get that lamp back!
Wait, what you gonna do with the lamp?
Wish for stuff, jackass!
Like how you wished to be this prince.
Pretty good idea by the way.
But there are better ideas.
Better wishes.
Like what?
I don't know.
But it's gonna be one hell of a ride!
Okay, Jesus Christ. I don't know what's going on here.
But you are in no position to be handling that knife...
...or this lamp!
Back off!
Listen to him, man. He'll kill you.
Yeah, now you're getting it.
See, I'm the one who deserves that lamp.
Because I'm the best wisher.
Because I'm the best wisher!
That's the trick!
You just really have to believe your own bullshit.
Who else could have done it?
And come this far? You?!?
You're an ugly old fart!
You're right, you're right!
I'm not the kind of person who can use the lamp.
I don't believe in wishes.
It takes someone who believes they can change the world to actually do it.
Yeah.
Someone like me.
So why don't you hand that lamp...
...over to someone who knows how to use it?
I think I will.
But if I give you the lamp - will you give me the princess?
Sure, you can have this prude.
I can wish for a slutty princess. Or a million.
I can wish for anything.
Get excited about this now?
Then so be it.
But first, I make my final wish.
Djinn! I wish to take your place as the wish granter.
Do you hear that? You're free!
I wish to be the all powerful Genie.
It's Groundhog day!
[Reference to: Groundhog day]
What the? Oh, no no!
The djinn can't be free!
I get a last wish!
Oh, come on. Work you stupid lamp!
Ah, this isn't fair!
Life is supposed to be fair!
I -
Yes! The power!
The absolute power!
Oh shiiiit!