Oh ho ho, shiiiiiit!
The universe is mine to command! To control!
And I am at your service - princess!
Jaffar!
You're...
... like a devil guy.
No, I'm just a djinn.
Oh...
Why did you wish for that?
Oh, don't you see?
Aladdin was right about one thing: My wishes were weak.
But you...
... your youth and your passion...
... and, yes,...
...your naivete...
These give you power.
When I was your age, I thought I could accomplish anything I ever wanted.
And more!
But I didn't.
Perhaps no one does.
But you have to think you will
or you won't have the strength to try, and maybe you won't make any big changes...
...but a few little ones, that path the way for the next generation.
And then they'll make small changes and leave it to the next and the next.
It's a bit like...
...a carousel of progress.
Always spinning towards a great, big, beautiful tomorrow.
And tomorrow is just a dream away.
But what if tomorrow never comes?
No. Tomorrow always comes.
Even if it comes without us.
Without me.
The lamp and the djinn must return to the tiger head cave, but before I go...
...I can grant three wishes.
I don't think I'm ready.
You must be. This is your kingdom now.
What will I do without you to guide me?
when I am lost, where will I turn?
so many doubts and fears inside me
I'm just a child, I've so much to learn
You remind me of someone I knew long ago
you have her eyes, you have her heart
that's why I love you so, and that's how I know
somewhere deep within you, like a tiny seed
waiting to grow into a flower, you have the power to lead
you've done your best to heed me, but you don't need me as a guide
for it's been in you all along, the power inside
if I do have power beyond what meets the eye
the source of all my hidden value is the moral you supply
if I'm capable of greatness it's not innateness, don't you see?
you're the one who put it there - the power in me
Do not be fooled by appearances, for though it may seem small
The power to love one another is the greatest power of all
no matter where life leads us, we'll never be apart
through thick and thin, success or ruin, I'll carry you in my heart
and I will treasure forever what the world will never see
You are kind, and that's enough
you're a diamond in the rough
and you are the power
the power in me
Now, princess: What do you wish of me?
I  wish there was a way to end the war with Pixar peacefully.
And I wish the kingdom had a sultan, who would make it the happiest place on earth again.
What else?
I wish you didn't have to go when our story's just begun
I'm sorry, princess. There are a couple of provisos, a few quit pro quos...
[Reference to: Disney's Aladdin (Gini)]
That's one wish I can not grant.
Then I wish you every happiness
It - is - done
Princess! Princess, there you are!
Uh! What is it?
It's your father! We went in to give him his daily pleasurings, and we found him - dead!
In his cold dead hand we found this declaration. Apparently his last act of sultan ...[???]...
From this moment forth the princess shall be the majority stockholder and so ruler of the kingdom.
Princess, it's a miracle!
What?
Achmed's artillery just blew open a secret vault in the palace...
...containing the lost treasure of Ali Baba.
[BASH!] Here it is, men! The throne room!
I'm sorry, Achmed.
You are not destroying this kingdom any time soon.
Wanna bet?
No.
I want to buy.
For my first act as sultan...
...I'm going to purchase the entirety of Pixar in the name of the magic kingdom!
Are you being ridiculous with me right now, princess?
Buy Pixar?
We are proud and noble people.
Very protective of our name and brand.
I could never sell Pixar for any amount of money.
Captain, how much was Ali Baba's treasure?
It was more money than I'd ever seen.
But I was able to count it.
7.4 Billion Drachma.
Sooooold!
And a pleasure doing business with you, princess.
But there is ONE condition:
You must bring in new administrators from your land, men with good ideas to help us rebuilt!
Well, that can be arranged.
We'll set you on the right track.
But you must respect our traditions and our heritage.
Please return our kingdom to its commitment to Devotion and to Duty.
You MUST bring back the two Ds!
All hail our new sultan!
The princess.
Oh rise!
Rise!
From now on no one need bow to anyone else.
Equality will finally come to this kingdom for all.
From now on...
... everyone... is a princess!
Even me?
Even you!
Oh yes, even you!
So many great things have happened today.
This is all Jaffar's fault.
Yes, you're right, captain.
Captain? Don't you mean princess?
I am so sorry, princess.
Darn tooting!
[laughing]
Wait, what happened to Jaffar?
So this is the life of a djinn.
Phenomenal cosmic powers -
shitty shitty livingspace!
[slightly altered reference to: Diney's 'Aladdin'(Gini) ;-)]
So ends the untold story of a royal vizier.
Funny.
That's not the ending I recall.
What...?
You're forgetting the best part.
When the two lovers were reunited and they live happily ever after.
Oh Shahrazade, but how...?
I'm pretty sure someone wished for your happiness.
So I've come back.
To stay with you in the lamp.
Doesn't this make you happy?
Yes, of course! But doesn't that mean, you're trapped here forever?
I alway said 1001 nights wasn't enough.
Oh, then the princess! She really did it!
Her other wished...
...came true as well!
By making everyone a princess she ensured that they were all treated with respect and compassion.
They all did then to others as they were done ...[???]... too.
She followed the golden rule!
And lead her people into the third golden age.
But Shahrazade, how do you know these things?
In the lamp we exist outside of time and space.
It's how the djinn was able to watch all those funny movies he quoted.
We can see anything, anytime - anywhere.
Oh, than let's see what happened to that thief Aladdin!
Aaaaaah!
Salam and good evening my dear friends!
[Reference to: Disney's 'Aladdin' (start of the movie)]
Please, come closer.
Oh, a little too close!
Is that Aladdin? He's old and fat!
Yes, look at this!
Comibination ...[???]... coffeemaker!
Also makes chilly and flies!
Will not break, will not... It broke.
He's hawking second hand goods,  he's a loser!
This is no ordinary lamp!
It once changed the course of a young man's life.
A young man, who was not what he seemed.
He does this 'till his 55th year, when he's killed by a thief over a loaf of bread.
And that's the end of the true story.
And what of our story?
How does it end?
It doesn't.
A thousand and one lifetimes is not enough to spend
At last we have a story with no end
Let this be a story with no end
A-a-ah!
Where we can write our own happy ending...
Made you look
[not sure here...Reference to:Nas?]
I know a thousand tales...
[Thanks for the show, Team StarKid
Thanks for watching the subtitles, everyone - xoxox]