The future is now!
Mankind has reached the stars!
And leading us into this new frontier is...
you!
Join the Galactic League of Extraterrestrial Exploration today,
and be a starship ranger!
Just like these ensigns here!
Hello, boys!
We're here to get the job done!
They sure are!
See new worlds!
We come to conquer...
...in peace!
Meet strange and fascinating new creatures!
Well, I wouldn't say... strange!
Escape the horrible robot wars of earth!
Annihilate human enslavers!
Boldly go, where no man...
Hey!
...woman...
Bark woof!
Haha!
...or data dog has gone before!
Sorry, K90X.
The starship rangers!
Leading human kind into the future!
For the past 900 years!
We're here!
I'm here!
We're here to get the job...
...get the job...
[alarm signal]
Captain's log!
Cap-cap-captain's log!
During our approach to an uncharted alien planet...
...unanticipated meteor shower.
...gamma radiation space storm!
...our outer hub...
...exploded!
Someone really f...
...ucked up big time!
We're going down!!!
[Crashing]
...starship crashed into this alien planet.
...but we ran into something else out there.
...hostile natives.
They're monsters!
Bugs!
[creepy noises]
Sliming aliens! Aaaaaaaaaah...
The future - the future - the future is...
...aaaaaaaah....
The fu - fu - future is no - no - now!
Be a starship ranger!
The future is now!
I wanna be
a starship ranger!
I wanna have
the things they've got
I could be
a starship ranger...
But there's just one little
thing they are
that I'm not
Yeah!
[laughs lightly]
beep, beep, beep, beep, beep!
Captain's log!
Hit the meteor showers, K90X!
I'll fight off this gamma radiation, if it's the last thing I'll ever do!
We're going down!
This is the last thing I'll ever do!!!
I'm here to get the job done because the future is now!
[laughs again]
All of my life I've pictured them out there,
keeping the peace in outer space
I may not be up there with them
but I've got what it takes
I've got a hunger and thirst for adventure,
I wanna travel the galaxy
The future is now
so I don't see how
the time isn't right for me
And I'll admit -
- it's -
- all in my head,
but who says it can't be real?
They may be far away,
but I can safely say
that doesn't change the way I feel
I wanna be
a starship ranger
Even if it might sound strange
Maybe now
I'm not a ranger
But all of that
is right about to change
Bug!
Bug? Are you in here?
No, but I am: A starship ranger!
Take this, you hostile native!
Pew, pew, pew! Pew, pew, pew! Pew, pew, pew!...
[goes on 'pewing']
Ah, how'd I know you'd be here?
Pew,pew... Can you pretend to die?!?
Okay.
[pretends to die]
Yeah!!! Pretend direct hit!
Mission complete!
My best friend Roach - is dead!
Okay, Bug, can we get out of here?
You know, this old alien wrack gives me the willies.
And no one even knows where it came from!
I do! It came from earth!
Yeah, whatever.
It's not from our planet, so I - don't - like it!
Oh, come on, Roach!
Hey! I got a great idea: Let's watch some videos!
I'll pull them up on the view screen!
No, no, no, no, no, those things scare me, and...
...I can't understand a thing they say.
Well, that's because the humans are speaking human language!
But it's okay. I can translate.
I've watched these videos a million times.
Oh, Bug, can we please just go back to the hive?
We aren't even supposed to leave the hive, unless we're doing our job!
But I don't have a job!
Yeah, but you're getting one today!
You, me and a million other bugs, we are going before the over queen!
Oh yeah...
Roach, I don't know.
I don't want to go into the over queen's slime pit and have her just -
- tell me what I'm supposed to do for the rest of my life!
Well, maybe I'm crazy, but -
- I feel like I'm meant for something...
...more!
Of course you're crazy!
Every bug in the hive goes before the over queen to get there job, that's how it works!
Everybody does their part for the greater good!
You know: The needs of the many bugs outweigh the needs of the few bugs.
Or the one Bug, yeah, I konw, but...
And besides... I hear it's not that bad.
Ah - Well, you know, at least that's what my ten million older brothers always said...
But Roach - It's not what I want!
Oh, yeah...
All of your life you've had your head stuck
up in the gaseous atmosphere
Don't forget, that dirt is solid
and clouds can disappear
When you're an insect you have a purpose
like it or not, from a fly to a flea
Need I remind you? Leave that stuff behind
so you can find what yours can be
Cause the needs -
- of -
- the many bugs
-they outweigh the few
And everybody knows
it's just the way it goes
and there's nothing you can do
You wanna be
a starship ranger?
Yeah!
Discover worlds
far and near?
Who gives a crap about starship rangers?
The greatest life to live
is found right here
Come on! Last one there is a delicious rotten egg!
Dirt eater!
Exoskeleton polisher!
I wanna build honeycombs!
The bug that ruins your picnic!
The fly on the wall!
We've all got a job to do
and it's how we all survive
by giving our life to the hive!
Cause the needs -
- of -
-the many bugs-
- they outweigh the few!
I know: today's the day -
Today's the day when we'll find what we're meant to do!
[buzzing]