Ah, hey Bug! What's the buzz?
Oh. Hey, Bumbely!
Just going to the over queen's slime pit.
Ah! Going to get your bug jobs, ha? Well, good luck!
Thanks!
Shake your leg, Bug!
Yep!
Mammals! We got mammals coming through!
Oh! Hey mister, where are you taking these mammals to?
Hey, that's a fine question, son.
Well, this guy over here is off to have a milking of his delicious fecal matter...
[Sound of pleasure]
... and this guy is off to the hatchery to have eggs implanted in its chest.
Huh! Oh wow!
Yep, ain't it the damndest? Say:
You boys are to consider a career in mammal wrangling. Bye!
[cute sounds from the mammals]
Did you guys know it takes over three tons of nourishment to fuel the bio processes that support our putrid hive?
I wanna make a difference! I wanna be nourishment!
Hey Bug!
Oh. ahm...
Hey Bugette...
oooh, I'll leave you two love bugs alone...
No! No! No!
Sooo - I just wanted to wish you luck today.
I bet you're gonna get a real great job from the over queen, like -
Dung roller.
Or dirt piler.
Or dung dirtier! Something real prestigious, like that.
I bet then you'll have a real parasite problem.
Pah! No Bugette. I've never been much of a ladies man.
[makes sounds like vomiting. Bug is slightly disgusted.]
Oh, Bug!
You make me laugh like nobody else!
You ought to make the nectar, cause you're so sweet.
Well, actually I don't think there's any bug job that I'm cut out for.
Don't worry! You'll be use to your job, whatever it is. Just look at me:
I was  assigned to carry around this mucus sack of carnivorous larva -
Oh, is that what that is?
[confirms]
And at first I thought it was the pits,
but now I'm just looking for that special bug to be there, when these little guys are ready to move into their pupa stage...
Well, I'm sure you'll find him some day, Bugette...
Maybe I already have...
Ahm...
Bug...?
I was wondering if, maybe later, after the ceremony,
you'd wanna... come over to my nest and I could tear off your head and let my larva devour your body...?
No, thanks Bugette.
Oh... okay.
Yeah.
Maybe some other time then...
Oh yeah...
Bye.
Bye...
I'm so - stupid!
[Bug is clearly relieved]
Bug!
Whoa!
What is your problem?
Why don't you have a go for Bugette?
She totally wants to
tear your head off and let her larva devour your body.
That's every bug's dream!
Well, it's not mine!
I'm sorry, Roach! Not everyone's as ladybug crazy as you!
It is true.
Deep inside my dorsal tube I'm - I'm just a hopeless romantic!
Ooh...
Yeah. But who'd ever go for a little bug like me?
The closest I'll ever get to a sexual experience is pollinating a flower!
[evil high pitched laughter]
Hey, you maggots, what's the rush?
Oh no! It's the mosquito brothers!
That's right: The mosquito brothers!
I'm Veeto.
I'm Neato.
And this is our sister Sweetheart.
Yo!
[With a very deep voice]
Oh, come on, Bug!
Let's get out of here. These guys are bad news!
Ou!
Ah... excuse me, gentlemen -
- and lady...!
Alright, but first you gotta pay the toll!
Ah, what's the toll?
Ah... How about some of that delicious blood?
My blood? No! I need that!
Oh, I'm full anyway.
Hey, come on, you guys. Let's go bust open a cocoon!
Trying peak in a butterfly when it's naked!
Say!
Come on, everyone! The ceremony is beginning! To the slime pit!
The queen will surely see I'm not like anyone else
She'll take one look and know my rightful calling
She'll understand
That I just can't
Be living my life for the hive
And I can finally -
Finally!
- know what it's like to be alive
I wanna be something that
can serve the greater good of our race
I'll do, whatever I can
To make our world a better place
If only I could get to outer space!
I wanna be a starship ranger
It doesn't matter at all where I'm from
So look out, starsip ragers
Cause here I am
Here I am
And here - I - come!
Dirt eater
Exoskeleton polisher
I wanna build honeycombs
The bug that ruins your picnic
It's all I wanna be!
Yes, yes, yes, yes. All bugs shall rise and keep buzzing to a minimum for the honorable, the beautiful and the terrible over queen!
Oh! She's even more beautiful and terrible than I heard.
[smells]
Huh! SMELL THOSE PHEROMONES!!!
Yes, now who shall be the first bug to step forward?
Wish me luck.
When deciding where to place me, I'd like your disgustingness to know
that playing some small part in the life cycle of the hive has always been my greatest ambition!
The over queen will consider this.
Hmmm... My decision:
Nourishment!
Yay!!! I'm making a difference! My Life for the hive!
[gets painfully eaten, according to the sounds]
Yum, yum, yum! More!
Now, who shall be the next little bug?
Oh! That's me, Bug.
Oh!
See you on the other side. Or in the over queen's belly if we both get nourishment.
Ohhhm...! And what's your name, son?
Ah... Roach, Mam.
And may I also add -
- that you are looking especially gooey today?
Hmmm, flattery will get you...
... everywhere!
My decision:
Queen impregnator!
Queen impregnator! No way!
Yes way! Now pick my most flatulent orifice and please burrow gently.
Oh! Bug! Bug! Look at me! I'm doing it! Ah! I'm really doing it! Okay, bye!
Bye...
Yes, now who shall stand before the over queen to receive the inescapable fate?
Oh, that's you, Bug!
No!...
Come on, Bug.
And what does your thorax desire?
[gulps]
Ahm...
I - I...ah... I...
I wanna be a starship ranger!
WHAAAAT???
What's that?
What's a starship ranger?
Am I a starship ranger?
I'm a starship ranger!
Quiet you! You're drunk.
No, I'm drunk!
SILENCE!!!
My decision:
Egg planter!
Egg planter?
Yes, egg planters shall report to the hatchery immediately.
But - but I don't wanna be an egg plan...
Silence, egg planter! And stand aside!
Yes...
Now, who shall step forw...
Wait a minute.
What - is that?