[Beep beep]
Mission log:
Officer February of the Galactic League Starship Ranger Corps, starship 15A2.
After - x - number of years in space we have reached the uncharted alien world and are now prepping for human colonization.
Upon arriving in an exploration pod it appears as though the planet's surface is - stable.
And there seem to be no signs of intelligent lifeforms - anywhere.
I will now analyze the air to see if it's breathable.
Hmmm, ah...
Contains copious amounts of - oxygen...
But...
I think, I should be okay.
I will now remove my helmet.
Let record show that I'm super ahead of schedule!
As the ship's head schienceofficer I will now scout the surrounding areas, looking for any and all signs...
[foreign sounds of animals]
Mission log:
I think I just heard a spooky noise.
And against my basic instincts and everything that I learned at the academy training camp,
I will now approach the noise for further investigation.
All right, noise:
On behalf of the 'Galactic League of Extraterrestrial Exploration' I demand you to show yourself!
Pikapi!
[Reference to: Pokemon]
Aaaaaaah!!!
You are the cutest thing I've ever seen!!!
Mission log: Total plot twist!
That creepy noise I thought I heard turned out to bee the  cutest effing noise I've ever seen.
Mission log: Get out! There are more of 'em!
My stars!
I seem to have landed in a field of these aminals...!
Hi! And what's your name?
Ararara!
Oh, I'm February!
Mission log: I've successfully made contact with the planet's indigenous lifeforms.
And they are ultra friendly!
In my professional opinion this planet is ready for human colonization by -
- this afternoon!
That is if that's all right with all you.
[cute sounds from the animals]
Oh, I'm so glad to hear it!
You see...
today is a really big day for me.
Can I tell you guys something?
See,
you might not belief this, but this is my first mission.
Yeah, it's my chance to prove to everyone back home, that - I am smart enough to get the job done.
Yeah.
And you know, back at the academy i finished last in my class.
But it wasn't my fault, I mean: How did they expect me to pass all those tests if I didn't know any of the answers?
But being here with all of you guys, it just really makes me feel like I'm doing something great.
Oh, hello.
Totoro!
[Reference to: My neighbor Totoro]
A...a...are you all right?
Aaaaah!
HOLY SHIT! ITS A BUG!!!!!
[Screams and laughter]
Hey! Was that thing what I thought that thing was?
I don't know.
But we better get it back to the boss. Come on!
So,
first day being a wrangler-bug, huh?
Yeah. I just got assigned this morning. [sighs]
Hey, why the long slime-hole?
Well, I just really had my dorsal tube set on being - nourishment.
Oh, I see...
Hey, well did you know that every egg in our swarm starts out by parasitically gestating in one of these mammals?
And who do you think wrangles those mammals?
Mammal-wranglers?
Ha!
That's right! The whole process starts with us!
So, you still think being a wrangler is lame?
No! Now I think it's kind of neat!
Yep, it sure is. Now come on, let's go!
Oh boy!
Starship 15A2! Come in, starship 15A2! I need evac, there are hostile icky bugs down here!
Ah! Where did it go?
Yeah! Where is it go?
Me thinks it went that away.
I'm with you!
All right, are you ready?
Now the first thing you're gonna wanna do is lay down a base code of slime.
Go for it...
FML!!!
[Short for: Fuck my life]
Hey mister, what are them weird noises coming out of it's mouth-parts?
Hey, we don't talk to them, we just wrangle them.
Now here's a tip:
Go ahead and secret a nice think layer of mucus onto the mammal's eyes to temporarily blind it.
We find this relaxes the mammals.
Help! Help me!
Wow, you're doing great!
Are you sure this is your first wrangle?
You're just saying that...!
Hey! I don't just say stuff!
Now come on, let's get her back to the hive.
Starship rangers!
I need the starship rangers!