Underneath these stairs
I hear the sneers and feel the glares
of my cousin my uncle and my aunt
Can't believe how cruel they are
and it stings my lightning scar
to know they'll never ever give me what I want
I know I don't deserve these
stupid rules made by the Dursleys
here on Privet drive.
I can't take all of these muggles,
but despite all of my struggles,
I'm still alive.
I'm sick of summer and this waiting around.
Man, it's September, and I'm skipping this town
Hey it's no mystery, there's nothing here for me now
I gotta get back to Hogwarts,
I gotta get back to school.
Gotta get myself to Hogwarts,
where everybody knows I'm cool.
Back to witches and wizards, and magical beasts,
to goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts.
It's all that I love, and it's all that I need.
At HOGWARTS, HOGWARTS, I think I'm going back
I'll see my friends, gonna laugh 'til we cry
take my Firebolt, gonna take to the sky
NO WAY this year anyone's gonna die,
and it's gonna be totally awesome
I'll cast some spells, with a flick of my wand
defeat the dark arts, yeah bring it on!
and do it all with my best friend Ron,
'cuz together we're totally awesome
yeah, and it's gonna be totally awesome!
Did somebody say Ron Weasley?
what's up, buddy?
so it took me so long to get here. I had to get some...
Floopowder, but we gotta get going,
come on, get your trunk, let's go!
Where are we going?
To Diagon Alley, of course!
Cool!
Come on!
Floopowderpower! Floopowderpower!
It's been so long, but we're going back
don't go for work, don't go there for class
As long as we're together -
- gonna kick some ass and it's gonna be totally awesome!
This year we'll take everybody by storm,
stay up all night, sneak out of our dorm
But let's not forget
that we need to perform well in class
if we want to pass our OWLS!
God, Hermione, why do you have to be such a buzzkill?
Because, guys, school's not all about having fun.
We need to study hard if we wanna be good witches and wizards!
I may be frumpy, but I'm super smart
check out my grades, they're "A's" for a start
what I lack in looks well
I make up in heart,
and well guys, yeah, that's totally awesome
this year I plan to study a lot
that would be cool if you were actually hot
hey Ron, come on, we're the only friends that she's got!
and that's cool
and that's totally awesome
yeah it's so cool, and it's totally awesome!
we're sick of summer and this waiting around
it's like we're sitting in the lost and found
don't take no sorcery
for anyone to see how
we gotta get back to hogwarts
we gotta get back to school
where everything is magic-cooooool
back to witches and wizards, and magical beasts
to goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
it's all that I love, and it's all that I need at
HOGWARTS, HOGWARTS
I think we're going back