Roooon!
You're supposed to take me to Madam Malkins,
and you used all those sickles mum gave you
for my robe fittings!
Who's this?
This is my stupid little dump sister Ginny,
she's a freshman,
Ginny, this is Harry.
Harry Potter,
He's Harry Potter.
Oh, you're Harry Potter!
you're the boy who lived!
Yeah, and you're Ginny.
It's Ginevra.
Cool. Ginny is fine.
Stupid sister
don't bother famous friend!
Do you guy's hear music or something?
Music? What are you talking about?
Yeah, someone's coming.
Someone's coming.
Cho Chang
Domo arigato
Cho, Chang
Gung Hey Fat Choy Chang
Happy Happy New Year,
Cho Chang
Oh! Who's that?
That's Cho Chang.
That's the girl Harry's totally been in love
with since freshman year.
Yeah, but he won't say anything to her.
Yeah, you never tell a girl you like her,
it makes you look like an idiot.
Conichiwa, Cho Chang.
It is good to meet you.
I am Ginny Weasley.
Bitch, I ain't Cho chang!
That's Lavender Brown!
Hey, hey it's alright. I'm Cho Chang ya'll!
She's totally perfect!
Yeah, too bad she's dating
Cedric Diggory though, ah?
Who the hell is Cedric Diggory?
What's that? Who is that guy?
Oh, Cho Chang!
I am so in love with
Cho Chang.
from Bangkok to DingDang
I sing my love aloud for Cho Chang!
I hate that guy!
I hate him!
So are we gonna get these robes or not?
Okay, alright let's GO!
God, sister!
Present your arm, nerd!
What, what, what...?
Indian Burn hex!
Oh, Crabbe and Goyle.
Are you okay?
Why don't you leave Neville Longbottom alone, ha?
Well well well if it isn't
Harry Potter.
You think all because you're famous
you can boss everyone around.
No, I just don't think it's cool for guys of your size
picking on guys like Neville, come on!
Oh well you know what I think?
I think glasses are for nerds!
We hate nerds!
And girls!
Wow! Well you asked for it!
You don't mess with Harry Potter,
he beat the dark Lord when he was a baby!
All right,
everyone just calm down.
Occulus reparo!
Wow, cool!
Now let's leave these big babychildish jerks alone.
Did someone say
Draco Malfoy?
What do you want, Draco?
Crabbe, Golyle,
be a pal ...[???]... and pay for my robes, will you?
So Potter!
Back for another year at Hogwarts, are you?
Maybe this year you'll wise up and hang out with the higher...[???]... wizard.
Listen,
Ron and Hermine are my
best friends in the whole world,
I wouldn't trade them for anything.
Have it your way.
Wait!
Don't tell me!
Red hair,
hand me down clothes
and a stupid complexion.
You must be a Weasley!
Oh my god, lay off,
Malfoy!
She may be a pain in the ass, okay?
But she's my pain in the ass.
Well, isn't this cute?
It's like a little loser family.
Hogwarts is really going to the dogs.
Luckily next year I'll be transfered to Pigfarts.
this year you bet I'm gonna get outta here
the reign of Malfoy is drawing near
I'll have the greatest wizard career,
and it's gonna be totally awesome
Look out world, for the dawn of the day
When everyone will do whatever I say
And that Potter won't be in my way,
and then I'll be the one who is totally awesome!
Yeah you'll be the one who is totally awesome.
Guys, come on! We're gonna miss the train!
Who knows how fast this year's gonna go?
Hand me a glass, let the butterbeer flow
Maybe at last, I'm gonna talk to Cho
Oh no, that be WAY too awesome
We're back to learn everything that we can
It's great to come back to where we began
And here we are, and alakazam!
here we go, this is totally awesome!
Come on and teach us everything you know
The summer's over and were itchin to go
I think we're ready for
Albus Dumbledore!
Oooooo
Aaaaaah
Welcome,
all of you to Hogwarts
I welcome all of you to school
Did you know that here at Hogwarts
We've got a hidden swimming pool?
Welcome, welcome, welcome Hogwarts
Welcome hotties, nerds, and tools
Now that I've got you here at Hogwarts
I'd like to go over just a couple of rules:
My name is Albus Dumbledore and I am headmaster of Hogwarts.
You could all call me Dumbledore.
Of course you could also call me Albus if you want a detention.
I'm just kidding.
I'll expell you if you call me Albus!
back to witches and wizards, and magical beasts
to goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
it's all that I love, and it's all that I need.
at HOGWARTS, HOGWARTS
Back to spells and enchantments, potions and friends
To Gryffindors!
Hufflepuffs!
Ravenclaws!
Slytherins!
Back to the place where our story begins
It's Hogwarts, Hogwarts!
I'm sorry, what's it's name?
Hogwarts, Hogwarts!
I didn't hear you kids!
Man, I'm glad I'm back.