Welcome to another magical year at Hogwarts.
And a very special welcome to my favourite student:
Mr. Harry Potter.
He killed Voldemort when he was just a baby.
He's even got that little lightning scar there to prove it.
And another very special welcome to our newest addition to Gryffindor:
Mr. Ginny...
Excuse me!
Mrs. Ginny Weasley.
Yeah, I'm a girl, and ahm...
I don't know... aren't we supposed to be sorted by the sorting hat?
Well ahm...
a funny thing happened to the sorting hat.
he actually got hitched with another piece of enchanted magical clothing.
So he and the scarf of sexual preference aren't going to be back until next year.
Basically I've just been putting anyone who looks like a good guy into Gryffindor,
anybody who looks like a bad guy into Slytherin,
and the other two can just go where ever the hell they want,
I don't even care.
Hufflepuffs are particularly good finders.
What the hell is a Hufflepuff?
Anyway,
it's time now for me,
to introduce my very good friend,
our own potionsprofessor:
Mr. Severus Snape.
O man!
Not Snape! I hoped, they had fired that guy.
What's wrong with professor snape?
Oh, Nothing. He's just uuuh EVIL!
Come on, Ron, he's really not that bad...
Harry Potter!
Detention!
For what?
For talking out of term!
Now before we beginn...
I'm going to give you all your very very first pop quiz.
Can anyone tell me what a Portkey is?
Ah yes, Mrs. Granger!
A Portkey is an enchanted object
that when touched will transport the one or ones who touched it,
to anywhere in the world decided upon by the enchanter.
Very good!
Now can anyone tell me what foreshadowing is?
Ah yes, Mrs. Granger!
Foreshadowing is a dramatic device, in wich an important plotpoint is mentioned early in the story
to return later in a most difficult way.
Perfect.
What's a portkey again ? I missed some of that.
Oh, a Portkey is something that when you touch it, that would transport you...
And remember a Portkey can be a sort of seemly harmless object.
Like...a football...
or... a Dolphin...
Professor?
Can like a person be a Portkey?
No that's absurd!
Cause then when a person were to touch themselves...
...they would constantly be transported into different places.
A person can however be a horcrux.
What's a... what's a horcrux?
I'm not even going to tell you, Harry. You'll find out soon enough.
Professor, what's the point of this quiz?
Oh no no. No point in particular.
Just important information that everyone should know.
Especially you!
Now, moving right along. There are four houses in all.
Gryffindor,
Ravenclaw,
Hufflepuff...
FIND!
...what?!?
And Slytherin.
Traditionell...
Traditionally points are given for good behavior and adducted for rule-breaking.
Example: Ten points from Gryffinfor!
What?!?
For Miss Grangers excessive baby fat.
Thanks Hermione.
Traditionally the house with the most points at the end of the year would win the house cup.
However, this year we're doing things a bit different.
Here to introduce you is our new professor of the dark arts:
Professor Quirrell!
Harry, what's wrong?
The house cup...
...a time honored tradition.
For centuries...
Go home, terrorist!
For centuries, the four houses of Hogwarts have competed for the honor and glory of holding the tile of house champion.
But where does this competition come from and what are the - roots of the tradition?
The house cup tournament began with the first generation of Hogwarts students.
That was a rhetorical question!
Granger, quit interrupting!
20 points from Gryffindor!
Thanks, Hermione.
As I was saying: when the tournament first originated, it was one of a completely different sort.
One champion from each of the four houses would complete a series of dangerous tasks.
Challenges, the winner would not only win the cup - he would also win the eternal glory.
Kinda like a house cup - ar no... like a triwizard tournament.
Yes... sort of like the triwizard tournament.
Except - no, not like that at all!
There are four houses. How can it be the TRIwizard tournament with FOUR teams?
Well, ah... professor, if I remember correctly, the house cup tournament was dispended after one semester...
...when one of it's students was killed during the first task.
Yes, it is very dangerous. But the rewards far outweigh the risks.
I - I don't think you heard me. I just said somebody died!
Hermine Granger, shut your unguardedly lopsided mouth and quit interrupting!
20 more Points!
Thanks, Hermine.
Come on! For the cleverest witch of your age, you really can't be a dumb ass somehow.
10 Points to Dumbledore!
Yes, yes - well, it will be very dangerous, but the winner will be remembered as a hero for ages to come.
And as the professor of defence against the dark arts, I believe that this - practical application is exactly what the curriculum needs to...
Achoo!
Gesundheit.
Did your turban just sneeze?
W...What? - No!
I could have sworn I heard a sneeze coming from your direction, but your mouth wasn't moving.
No,...that - that was simply a fart, excuse me.
Achoo!
I must be going.
I simply farted once more, excuse me!
With the new resurrected house cup, a champion from each house will be selected to compete.
So Snape: would you do us the honors, please?
Yes, headmaster.
First, from the Ravenclaw house:
Mrs Cho Chang!
Oh my god, I won! Who can it believe - I can't.
And next from Hufflepuff:
Mr. Cedric Diggory!
Well, I don't FIND this surprising at all.
I find it perfect. Now I can spend more time with my beloved boyfriend.
I'm glad as well, my darling!
And next, from the Slytherin house:
Draco Malfoy!
I finally beat you, didn't I, Potter?
What you think of that, ha? I'm the champion this time!
Draco would you sit down ya little shit! 'Champion' is just a title!
And finally from the Gryffindor house:
... oh my!
Isn't this curious?
The one person in all of Hogwarts whom I have grown a grudge against,
is suddenly in a tournament, where he may very well lose his life.
It...It's me! Apologies to my fellow Gryffindors right now, for I...
Sit down, you inarticulated bump!
It's Harry Potter!
That's really all, folks. The four Hogwarts champions: I want all of you to start preparing immediately, because the first task is in two month.
And it could be anything...
So let's get to it! Ha ha!
Cho Chang! Cho Chang! Cho Chang!
Draco Malf... Drac... hey...!