Harry, you've got this tournament in the bag.
I don't know man,
this Cedric Diggory is pretty awesome
NOT!!!
He sucks!
I'm totally gonna win! It's in the bag!
I don't know Harry...
Oh my God!
Hermione shut up!
Why do you have to rain
on everybody's parade?
Because, RON, this is dangerous!
Dangerous? Oh come on, Hermione,
how dangerous can it be,
especially for me?
Wha... You're not invincible, Harry!
Somebody died in this tournament!
Oh! I'm the boy that lived, not died!
What's the worst that can happen?
And...and I don't know about that
Quirrell-character.
You know, first he resurrects some
horrible ancient tournament,
then when he bumps into you your
scar starts to burn,
and you have to admit, there's something
really funky about the back of his head!
Come on, think about it: Professor Quirrell
is a Professor and who hires the Professors?
Dumbledore!
He`s the smartest, awsomest...
practical wizard...
Beautiful!
...beautiful wizard in the whole world,
why... Why would he possibly hire somebody
that's trying to hurt me?
Wha...wha... I mean, what about Snape?
Yeah, what about him?
He's hated you for years!
And he's hated your parents, too, Harry,
everybody knows that!
And he... he just so happens to pick
your name out of the house cup
out of  HUNDREDS,
if not FIVE possible Gryffindors...?
What a coincidence, who would doubt?
No, Harry, I don't think it is a coincidence!
When you defeated Voldemort
you made a lot of enemies.
Once you might not even know about that.
Alright Hermione, you're distressed,
you're saying that this tournament
is just one big plot to trying kill me?
I don't know... ah...MAYBE!
Anyway I just think it's dangerous,
and I don't think you should do it!
Alright Hermione, if it means
that much to you...
...I'll drop out.
Oh, thank you Harry!
Wait, wait, what?!?
The house cup? What about all
the eternal glory you'd win?
Come on!
Hey! Eternal glory?
Already got that.
Besides, Neville would be a great
Champion.
No! No! No!
I do not want schlong bottom
to be my champion!
Okay, all you have to do...
Oh, look there's Dumbledore!
Why don't you just talk to him now
and tell him that your dropping out?
Ah... Lis... Listen, Hermoine,
Dumbledore and I are really really cool,
we are super tight,
I don't want him to think I'm being lazy
or disrespectful.
So can you just tell...
why don't you tell him? Just tell him
I want to work on school or something.
Alright? Hey, you got this one, you're the best!
Alright.
Don't worry about it.
Dumbledore?
Yes, Granger?
I need to talk to you for a moment.
It's about the house cup tournament.
Ah, well first of all I think it's an awfull idea,
but second of all I don't think that
Harry Potter should compete.
Granger, why you always gottta be
such an old stick into my butt?
A great! Tell me why Harry Potter
should not compete.
Ah, because he... wants to study!
Granger, nobody studies at Hogwarts
except for you!
Ah... okay, well...
he wants to focus on the OWLs.
Why couldn't Harry have
told me this himself?
He thinks I'm cool.
We're tight!
Profess... I'm a really bad liar, okay...
I think it's a ruse!
I- I'm set up, and I even think Snape
might be trying to kill Harry Potter!
Severus Snape is one of the kindest,
bravest, gentliest, sexiest men
I have ever met.
Severus Snape is triying to kill Harry Potter
just about as much as he's trying to kill me!
Oh, hi Professor Dumbledore!
I happened to be in the kitchen
and I made you this...
delicious Sandwich.
Why, thank you Severus!
You see, Granger, how thoughtful!
Here you are, Professor.
Bomb apetit, I mean:
Bon apetit...
Ah... Is that sandwich ticking?
It looks like it's licking!
Finger licking good!
Professor, I don't think you should
eat that sandwich!
Why, Granger. Listen a state more often,
you might even get a sandwich out of that...
Granger, what the hell...
Granger, what are you doing?
It's all going exploding my sandwich!
I'm sorry, Sir!
Hey! Even if I did believe that Harry Potter
was in danger he has to compete!
You see that cup?
Yes.
It's enchanted!
Whosoever's name comes out of the cup
has to compete or the results would be bad.
What do you mean bad?
Well, try to imagine your entire life stopping
instantaneously and every more you and your body
exploding with the speed of light.
Total-protonic-reversall!
[Ghost Busters reference]
Yeah! So you see he has to compete, then...
Hermine, if it makes you feel any better,
the last guy that died in the tournament
was a Hufflepuff
so ahm...
I'll keep my eyes open and nothing's
gonna get past old Dumbledore.
Alright.
Now I gotta go make myself another sandwich.
Although I don't know how it's gonna be
as good as the last one.
The last one ticked!
Because it was a bomb...!?!
Harry, I'm so sorry but...
I think you gonna have to compete in the
house cup tournament.
But don't worry, I won't rest until I find out
what the first task is gonna be.
And I'll sabotage all the other Champions,
so you'll win by default.
Alright. Awesome!
Well, Isn't this touching!
Oh my god, just butt out, Malfoy!
Father and I have a bet, you know?
He says you won't last five minutes
in this tournament.
I disagree.
I say you won't last five minutes at Pigfarts!
What? Alright, Malfoy, what...
what is Pigfarts?
Oh, never heard of it?
Ha! Figures, famous Potter doesn't even know
about Pigfarts!
Malfoy, don't act if you don't wanna talk about it.
That's like the ninth time you mentioned Pigfarts!
What is Pigfarts?
Pigfarts is only the greatest
wizardringschool in the Galaxy.
That's why I'm being transfered next year.
Malfoy, I've never heard of that.
That's because Pigfarts...
... is on MARS!
Alright. Malfoy, you know we're trying to have
a conversation here so you just leave us alone.
Oh no! I'm not even here!
Anyway, I think we can find aut,
what the first task's, when Dumbledore...
DUMBLEDORE???
What an old coot! He's nothing like Rumbleroar!
RUMBLEROAR!!!
Anyway, I was saying...
Rumbleroar is the headmaster of Pigfarts!
He's a lion who can talk.
Malfoy, if you don't mind...
we're trying to have a conversation here it's not like...
you're not even eating, get out of here!
I can't help it if we can hear everything you say,
we're the only ones in here.
Just... Malfoy just get out of here. Please?
Where are we supposed to go???
ah, I don't know..., ah... Pigfarts!
Haha! Now you're just being cute!
I can't GO to Pigfarts!
It's ON MARS!
You need a rocket ship!
Do you have a rocket ship, Potter?
If you do: You know not all of us inherited
enough money to buy out the NASA
when our parents died.
Look at this!
Look at this... it's rocket ship Potter!
Oh! Starkid Potter,
Moon shoes-Potter!
Traversing the galaxy for intergalactic
travels to Pigfarts!
Alright, that´s it.
That's the most misguided way to try to
make me feel jealous!
I don't care if you make fun of me,...
...but dragging my parents into this
it's a whole other story!
Woah, not so fast, Potter! Crabbe! Goyle!
Oh shit, just...
Back off, nerd!
I'm scared, I'm scared!!!
Not so tough now, are you Potter?
Maybe you should hang out with someone better...
then that lolly gaging ginger and
his stupid mud-blood girlfriend!
Oh! That is it, Malfoy! Jelly-legs-jinx!
Oh come on!
Hey, it's not fair,our legs are jelly!
Take it back, Malfoy!
Take what back?
Take back what you said about your stupid
made-up space-school!
Yeah and all that stuff about Hermione
being my girlfriend. That's not even a little bit true.
And say you're sorry for calling me a you-know-what!
I'm sorry!
And you promise you'll never do it again?
I promise!
Right!
Now, next time we tell you to leave us alone,
you better do it!
Come on Harry, Ron, let's get out of here!
Besides, you already ate all my lunch!
Oh! Thanks, Hermione.
Yeah. Unjellify!
That was the most bad-ass-thing I've ever seen.
Too bad no one was here to see it.
It was like an outburst of aggression.
Wow! That sucked, royal Hippogriff!
We got beat by a girl. Who is a nerd!
I didn't mean what I said, you know?
Pigfarts is real!
Am I... am I bleeding?
Goyle?
No!
I thought maybe....
maybe it was a little bit...
Woah! Never been pushed down like that by a girl!
Maybe I shouldn't call her a mud...
Whatever!
I can't believe I couldn't figure out
the counter curse was just unjellify!
Right.
I'm not surprised.
Come on, let's go watch 'Wizard's of waverly place".