Fools! They're all fools.
They think they're safe.
They think they're back for another fun
year of learning shenanigans at Hogwarts.
Little do they know the danger that's
lurking right under their noses.
Or should I say: on the back of their heads?
Oh, I can't breathe in that damn turban!
I'm sorry my Lord. It's a necessary precaution.
For if they knew that you lived...
And when Harry Potter destroyed you,
your soul lived on...
Yes, that when my body was destroyed,
I was forced to live in the forbidden forest.
Eating bugs and mushrooms and, ugh!
Unicornblood
Until I found you and let you
attach yourself to my soul.
Yes. Nobody must know any of that.
Now, Quirrel... get me some water!
Now Quirrell...
Pour it in my mouth!
Your plan to infiltrate Hogwarts on the
back of my head is going swimmingly,
my liege!
Yes, yes, yes! I'm done with the water!
We must not have any more foul-up's
like tonight in the great hall.
I'm sorry, my lord. You sneezed.
I know that!
Get me some snazenex, you swine.
Wash that turban!
Tickles my nose.
Yes, my dark king.
Okay, just... relax with the dark king.
Okay?
I watch you wipe your butt daily.
You can call me Voldemort, we're there.
We've reached that point.
Yes... yes. Yes, my... Voldemort.
Now Quirrell:
Get us ready for bed!
We must be well rested, if we wish to kill Potter.
Tonight in the great hall - he was so close.
I could have touched him!
Revenge is at my fingertips, Quirrell.
I can taste it!
It tastes like...
Coolmints!
Bedtime is to ring, Voldemort.
Yes, excellent.
Well, ah... good night, Quirrell.
Good night.
Okay, okay, I can't do this!
You gotta roll over. I can't sleep on my tummy.
I always sleep on my back. I have backtroubles,
it's the only way I'm comfortable.
You roll over right now, or I'll...
eat your pillow!
You'll having a dream that you're
eating a giant marshmallow...
but really you'll wake up, and your favorite
goose feather pillow will be missing!
Fine, we'll compromise. We sleep on our side.
Okay, I guess I can do this.
Now, good night!
Good night, Quirrell.
Hey, Quirrell...
...how long have those robes
been on that chair?
I think they're from last night.
I just put them there for now.
Ah... you planing on putting them
in a hamper? What's your plan
for these?
I'm thinking I just leaving them there
for now and maybe put them away
in the morning, okay?
Ugh! ..No! No!
No, that's not okay!
I can't go to sleep knowing that there
are dirty clothes on that chair.
The chair is going to start to
smell like dirty clothes!
Look, I promised I'll put them away
in the morning.
You put them away RIGHT NOW!
I command you to get up and...
fold them at least!
Make it into a neat pile!
Look, if we're going to be in this situation
for a while, we're going to have to learn
to live with each other.
Now, I've been single for all of my life
and I have some habits.
And sometime, I leave laundry around.
Well, I believe, that everything has it's place.
Muggles have their place.
Mudbloods have their place.
And so do your cloths!
Namely: a dresser!
Well, aren't we an odd couple?
You won't sleep on your tummy
You won't sleep on your back
We're quite a kooky couple you'll agree
We share some hands and fingers
And yet the feeling lingers
We're just about as different as anyone can be
You like plotting a garden and I like plotting to kill
You think that you should rule the world,
I think books are a thrill
Sipping tea by the fires swell
Pushing people in is fun as well
I like folding all my ties
And you have no friends,
hey that's a surprise
I guess its plain to see
when you look at you and me
We're different
different
as can be
You're a sissy, a twat, a girl!
I'm the darkest of lords!
I'm the brightest professor here
I've won several awards
My new world is about to unfold
You got beat by a two year
I'll kill him this time through and through
Or you might just give him another tattoo
You really must agree
when you look at you and me
we're different
different
as can-
I'll rise again and I'll rule the world
But you must help me renew
For when our plan succeeds
Prevails!
Part of that world goes to you
When I rule the world I'll plant flowers
When I rule the world I'll have snakes
And Jane Austin novels
And goblins, and werewolves,
a fleet of dementors, and giants,
and thestrals, and all my Death Eaters!
When I rule the world!!
Hahaha!