Harry, don't you think you should trying
figure out what the first task
is gonna be?
You could actually die if you're not ready.
What?!?
Come on!
I mean: Can't you just do it for me?
Can't you just prepair all my stuff for me?
What are you doing right now?
I'm planning your potions-assay.
Oh, well do that first because
that's due tomorrow.
But after that... after that can you
prepare for the first task, please?
Thank you! You are the BEST!
Yeah.
You got it.  Thanks Hermoine.
Hey Ginny, come here! I wanna show
you something, come here.
Hey, Harry Potter!
Listen, I wanna play this song
that I'm working on.
I met this girl I really really like.
I wanna let her know that she's
really special.
So I just wanna know what you think.
Just for the purpose's of now because
I'm still working on the lyrics. I'm putting
your name where her name should be.
But I don't think it's really gonna work out,
because... well, the music'll show.
You're tall and fun and pretty,
you're really really skinny...
Ginny!?!
I'm the Micky to your Minnie,
your the Tigger to my Winnie,...
Ginny!
I wanna take you to the city,
gonna take you out to dinny, Ginny.
You're cuter then a guinea pig,
Wanna take you up to Winnipeg.
That's in Canada!
Ginny, Ginny, Ginny---
You know what? This isn't working.
It sounds horrible with your name.
...[???]... But I don't know:
How does it make you feel?
Emotionally?
Wow!
Wowy! Harry Potter!
Don't you think it could...ah...
I don't know...
... make a girl fall in love with me?
Oh, I think it already has...
Awesome! 'cause it's for Cho Chang!
Oh yeah...She, she's beautiful...
What, are you nuts?
Beautiful!?! More like
Super-mega-foxy-awesome-hot!
She's the hottest girl I've ever met.
She's far more attractive,
far more appealing,
far more instinct than any girl that I know.
In my near group of...of friends.
She's far more interesting
than any girl that I know!
Hi Neville!
Move, move, move, move,...
00:02:19,750 --> 00:02:21,320
Awesome.
Hey Harry, what's up?
So, I was just off stage hanging out with Hagird,
and I was... ah,I saw these delivery-wizards,
bringing giant cages into the dungeons,
I don't know, what that's for...
Giant cages?
I bet whatever is in those cages
has something to do with the first task!
Harry, we have to find out what it is!
Hey! Hey, guys!
Chill!
I'm busy!
No no no no no no no!
Guys, now listen:
This could be a matter of life and death!
What does it matter,
because it's after hours, okay?
So, we can't leave Gryffindor house,
We'll probably get in trouble if we do.
and even if we do...
schlong bottom over there
will probably tell on us.
Neville won't tell!
Oh, yes! I certainly will!
Damn. What are we gonna do?
It's simple guys: The cloak!
Of course!
The cloak!
Harry, what cloak?
Shut up!
...[???]...
...I got a... I got a present last year...
oh, bye Neville!
I got a present last year.
First year at Hogwarts. And, ah,...
That cloak...
It was left to me by my dad.
My dad is dead, my father is dead.
I have a dead/ dad father... [pun]
[???]...my invisibility-cloak!
Oh wow!
Oh boy, wowy, Harry Potter!
You have an invisibility-cloak!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Do you know what I
would do if I had an invisibility-cloak?
I would...ah... I would kick weiner dogs.
I would pretend to be a ghost,
and I would scare ...[???]... people.
I'd use it to avoid ever having to
face my reflexion in the mirror.
Well, actually I was gonna to say, that
I would use it to fake my own death
and watch people cry at the funeral.
Okay, anyway, let's get outta here before
Neville comes back from the bathroom,
let's get outta here.
Wow wow wow wow wow,
where do you think you're going?
With you guys...?
No, no! No way!
No kid sisters allowed, okay?
Besides, there's only enough room
under this cloak for two people, so ah...
Come on, Hermione! Come on...
The way his hair falls in his eyes
makes me wonder if he'll
ever see through my disguise
and I'm under his spell
everything is falling
and I don't know where to land
everyone knows who he is
but they don't know who I am
Harry
Why can't you see
what you're doing to me?
I've seen you conquer certain death
and even when you're just standing there
you take away my breath
and maybe someday you'll hear my song
and understand that all along
there's something more that I'm trying to say
when I say
Harry
Why can't you see
what you're doing to me?