Master! Master!The shipments
for the first task of the tournament
have just arrived!
Yes, I know, Quirrell.
I hear everything that you hear.
Isn't it wonderful, master?
We've made sure, that Harry Potters
Name was drawn from the cup
and soon he will be ours.
Yeees!
It's really happening, isn't it, Quirrell?
You know, with the plan going so well,
I feel like maybe we should celebrate.
What do you say, Quirrell?
How's about we go out?
I hear it's Karaoke-night
down at the Hogshead.
I don't know.
I've all these papers to grade and
I've been giving so much attention to this
revenge plan that I'm really behind.
Ah, come on, Quirrel!
You've been working so hard all year!
You deserve a night off!
But the papers!
Oh, just give them all B Minuses
and be done with it!
Now, that's evil!
Ha, yeah thanks! I am the dark Lord!
Come on! Just a few drinks...
And we try to pick up some chicks.
I wouldn't know what to say.
I'm no good at that.
Come on, it will be fun!
You'll just move your lips
and I'll do the talking.
Aaaaahm...
Quirrell!!!
Man!
Listen!
I may just be a parasite
on the back of your head,
slithery devouring your soul,
every time you take a breath,
but I can see, that your're too good a guy,
not to have a bit of fun once in a while!
You deserve this!
Well, if you put it that way, then...
Yeah! Let's just go wild tonight!
Haaaaa! That's the spirit, Quirrell!
Put on a fresh pair of wizard-shorts
and grab your tunic!
Quirrell, we are gonna get you laid!
Seriously man,
back, when I had a body...
Wuh!...I had mad game with the bitches!
Just ask Bellatrix Lestrange!
Wow ah...
this cloak isn't as big as it used to be.
Shhh! Someone's coming!
Did you just hear something?
No. Only quiet.
Maybe...one...raindrop.
It's no matter.
Tell me, Goyle:
Who, do you think,
is the ugliest girl in school?
Ah...?
Oh! Buckbeak! For sure.
Crabbe?
Ahh, Winky, the House elf!
Good one!
Yeah!
Do you know who I think
the ugliest girl in school is?
That Hermoine Granger.
Do you know, what I'd give her
on a scale of one to ten,
with one... one would be the ugliest
and then ten is beauty?
I would give her:
an eight!
An eight point five!
Or a nine.
NOT, not over a nine point eight!
Because there's always
room for improvement.
Not everyone's perfect, like me!
That's why I'm holding up for a ten!
Because I'm worth it!
[Shampoo advertisement spoof]
Come on, let's go.
Wow, those ones are jerks!
Alright, forget them.
Now where did you say you saw
those creates being delivered?
Well, I think they were being delivered
to the auditorium, so they should be at
the end of this hallway and to the left.
Look!
A goat?
A goat? Oh my god,
I've to fight a goat.
I hope that I can do that morally...
And the goats have all been send for
feeding-time, headmaster?
Feeding-time?
Dragons don't wanna be fed,
they wanna hunt!
[A famous movie about Dinosaurs]
Did he just say DRAGONS?
Did you just say:
I must have, because anybody else
hiding in this room would have known
to have shut up.
Potter!?!
Headmaster, do you really think it's wise
to have children fight dragons?
No Snape, I don't think it's wise to do
anything anymore.
Like, here I am alive and well today and
I could very well be killed by you tomorrow.
Well, that's absurd!
Severus, let's go to bed.
Have you ever seen my room?
I've got some pretty kickin' Posters
on my wall...
Well, I am rather tired.
Oh man, to fight a dragon, this is bogus!
How can I fight a dragon?
I'm just a little kid!
Well, maybe it won't be that bad, Harry.
Maybe, maybe you'll just have to fight
like Mushu from Mulan.
I don't know, maybe like
Puff the magic dragon or so...
Ron, this is serious, okay?
Harry could die!
Now look there's still the time alright?
If we just can figure out a plan.
Okay. well, we should quiet do that back
in the common room. Where's... Wait,
where's the invisibility cloak?
well, I threw it over on that magical
walking chair over th... Oh, crap!
Oh! That's... That's gonna be an issue...