I thought walking home drunk
was hard before...
We should have realized, that...
that with both of us drinking into one belly
we get twice as drunk!
Hey Quirrel!
QQQQQQUUUUUIIIIRRRRRRRRRREEEELLLL!
You remember the girl you were talking to?
Yeah.
I was talking to her sister on MY side...
Oh, so that's why she freaked out
when we stood up!
She doesn't have even known that
we were just one person!!!
You know I haven't had... I haven't had
this much fun since the only headless Nicks
d... Nicks  deathday party of '91.
I haven't had this much fun since ah...
yeah, well shit, I can't remember
I ever had any such fun...
You never have fun... ever?
Doing...doing anything?
Maybe that's why you're so evil...
Yeah, "MAYBE".
definitely due to the fact that muggles and
mud-bloods make me sick to my stomach,
but ah...
Yeah, I guess you could be right....
oh yes...That's kind of funny...
What is it, Voldemort?
Oh, it's just that I never...
I never ever really ever...
I never really ever ever... really ever...
... considered another reason for me being so evil,
you know, 'cuz normally I just, ah...
...I just kill people that try to get me to open up,
you know?
OOPS!
But it's... it's kind of nice to just, ah...
kind of nice to just talk.
Yeah...
You know, I have to admit,
I was kind of nervous, when you first demanded,
that you attach yourself to my soul.
Yeah, I c... I could sense that...
Well, like now I think it's... it's kind of cool!
It's like having a really close roommate,
or... or even...
Yeah, like a slave!
Like a... like a deatheater!
No man... It's like...
having a friend!
I've never had a friend before...
Well, looks like you've got one now!
Who would have thought that at the beginning
of this year, we'd feel like that for each other!
I guess everything is different
between us now, ah?
I guess it's plain to see,
when you look at you and me:
We're different,
different
as can be.
We simply guarantee,
when you look at you and me:
we're different, different as can be.
It's a comedy of sorts ,
when you're bound to Voldemort!
And I'm happy as a squirrell,
Long as I'm with Mr. Quirrell!
We'll lead 'em to the slaughter and we'll murder
Harry Potter, we're different
different,
different, different as can...