The Hogwarts champions shall now
enter the champions tend,
in preparation for the first task!
Oh, man I can't believe I've gotta skip
lunch period for this stupid task.
Okay, Harry. Today is the day!
The day you fight the dragon.
Now, did you read those notes that I
wrote for you on dragons?
No.
What? Why not?
Are you kidding me? They're so boring!
So you... you didn't read them?
You didn't prepare at all?
You're not prepared at all?
Well, no. But at least
I have my wand...
...ahm...
I dropped my...
Here!
Hey! Cool! You're the best!
Harry, just... please don't die today!
I don't wanna see my best friend
get eaten by a dragon!
Hey, relax, okay?
Save the tears for my funeral.
So, tell me more about this pigfarts!
I FIND it to be very interesting.
Well, while you're there you have to
wear your space suit at all times,
'cause there's no atmosphere on mars,
so if a single docking bay door opens,
you'll probably die.
Oh my. How dreadful!
Well, the good news is:
If you're a good enough student,
Rumbleroar let's you ride around
on his back.
And...And he is the headmaster lion?
Who can talk!
Cool!
Well, hello Harry.
How are you feeling today?
Hi Cedric. Trying... to stay positive.
Oh, good. I', happy to FIND
you this well.
Mrs. Granger?
Hello...
Sugar pie?
My darling?
Was that a kiss for good luck?
No, that was just for being so
cotton-picking cute.
This one's for good luck!
I hate that guy!
It's okay, Harry. You gonna be great!
Oh! God! Granger,
I thought you are a Boggart!
And a terrifying one!
And what the hell are you doing
in the champions tend? Get out of here!
Ten more points!
Thanks Hermione!
Are you kids ready to fight a DRAGON???
Of course you are! You're just children!
What the hell am I thinking?
Outside of this tend are thousands upon
thousands of screaming fans! They'll either
gonna be cheering for YOU - or the dragon!
But either way they're gonna
make some kind of noise.
So, in order for the
selection process to be fair,
I am going to RANDOMLY select a cardboard
cut out size version of the dragon
you'll be facing.
For you, Cedric:
Puff the magic dragon.
Figment - the imaginary dragon.
The reluctant dragon.
And for you, Potter:
The Hungarian Horntail!
The most terrifying thing ever seen
in your whole life!
Okay, there are no more complains, I...
Wait a second! Wait a second!
This is terrifying!
Those are the cutest things
I've ever seen...
This thing is horrifying!
Excuse your imagination.
My god, this competition is gonna suck!
All these dragons are wimps!
Accio double stuffed. [cream]
OH, MY GOD! A MONSTER!
Is that yours?!
Yeah!
Oh my god! It's awesome.
Let me hold it.
Oh my god, this thing is terrifying!
I hope the real thing is smaller!
Grrrrr!
Roaches what are you gonna do?
I don't know I'm not cut out
for this kinda...
Ron! Ron, you can't be in here!
This is the champions tend...!
Mrs. Granger!
Ron! Ron, you can't be in here!
This is the champions tend...!
What the devil are you doing
in the champions tend?
Ten points from Gryffindore!
Oh, thanks Hermione!
Good luck, buddy! Bye Snape!
Bye!
Cedric Diggory:
Now is your chance to face - your dragon.
All right, fellows. Wish me luck!
I believe in you!
That's all I needed to hear!
Hey Malfoy, tell you what:
I'll let you switch dragons with me. I'll give
you the chance to switch dragons with me!
I give you that opportunity.
Hmm, let me think about... no!
Come on! I'll - I'll give you my "Gushers".
Oh, no. No. I have a "fruit-by-the-foot".
Cho Chang, your dragon awaits!
Well, I can't IMAGINE
if this would be very hard?
Then I IMAGINED it won't be!
Come on! Tell you what: I'll throw in my
teddy bears with "Gushers" So you can
make a littler Gusher-teddy bear sandwich.
All right, you throw in that pack of Bugles
and you got yourself the deal.
Absolutely not!
Draco Malfoy...
Professor Snape, is there a way that I can
kinda forfeit or switch dragons? Or maybe...
What?!? What are you doing?
I'm protecting you, Potter!
Welsh Greenbacks can't STAND the taste
of Hans tomato ketchup.
But I'm not fighting a Welsh Greenback.
I'm fighting a Hungarian Horntail.
Oh, silly me!
Hans tomato ketchup is what
Hungarian Horntails like best of all.
Good luck, Potter!
And now Harry Potter will battle the terrifying
Hungarian Horntail, the most terrifving thing
you've ever seen in your whole life.
It should be noted, that this particular dragon
has not been fed in two weeks!
Come on, Harry!
You can do it, Harry!
Think positive!
Oh my god!
Accio Guitar!
Hey dragon
you don't gotta do this
Let's reevaluate our options
throw away our old presumptions
'cause really
you don't wanna go through this
Im really not that special
the Boy Who Lived is only flesh and bone
the truth is in the end
I'm pretty useless without friends
In fact I'm alone
I spend my time at school
trying to be this cool guy
I never even asked for
I don't know any spells
Still manage to do well
But theres only so long that can last for
I'm living off the glory
of some stupid children's story
that I had nothing to do with
I just sat there and got lucky
so level with me buddy
I can't defeat thee
so please don't eat me
And all I can do
is sing this song for you
Lalalalala
Rarararara
You never asked to be a dragon
I never asked to be a champion
We both just jumped on the band wagon
but all we need is guitar jamming
Lalalala...
Rarararara...
Goodnight Dragon!
One! Two! Three! I've beaten the dragon!