Attention all Hogwarts students!
Tonight is our Annual Yuleball.
so please make ready to pick up your
Yule-ball-wreath
and give it to that special someone.
Ah! Ginger!
Oh, hey Harry Potter...
Hi Ginny.
Fancy seeing you here, ah?
Ah, well, it's the cafeteria, so, yeah...
Ah...so, ah... the Yuleball is coming up...
Yeah, I know it is... very very soon, yeah...
Ahm... oh, were you thinking of
going with anybody?
I was. I was actually just waiting for the
right time to ask somebody. I think...
I think the time's about now, so if...
... if you have something to say, just...
get it out, 'cuz...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhh
Oh, is this for me?
Oh Ginny, how did you know that I needed a
wreath, so I can ask Cho Chang?
You're the best!
Oh, Harry Potter...!!!
Just... forget it!!!
Alright, I will!
Cool!
Hey! Hey, Cho Chang, listen... ahm:
I know the Yuleball's coming up,
and I was wondering if, ah...
...maybe you wanted to go with me,
BUT just in case you're kind of...
on the fence about it,
you should know that I play guitar
and that I conquered the
dragons heart with it,
so I think, I conquer yours.
You're tall and fun and pretty,
you're really, really skinny
Cho Chang!
You're the Mickey to my Minnie
I'm the Tigger to your Winnie,
Cho Chang!
You're cuter than a guinnie pig,
Wanna take you up to Winepeg
That's in Canada!
Oh, Cho Chang!
ChinaChinaChina - Cho Chang!
Whatever...
My oh, Harry Potter!
Bless your heart!
But...ah...I have to say no.
That young strapping boy Cedric Diggory
already asked me and I just go with him.
Sorry...
Come on, girls! Let's go show the
Moaning Myrtle our ball gaunts
and make fun whether she can't go!
Hey there, good buddy!
How're you doing?
Okay...
Is that a yule-ball-wreath?
Yeah...
Who you gonna ask?
Well, I've asked Cho Chang, but she
turned me down for Cedric Stupery!
Oh my god, they're going together?
That's so great! I love him so!
They are so a cute couple...
No! No!
Oh my god, they're going together?
That's so great! I love him so!
They are so a cute couple...
...I hate him! I hate him so much!
Oh my god, he pisses me off...! Wow!
Oh man, that sucks, dude.
I don't know why she turned you down,
you're like the coolest guy in school!
I know, I don't get it! I play guitar,
I'm Harry Potter! I'm awesome!
You want some cheese-twigs?
Yeah.
I don't get it man.I mean I guess
I will just go as stag, ah?
I'll probably go stag, too.
The only two girls that I know,
that don't have dates already,
are Ginny...
...and Hermione.
Oh my god!
I'm not going with my stupid sister!
And I think of Hermione as sister.
So that's out!
We are in such a puzzle.
Hi, look at these strapping young men.
Hi, Neville.
Hey, Neville:
Want this Yule-ball-wreath?
Well, yeah, when you're willing to part
than I will take this for you.
Hey, Ron: Let's go hang out with Hagrid.
He can teach us how to dance
and we're getting our dress-ropes.
That can only lead to desaster and hilarious.
Let's go!
Give that plant, nerd!
Ahhh!
Oh, Goyle rules!
So anyway,
It was RELUCTANT enough at first...
[The reluctant dragon]
....But I lured it out of it's cage
with an upside down...[???]...
And I soed it with my "Fruit-by-the-foot" ...
and deheaded it with a quick slicing-charm.
Bloody fool.
What?!? Goyle?
What are you doing with that wreath?
Would you going to ask someone
to the Yule-ball?
N...n..no!
Dancing's for nerds!
And pretty girls!
Right.
Do you know who the last girl I'd
have asked to the Yule-ball would be?
That Hermione Granger.
Not even if we were the last
two people on earth...
and she looked absolutely stunning
in her ball-gaunts...
and ever time I looked at her,
I got butterflies in my tummy...
Not even then.
Ugh!
They don't even have dances at Pigfarts.
All the noise would disturb Rumbleroars
slumbering cubs.
Dancing is for Pansies.
Ey you there, what's your name?
Pansy.
Perfect!
You're going to the Yule-ball with me.
You see that dragon?
Well, it was reluctant enough at first,
but I lured it out of it's cage...
Yule-ball-decorating-crew!
Does the Yule-ball-decoration-crew
coming through?
Last minute decorations.
Hu-ha!
My Lord! The Yule-ball has finally arrived
and I've brought the key.
Yes, I KNOW Quirrel.
I HEAR everything you HEAR!
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have snapped.
I'm just nervous, that's all.
Nervous?
No.
Why?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Hey! It's just me.
You can tell me ANYTHING.
You know that.
Yeah, yeah. You're right, you're right.
I'm just nervous because we've been
planning this night for so long,
and... I want everything to go perfectly,
you know?
Don't worry.
We've mapped out everything.
We've anticipated every little problem
and ...[???]... for it.
We've even prepared what you're
going to say to Potter when you see him.
So just cool down.
Relax.
By the end of the night you'll have
your revenge and your body back.
You're right, you're right, I'm being...silly.
But..uhm...
I..you know, I...
Quirrell, over the last year I....
I've really grown attached to you.
No pun intended.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But hey! We'll still hang out.
Just because we won't be attached,
doesn't mean we'll be two completely
different people.
No pun intended.
No, no! Of course not! Of course not...
Hey, Quirrell. We should make plans.
Evil plans?
Oh,...ah...
No. Casual plans.
Like...ahm..
...you go rollerblading on Saturday,
and then, ahm...
see a movie at night.
Yeah. It'll be great because we'll both
be able to watch it for a change.
Yeah, yeah...
I bet it'll be nice to sleep in our own beds.
Not have someone behind you
all the time...
And have the privacy
of my old life back again...
The solitude...
Now,
whatever happens tonight, man, it's...
It's been a blast!
Yeah. One crazy year!
Yeah!
Hey!
Promise we'll go rollerblading
and see that movie!
Oh, man. I promise!
Okay.
Qurrell: Let's go plant that key and split.
Pun intended!
Oh, hi Professor Quirrell.
What on earth are you doing
in the great Daaancehaaall?
Just moments before the daaaance?
Just... decorating for the Yule-ball.
Last minute decorations.
Just one final Touch.
A ladle?
A very special ladle for a very special night
for a very special punch.
And what's so special about it?
Let's just say there's... squirt in it.
Squirt?!?
Is that not the favorite drink
of one Harry Potter?
Is it? I had no idea!
Well, we better be going...
We?!?
I! I better be going.
Loud music hurts my ears!
Okay, well, I'll see you later then.
Or maybe you won't!
Or maybe I will!
Excuse me.
No, excuse me. It was my fault.
Hey Severus!
Oh, ah Headmaster!
What are you doing here?
You're getting some punch, are you?
Oh, no, no! There's Squirt in there!
Only Harry Potter likes that hog shit.
I'll stick to my Red Bull.
Thank you very much.
Well, good night, headmaster.
Serverus, I...
I saved this last dance for you.
[Oldie: Save the last dance for me]
Well, I would, headmaster, but you see:...
Well, an old friend is comig back
into town tonight...