Hey Ron.
Hey,what's up there? How's it going?
Have you seen Hermione anywhere?
No I haven't.
Shit.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
It's just, you know...
I heard Parvati Patil telling Padme Patil,
she'd seen Hermione in the girls
Locker room before,
crying her eyes out on the bathroom stall.
Why?
I don't know, is that not the saddest
thing you ever heard?
I mean, I don't know, it's just...It was ...
[???]... that one day Hermione would realize
that no guy would ever like her.
You know, If it's  her obnoxious personality,
her ugly face,
her misshaped body...
you know, it's just... I don't know, I think
that she'd getting at least one night
of happiness,
before she realized she's gonna be going
old alone, you know?
Hey, are you two over here
talking about Granger?
Malfoy get out of here,
t's none of your business. Why don't you go
dancing with pansy or something.
Hey! Go get me some punch!
Okay.
Oh, I should tell you there's squirt in it.
Squirt?!?
Never mind, I'll STAY dehydrated!
Go powder your nose or something.
I just fixed my make up a little while ago.
Trust me: You need more powder!
She's a pain in the ass, right?
So anyway:
Those stranger's not 'round here?
Probably the better doing! No one would be able
to keep their plummers and peach's down with
that ugly mug of her's dancing about!
Why don't you just give her a break for once,
okay Malfoy?
Why defending her, Weasley?
Have a crush?
No...
No, why all the insults, Malfoy?
Covering up a crush?
Oh!  Right, right! Like I'd ever have a crush
on that stupid...
Oh my GOSH!
She look's so beautiful, bless her heart!
Here I am face to face with a situation
I never thought I'd ever see.
strange how a dress can take a mess,
and make her nothing less than
beautiful to me.
It seems like my eyes
have been transfigured
something deep inside has changed
they've been open wide,
but hold that trigger
this could mean. Danger.
I'm falling in love,
falling in love,
I could be falling in love,
falling in love
with Hermione Granger!
WHAT? What the hell is this?
YOU expect me to sing about her?
I don't care about her .
it's just a little make up
Draco, wake up!
I'm mistaken!
she -  is the hottest girl I've ever seen.
now -  because she's like a girl
I've never seen.
don't know why -  I'd ever be so mean.
this could mean DANGER!
I'm falling in love,
falling in love,
I could be falling in love,
falling in love
With Hermione Granger!
I WANNA LET HER KNOW
I FEEL SO QUEEZY
BUT I CAN'T LET IT SHOW
SHE'D LAUGH, POOR WEASLY.
Come on, Ron.
Come on,...Draco.
You gotta let it go! You gotta let it go!
WHAT? What the hell is this?
Here I am face to face with a situation
I want to sing about her
sing about her.
I never thought I'd ever see.
I want to make up
Strange how a dress
can take a mess,
Granger, wake up
I've been mistaken.
and make her nothing less than
beautiful to me.
She - is the hottest girl I've ever seen.
It seems like my eyes
have been transfigured
Now - 'CAUSE she's like a girl
I've never seen.
something deep inside has changed
Don't know why -  I'd ever be so mean.
they've been open wide,
but hold that trigger
This could mean DANGER!
I'm falling in love,
falling in love,
I could be falling in love,
falling in love
With Hermione Granger!
Danger!