Oh my god, I can't believe it.
What?
I just can't... I can't believe she's dancing
with ever guy but me, That is so...
that's so stupid, that's so...
Why do you even care about it?
I don't! I don't care.
I don't care and that's what
I'm gonna go up and tell her!
I'm gonna go and say:
I don't care what you do!
And she's gonna feel so damn stupid.
She is gonna feel like such an idiot!
Listen Ron, you drank like a real jerk,
maybe you should take it easy
on the Butterbeer.
No! No.
Hey, Hermine! Hey, you look great!
You look wonderful!
Hey Guys!
Thanks! Yeah, you know, I... I used to
think looks weren't important and now I think
they are more important than anything!
It's just, I'm having so much fun,
dancing with everyone...
Wow, Hermione, when did you
become so shallow, when?
What's wrong with you, Ron?
Nothing! Nothing's wrong with me!
Why don't you just go ask Longbottom
to dance, ha? Go do it!
You know what? Maybe I will!
That sure hurts. Not so good...
Wait a second! Wait a hot second!
I know what's going on here!
You've got a crush!
Alright. Ron, listen... listen to me now:
Cool advice: this may sound crazy,
but girls don't really like it, when you're angry
at them, much less when you shout at them.
Now maybe you should just go over there
and tell her how much you care about her,
okay?
Maybe she'd ask you to dance.
Wha...No, no!
'cuz then she'd know I liked her!
And you always said, that you don't tell
a girl you liked her. 'Cuz it makes you
look like an idiot.
...[???]....
It's something you have to do!
...[???]...
Okay? And what have you got to lose?
Look at our robes!
If we dressed like this in the muggle world,
we would get our ass's kicked!
You have nothing to lose,
ABSOLUTELY nothing.
She probably wants to dance with you
just as much as you wanna dance with her.
You just gotta...
You... you just gotta...
give her... a chance!
You ...[???]...that you can see before.
You gotta go and maybe find something
special, and...
...the whole time you just really hadn't
the guts to ...
...say anything.
Harry, where are you going?
I'm still mad and sad.
Hold on!
HP is going to take his own advice now.
Hey Ginny.
Oh... Hey, Harry.
Can I sit down?
Ah...yeah...sure...
Soooooooo...ah...
How is Hogwarts?
You know, it's okay.
Actually I was really excited
to come here, but...
now that I'm here I'd...
I just don't think I belong.
Oh yeah, I totally know, what you mean.
Ah, no. No.
For you're Harry Potter.
Yeah I know. Like for 11 Years I was this dumb
kid they got the crap kicked out of me under
a staircase, now it's like: you're a wizard!
You have all these powers!
And everything's on cool all the sudden.
It's weird, it's kind of isolating! Ahm, ahm...
No, I'm sorry, now I'm complaining
about being famous, I'm sorry.
No, I understand. It's...it's...
like when you first got here and nobody
wanted to get to know you because they
thought that they knew you already, but...
eventually you'll find people that'll want
to get to know you for the real you!
Now Ginny, I feel like I already have found
these people and I won't take it for grant.
So tell you what: Come on!
Do you wanna dance?
It's the whole point of the evening.
I gotta warn you:I learned all my best
dance moves from Hagrid, so...
I'm not that great.
Oh, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Wow! Harry Potter!
I don't care what anybody says.
You're the best dancer that ever was!
I've a confession to make, Ginny.
These shoes right here...
... are magical enchanted dancing shoes.
Oh wowy, Harry Potter!
I'm messing with you!
I'm just awesome at dancing.
AAAAHH!
Outch!
Hey!
Alright, I tell you, when you really danced
with Neville it's when you crossed the line,
okay?
Take this. Beat it! Get out of here!
Ah!
Come here. COME HERE!
Ah! Why are you being so mean to me?
I'M NOT BEING MEAN!
Ow! Yes, you are!
You know, every day everyone is trying to
put me down, and on the one day I actually
feel like a perfect you're trying to ruin it!
Oh shit...!
What is wrong with you, Ron?!? Come on...
Weasley!
The lady said NO!
Not - YOU - too!
You know what, I'm so sick of both of you!
I HATE YOU BOTH!!
What did you say to her?
Nothing!
I'm bleeding!
Look at this!
Ginny... Ginny, I'm feeling kind of dizzy.
Maybe we should stop spinning.
It's from all this spinning, ha?
We have stopped spinning.
Wait! No! No, no, no, no!
I can't... I can't do this...you're...
You're Ginny Weasley, your're my best friend's
little sister, you're Ron Weasleys sister!
I c... I...I'm sorry, Ginny, I can't do it!
I'm sorry!
Hey Cho! Hey, hey, come on, dance with me!
I'm Harry Potter, let's go!
Excuse me, I believe I was
dancing with the lady!
Yeah and I'm...cutting in!
Well, I FIND that to be very rude!
Alright, Cedric, why don't we FIND out,
what the lady has to say about it?
Oh boys, this is no need
to fight a little on me!
But by the ways: Cedric thinks you
cheated on the dragon's task...
CHEATED? Are you kidding me?
that thing was trying to eat me!
I was in it's mouth!
Exactly! But what aren't in there?
I'd like to FIND out!
Alright, that is it Diggory,
we're dueling, let's go!
Oh, Godderics Hollow.
All this excitement is making me thirsty!
Oh, Cho! I'll get you something to drink!
I'll get you some punch!
No! I'll get the punch!
No, I'll get the punch!
Fine! Have the punch!
[Pun: punch = Drink / punch = boxing move]
You did it!
Cedric Diggory, I'm gonna kill you!!!