Where are we?
I don't know, Cedric. Someone punched
me in the face and my sense of direction
got a little goofed up!
Well, it seems clear to me now, that that
punch-ladle was a port-key.
And now - thanks to you! - we've both been
transported to some mystery location!
Brilliant Cedric! Well, you're a Hufflepuff, so why
don't you FIND a way out of this place, okay?
Harry I think I FOUND something!
It appears to be a headstone.
We must be in some sort of graveyard.
Tom Riddle, Mary Riddle, Thoms Riddle...
"Riddle me this", ey Potter?
[That's a Pop/Rock Band]
Cedric, I don't know about this place,
I think we gotta get out of here!
Harry, you're a Gryffindor.
Where's your sense of adventure?
God! Cedric, you're so annoying, okay?
You're like this guy, that's just around
all the time, when I don't need
a guy around!
You're this spare guy all the time!
The spare dude! You're such a spare!
Kill the spare! Avada Kedavra!
There are so many regrets... I'm dead!
Oh, my wizard-god!
Not so fast! Petrificus totalus!
Professor Quirrell, you just killed Cedric!
Not I, Potter. But perhaps
you'd like to see who did.
He's dying to see you!
Harry Potter, the Boy Who Lived!
It's good to see you again!
The cauldron is ready, my Loooooord!
Cauldron? What are you gonna do,
eat me? That's nuts!
As delicious seditious I think
you would make, Potter,...
... I'd need a stomach of my own
to digest you.
But I haven't got one of those...
yet!
Detention, Potter!
Detention?!? God, this guy is almost
being as big an asshole as snape is!
Worked!
When I was a boy
An orphan boy
I'd love to move my feet
I'd hear a tune
and start to swoon
My life would seem complete
The other boys would laugh and jeer
But I'd catch 'em tappin' their toes
And when I'd start to sway
[could mean rocking or reign *g*]
they'd get carried away.
And oh, how the feeling grows!
I'd take my foot
My little foot
And with that foot
Oh, how I'd start to shake
I'd take two feet
Two tiny feet
Hey look! That's neat!
It's coming true
Oh boy, I get to dance again! Wahoo!
To dance again
I've been waiting all these years
Now, at once, a chance appears
to hear the beat, so on your feet
It's time to dance again!
C'mon Potter! Imperio!
You take your foot
Your little foot
Hey look! Your foot!
See how it starts to shake
Ooh try his arms!
How bout a twirl!
He's like a girl!
How overdue!
I get to finally dance again with you!
To dance again!
I've (you've) been waiting all these years
To dance again
Now at once a chance appears
It's lovely swaying, and the music's playing
So come on! Let's dance again!
Everybody!
I take my foot!
(You take your foot)
My little foot!
(Take that little foot!)
And oh my foot!
(Let me hear it now!)
Look how it starts to shake
Oh, Voldy's back
(Hello world!)
For the attack
(I'm gonna getcha!)
He'll take over the world, it's true
But first there's something he's gotta do
I'll dance again!
He'll dance again!
I've been waiting all these years
He's been waiting all these years
To dance again
Now at once a chance appears
Everybody make way for a pas de bourre
[dance-move]
It's time to dance
Its time to dance again!