Yes! Ahm...
My dark Lord!
You look fabulous!
Belatrix Lestrange...
Oh, my Liege. Now it's going to be
like the old days when we did
nothing but torture,...
murder,...
and make love!
The old days are back, baby!
I can't tell you what it was like without you!
Well, I'm never going again!
'Cause I've conquered death!
And my first pleasure will be to
KILL Harry Potter!
Then next: to take over
the ministry of magic,...
and rule the World - FOR ALL TIME!
And you will, my lord!
But not yet!
For now, we must stick to the plan.
We blame Potter's murder on Quirrell.
So that your return may remain a secret.
The deatheaters aren't prepared
to take on the entire ministry of magic.
Much less Dumbledore and
the order of the phoenix.
I'm sorry!
What was that about me going to
Azkaban for Potter's murder?
Oh ho! You show refer to him as my lord,
my Liege or my dark lord!
Oh no, no, no....
Bellatrix - it's cool!
Quirell is cool! Quirell is cool! He is...
Over the last year, he has proven
himself to be a very good fr...
A very good servant to
the will of the dark lord.
Oh, I see so - so your time has come and I'm
your "Sally Hemings", is that right?
[She was a slave to Thomas Jefferson]
No!
No Quirrell, that - ah...
That came out wrong. It's not like that.
Isn't it?
Oh, silence slave! Crucio!
Oh no, no, no!
What's the matter?
He's your pawn. You are his queen.
It is an honor to serve the dark lord.
NO MATTER WHAT'S THE TASK!
Are you alright?
Did you really know the whole time you...
blame Potter's murder on me?
Yyyes! Yes - ah...
...I knew.
But things have changed over the last year.
I feel different for you now!
Don't touch me!
But things have changed over the last year.
I feel different for you now!
I can explain this. It's...
It's like that movie: "She's all that".
We watched that together. - Quirrell:
Remember how at the end
Freddie Price Jr. turns out to be good.
No! I didn't see the end because
you were watching it while you were on
the back of my head, sucking my soul!
Well, I wish there was another way.
But I've got to take over the world!
Oh there is!
I let you know now that it's gonna be...
pretty hard to make that
rollerblading date from Azkaban.
Deatheaters: take him away!
And now you have what you waited
for for so long.
What?
Your chance to kill Harry Potter!
Yees!
Kill Potter!
Ava...woah! Where d'you go?
You won't kill me today Voldemort.
But I tell you what:
I'll get you some punch!
Oh my Rowling!
What happened, Harry Potter?
Harry, what the hell are you doing over here?
You missed the raffle!
What happened to the graveyard? Uhm...!
It's - it's  Voldemort! It's Voldemort!
He is back!