Extra! Extra! Read all about it!
Harry Potter, the boy who beat
Voldemort now says he's back?
Daily Prophet!
Get your Daily Prophet here!
Harry Potter vs. Voldemort, round two!
Minister of magic Cornelius Fudge
makes a statement!
I've heard these Voldemort-rumors
and I for once simply don't believe it.
Voldemort talks about it on his new
"Floo-Tube" channel!
I'm gonna find Harry Potter and
I'm gonna [peep] to his [peep]!
Also there's a review on: 17 again.
[A movie with Zac Efron]
Well, it a little slow at the beginning,
but hey...
Come on! Zac Efron,  Zefron, enough said.
I've seen these so called "Posts",
and I still don't believe it!
This is a ruse! You've all
been hoodwinked!
Professor Quirrell confesses the murder
of Hogwarts student Cedric Diggory!
Receives life in Azkaban!
Extra! Extra! Read all about it! Extra!...
This totally sucks, man!...
This is horrible!
Yeah, I know. I mean...
Look at this it's... it's terrible.
Harry Potter vs. Voldemort,
the fight of the century...
No, it's not THAT! It's Hermione.
It's just like...
I can't get her out of my head
and every time I look at her
I have these pains in my chest
and I just know it's her fault,
that bitch...!
I'm just not cut out for this, Harry.
I'm not!
Yeah man, I know what you mean.
It's like when you try to save the world
and the whole world is just against you...
No! No! No! No! No!
This isn't about you!
Why does every conversation we have
to have , have to turn into a Potter-talk?
It's not Potter-talk...
No! No, I'm miserable!
And all you can do, is talk about yourself!
You're like the most self observed
guy I know!
If you where miserable, I'd be there
for you, but you won't even listen
to me, and I'm sick of it!
So...so...so good luck with whatever
you were talking about,
And I hope that you and Voldemort
live happily ever after.
ME, I'm never going to be happy again!
So I'm just gonna go curl up in my
sock drawer and sleep for days!
Ron...
Were you just talking to Ron?
Yeah, Iwas trying to
tell him about Voldemort...
Would he say anything about me?
Ah...Yeah,...he said - ah...
Was one of them an apology for
how he treated me at the Yule-Ball?
Yeah, I heard about that. Listen,
I was wondering, if you heard about
little something
I remember: Voldemort is back,
Cedric Diggory is dead,
Professor Quirrell is crazy
and now I have to save the world!
Did you hear that, Hermione?!?
Actually I have heard those things,
Harry, about a thousand times.
But never have they been told
to me with so much sets!
Love the attitude, Harry Potter.
You're acting like Garfield on a Monday!
[James A. Garfield died on a Monday after
he was shot some time before]
Don't you think I have a right
to be a little stressed out?!?
Wha... No! No, I don't!
You know what, this is just like
with the dragon, okay?
I stressed out, I told you to prepare
and jet you didn't do anything
and you were fine!
You know, you just played
a little guitar!
I mean, I don't know what
you're crying about, Harry.
This is just like when you defeated
Voldemort and you were a baby!
Hermione, come on...
You're the friend that's supposed to
tell me to go to the library and
trying figure that stuff out...
You know what, Harry?
I don't do that anymore!
What...?!?
Read it and weep, Potter!
I've heard Voldemort's back.
And he's trying to kill you, what do
you think of that, MOON SHOES?
Malfoy, I unsucceded, I don't see why
you're so happy about this.
If Voldemort is back- which he is -
you might so kiss Hogwarts goodbye.
You might so kiss the whole
planet goodbye!
Kiss the planet goodbye?
Having second thoughts about
Pigfarts, are you?
Malfoy, you're the last person
I wanna talk to right now, okay?
You know what?
As soon as you're out of the way,
I'll be the coolest kid in school!
Malfoy, that will never happen.
Everybody hates you!
Alright, okay! This coming
from Hermione "Stranger"!
She's right, Malfoy!
She's cooler then you!
Yeah, even Moaning Myrtle
is cooler then you!
Take this! Expelliarmus!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Stop it!
What the devil is going on hereeeeee?
Draco Malfoy, pull those
trousers up at once!
Professor, I just...
I don't want to hear it!
I want to see you in my office!
NOW!
This is all your fault, Potter.
You'll pay for this! YOU'LL PAY...
Nice - you're the man!
That made me feel better!
Hey Ginny, what's... I hope you've
something to say about Voldemort!
No...
(sigh) whatever...
No, I'm fine!
Ah.... Harry?
Yeah?
So...We kissed at the Yule-Ball,
and...well, I thought we were
gonna be together forever.
But we're not.
Yeeaah... that, ah...
that pretty much sums it up...
What's going on?
Ginny, THIS is what's going on,
don't you get it?
Everyone is who... is in danger,
who's near to me. We can't be
together,because...
when Voldemort is back - which he is -
you're in mortal peril, don't you get it?
It's like the Spiderman movie haven't
you seen that?
MJ and Peter Parker can't  be together.
But the whole point of Spiderman two was
that MJ und Peter Parker could be together
in the end!
Yeah, I know, but the point of Spiderman
three is everything sucks and it falls to shit!
Ginny, what I'm trying to say is,
I don't want my life to be like Spiderman
three, I hated that movie!
I'm sorry, it's just...
that's my little way of saying, well
we can't be together.
I'm sorry, Ginny.
I'm such an idiot!
I need a... I need a Butterbeer...!
Hey! Pst! Potter...!
Hey! It's me!
Who are you?
It's Dumbledore!
Listen Harry, I've got some very
important things, I got to tell you!
Oh, about Voldemort?
Yes! Things that are absolutely crucial
for you to know, but I can't get into it
right now...
You need to meet me in my inner office
at ten o'clock. And come by yourself!
Bring that...ah - invisibility-cloak of yours
and don't go blabbing your mouth about this
to anyone else!
Voldemort has spies that could be anywhere,
even inside of Hogwarts!
From now on the only person you can trust,
Harry, is me and Severus Snape.
Listen Dumbledore, I know you
don't wanna hear this,...
but I am not so sure about...
Snape...
I think, no, I'm pretty sure,
he's working for Voldemort...
What?!? That's stupid! YOU're stupid!
No, no! I'm positive, that night in the
graveyard some Deatheater cuts
off his hand,
and Snape...[???]...
Oh ...[???]... Snape has assured me that
he lost his hand in an entirely unrelated
incident.
Dumbledore, why do you trust
Snape so much?
Because I love him!
Professor, I...
Quiet! I don't want to hear anything
else about it!
There's no way, that Severus Snape is, was
or ever shall be a servant of Voldemort!