All hail, Voldemoooort!
Severus Snape, what are you doing here?
Got tired of being on Dumbledores lap?
I ought to Jelly-legs-jinx you right now,
traitor!
Don't be goofy with me!
I need to see Voldemort.
How do we know this isn't some
Order of the Phoenix practical joke?
I thought you deserted the deatheaters
when the dark lord lost his body.
Or were you always a spy for Dumblebore...
Slumbersnore!
Bumblesore!
I heard you had your dark mark
laser surgically removed.
Oh! Well, if you two know soooo much
about me, you should write a
bioooography!
Snape, the double agent!
That's right!
I've always been a servant of Voldemort.
I've simply been working undercover
finding out valuable informations
such as the inner workings of Hogwarts,
the roster of the Order of the Phoenix,
and finding out exactly what a true
Hufflepuff is anyway...
I've seen things, no Slytherin should see.
So if you're done putting each others
feet in each others mouths:
I would like to see my master!
Of course. Right away, Severus.
Good. I'll be in the drawing room.
Painting a picture of the stupid
looks on your faces...
Then, after sneaking into the
department of mysteries,
Excuse me...!
we'll enchant the...
Wooooooooh!Woooh!
WOHOHO! EXCUSE ME!
I was in the middle of plotting! ...
Where was I?
The statues will occupy the guards in
the the main Lobby, while you and I
sneak into the ministers office,
where you will be ONE killing curse away
from complete control of the
entire wizarding world!
How does that sound, my Lord?
My Lord?
Voldemort...?
Ah...yeah!
Gringots! That's great! That's great...
Polyjuicepotion, always very classic....
I'm sorry, what were we talking about?
Did you hear ANYTHING of my evil plan?
Well, ahm...
the details are a little fuzzy, but...
ah, but you did have a very evil tone...
He's all yours!
What, wha... Bellatrix, come back!
No! It's...do...co...don't be like this...
(sigh)
Now TWO people are mad at me...
What?
Sir, Severus Snape is at the door and
[???] access to you.
Severus Snape?!?
See him in.
Is that a new body, my Lord?
You look absolutely ravishing!
Severus...!
For such a super secret spy you're
a terrible liar.
I'm a wrack!
You'd better have some good news.
My Lord, you know how for years we
were trying to get deatheaters...
Aah!Aah!
For years we've been trying to sneak
deatheaters onto the grounds
of Hogwarts.
Well, I think I finally discovered
a way how.
Well, by all means, Snape, tell me!
I can't.
Can't? Tease! Why not?
I made an unbreakable vow not
to let any deatheaters in...
Unbreakable vows! I hate those...
I know... but I had to do it to convince
Dumbledore of my loyalty.
Yes, Snape, I understand...
but if you can't help me, what do
you propose we'd do?
Well, I can't tell you,
but I've brought along someone who can!
All hail Lord Voldemort!
Lucius Malloys boy???
Draco Malfoy! Malfoy...
[Voldemort] Are you serious?
Help from a child! You've got
to be kidding me!
Don't make me laugh, I'm pissing!
If this homemade dark mark won't
convince you, ...
...then at least hear me out!
Okay. Okay. Okay!
How do you propose you get MY
deatheaters into your little
daycare center?
And don't... and don't suggest
a giant slide!
Or a  Trampoline!
'Cause we've already tried those....
The vents!
Your deatheaters shall enter through
the ventilation system of Hogwarts!
Ah, the vents...
Uhm... How do we find these vents?
Well, I'll tell you how to get to the vents.
But first...
...we discuss the subject of payment!
Ah, the catch!
There's always a catch!
There's nothing in this world so cruel
and demanding as the soul of a child...
What do you want, Malloy?
I want:
A galaxy traversing rocket-ship with
enough fuel to get me to MARS!
What do you want with a rocket-ship?
What business do you have on mars?
Well, let's just say:
Pigfarts - Pigfarts - here I come.
Pigfarts - Pigfarts - yum, yum, yum...
No...no...no...no...no!
with all due respect, my Lord:
There's one tiny flaw in this flawless plan.
Albus Dumbledore!
Arrgh,...  you're right, Snape!
(sigh)
Normally I'd say: 'I'll kill him!', but I...
...I haven't been feeling so evil lately...
So here is how it's gonna
break down, Milfoy.
I need your guarantee, ...
...that you'll lead my detheaters
into Hogwarts.
I'll simultaneously be attacking
the ministry of magic.
Now I need you to PROMISE, ...
that by the end of the siege of
Hogwarts Dumbledore will be dead, ...
... leave Harry Potter for me!
But Dumbledore - must die!
Do we have a deal?
We shall shake on it.
An unbreakable vow!
By the end of tomorrow night
Albus Dumbledore will be dead?
Yes. - And I'll have my rocket-ship?
When the technology is available.
And you'll have to be my slave
for a whole day, starting now!
Nooooo!
You litte shit!
You got me!
You got me! Oh, that is so embarrassing!
That's the second time that
that's happened!
That's why I hate unbreakable curses!
Oh, there are so many things
I'm going to have you do for me!
You're going to - clean my room, ...
and lay-off my nickles, ...
And you'll going to tape
'Wizards of Waverly place' for me.
Oh, I hate tours!
I'll be busy with the murder!
Slaaaaaughter!