Harry, why would Dumbledore wanna
meet us so late at night?
Well, he's got some information to tell
us about Voldemort. Did you bring the
invisibility-cloak?
I have it right here. I...
Okay Harry. This better be good!
I don't have a Snack AND I'm missing
'Wizards of Waverly Place' for this, okay?
So what do we have to do
that's so damn...
Oh my God! Thank you.
I love Hogwarts.
Hogwarts is amazing!
You want one?
Yeah!
You know what? I am leaving!
Oh N-n-n-n-no! You're not!
No you're not!
Okay, when I said I needed your help
I meant the both of you!
So you guys gonna get over these...
hurt feelings before something
gets hurt, okay?
Come on!
Hello Harry.
Oh, damn it! I told you to come
by yourself!
Why d'you have to bring the fatties?
Dumbledore - Ron and Hermione are
my best friends!
And if these information is as
important as you say,
they have a right to hear it.
Well, I've been wrong before.
Get in ya hot legs/grace.
I was talking to Weasley!
Thanks!
Well, sorry the place is such a sty.
OH - MY - GOD!
That it a BOSS Zefron Poster!
It's awesome!
Just the greatest...
...[???]... you have ever seen
And he just seems like...
... a charismatic ... ah...
human material.
You think you like him?
Wrong!
'Cause I love him the most.
Harry Potter loves Zac Efron more then
anybody else on the planet.
Anyway, no, that's not what we
talk about. We talk about Voldemort.
Harry's right. It's not necessarily about
Zefron. Everybody knows I like
him the most.
But ah,... about the dark Lord:
If you ah... want to defeat this guy
you're going to have to know about
horcruxes.
What's - ahm.. What's a horcrux?
A horcrux is one of the most terrifying
pieces of magic that a wizard
can create.
It's actually when a wizard takes a piece
of his soul and puts it into something else.
Why would anybody ever wanna do that?
Harry, if you have a horcrux
you can never truly die.
Your body can be dead,
but your soul can live on.
Oh, it makes sense now, Harry!
Everyone knows that the night your parents
were killed, Voldemort was destroyed.
But somehow he survived.
He must have had a horcrux!
He didn't just have ONE horcrux.
He had SIX of 'em!
I've already killed the first fife for you,
so don't worry about that.
But you guys have to find
the last one with this.
The sword of Godric Gryffindor!
Godric Gryffindor was one of the
four founders of Hogwarts.
If anything can destroy a horcrux,
that sword is it!
This thing is so damn awesome!
Oh my god. Every wizard
should have a sword.
Not these stupid drumsticks!
Forget about them!
Okay, you know what Dumbeldore.
So we know what a horcrux is,
that's all well and good but how
do we find them?
Where are they? Where's the last one?
You'll find them with this.
Woah!
Looks like...
Looks like 'G-Unit' bling,
[G-Unit: Gangster Rapper
like 50 cent]
But it is actually a horcrux-seeking
medallion.
Wait. - That's a horcrux-seeking
medallion?
I... that sounds a little to convenient!
Oh, you've a problem with a time-turner
not with a horcrux-seeking medallion!
Wait - so if he has this piece of bling,
then why are Ron and I even here?
Yeah. Voldemort isn't any of our
business!
Hermione Granger:
When one of youz has gotz a problem,
that means all three of youz
haz gotz a problem!
What would Zac Efron say in
time like this?
We're all in this together...!
Anyway. You just gotta..- You gotta
find the horcruxes and you gotta
destroy them!
It's the only way that you could def-.
...[???]...Guess...Oh - it must be
the Death Eaters!
They're coming to kill me...
Kids get your beards on!
We don't have any beards!
I thought I told you to bring beards!
What is with the invisibility-cloak?
Oh well, put that on it's not a beard!
Hey, are you Dumbledore?
No no, you see, I've got this beard on!
Well, have you seen him?
Oh... I thought I saw someone
over there by that mirror.
But I could just have been imagining
what...[???]...if I looked like without
this beard.
Alright. Everybody spread out
and look for Dumbledore!
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
Be careful with the Zac Efron Poster-
it's an antique!
Why do you care so much about Zefron?
I just appreciate his charms. And hair.
Yeah. But everybody knows, that I
like him the best!
What was that?
I wish that I could say, that..
it was me.
Because I feel, that I love Zefron
the most.
But it was definitely a voice from
within this room.
Is it an invisible man?
Could the predator be in the room?
[A movie with Arnold Schwarzenegger]
Begin invisible-man-search!
Alright! It's me! It's Dumbledore!
Dumbledore? Where do you come from?
The man with the beard turned me in.
Now we've got you right
where we want you!
Yes. But what I don't
understand is how!
We had the help of a man on the inside.
Someone you trusted. Someone you
may have even loved!
Slughorn?
Lockhart?
Aberforth, my brother?
No!
It was me!
Malfoy, ya little shit!
That's right, Dumbledore.
I betrayed everyone!
And now I'm going to kill you!
Oh no, you're not, Draco. If you were
gonna to kill me, you would have done
so already!
No, no, no! Not necessarily true!
I just wanted to offer you one more
game of connect four before I
offed you!
Draco, there are other options.
You know, it is time that you look inside
yourself and figured out, what it is that
you really want.
I want Hermione Granger-
and a rocket-ship.
Then why don't you just take the girl
out for a happy meal then go to
space-camp.
Come on!
Murder leads to a life of despair and
desperation.
I know, you're gonna do the right thing,
eh? - Atta boy!
What the devil is going on heeeeere?
Severus, thank you!
We've got Dumbledore cornered!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Kill him! Do it, Draco!
Uh... I... I don't think, I can...!
Coward! 10 points from Gryffindor!
Severus!?!
I don't understand! I gave you my
leathermens jacket!
It never fit me.
Why didn't you tell me? I could have
shrunk it with magic.
Severus, please! Don't kill me!
Avada Kedavra!
I hate Snape! I hate Snape!
I hate Snape! I hate him!
I'm gonna kill him!
It's not your fault, Harry!
No, it IS my fault. Don't you get it?
Everybody's dying because of me!
First Cedric, now Dumbledore.
I can't do it anymore!
Come on! Let's go to the Burrow!
Ron, don't you get it?
I have to do this by myself.
I did it once when I was a baby.
I can't have you guys be near me.
...[???]...risk!
We know, but we don't care about
the risk!
No, you don't understand..
You... you have to get away from me!
You can't mean that...!
I do! Just leave me alone!