Cornelius Fudge, the minister of magic!
I still don't believe you're back...!
Believe this, Fudge:  Avada Kedavra!
Uh! - A heart-attack...surely...
Aaaaaah....
Yes! Yes! The ministry has fallen!
Yes! Now you're the minister...
Nay the king of all magic!
Oh, Voldemort... Take me right here!
Right now, right here on
the ministers desk!
I'm gonna get ya!
I'm gonna get ya!...
Come here, trixie!
Wait!
You wanna try something new?
Oh... some new...!
Get on the desk!
Now sit up - bitch...
Yes, command me, my Lord.
Aaah, mmmmh, that's nice...!
So what do we do now?
Anything we want...
hang out mostly...
we could watch a movie...
how's about  'She's all that'? I've
never seen the beginning of it...
Are you feeling okay, my Lord?!!?
Of course I am, Quirrell!
Alright, that's the dozenths time
you called me that!!!
No, I ah...
I called you a squirrel!
I called you a squirrel.
No! You're thinking about peon
we sent to Azkaban!
He's not a peon!
He's more a man then you'll ever be....
I can't do this.
If I'm going to be evil with all of you,
I need to be evil with ALL of you!
Evil with all of me?...Wha...
what does that mean...?
I'm all right here...
No! There are pieces of you missing!
Are you talking about my horcruxes???
'Cause if it...If it weren't for those
I wouldn't even be here right now...!
I can't remember dad
and I can't remember mom
and aunts and uncle aren't
quite the same
but I had him and life seemed fair
yes, I had him he was here
to give me strength, show concern,
ask for nothing in return
say hello, talk me through
do the things that fathers should do.
And I'm missing you
I'm just missing you
There it is, he's gone
and he's hung me out to dry
the joy he said he felt, well,...
I guess it was a lie
but when I had him my life was fine
when I had him he was mine
He'd share his thoughts, be a friend
stick with me until the end
watch a movie, roller-skate
fill the world with fear and hate
And I'm missing you
I'm just missing you
Now I'm all alone
Now you're gone for good
now I'm stuck right here wishing
I understood
You gave me hope when my
spells weren't right
You gave me someone to hold
every night
And I'm missing you
I'm just missing you
and I'm missing you
My dark Lord, news from Severus Snape!
Dumbledore's dead and the Dementors
have control of the castle.
Hogwarts is yours, my dark Lord!
Aaah! Excellent!
Prepare my flying-machine!
Looks like I'm going back to Hogwarts...!