Haaaaaaaarryyyyy!
Ginny, what are you doing here?
Get out of here!
No, there's no place to go.
The Death Eaters are all
over the castle!
I know and they are looking for me.
And if they find me, they're gonna be
with you - you...you...
...you gonna get in trouble.
Get out of here!
What you gonna do?
I don't, Ginny! I'm not cut out
for these kind of things.
Oh no, you have to do something!
I don't know what you can do,
but you can do it!
Y..y - you're Harry Potter!
NO!
You're the boy who lived!
No, Ginny! You don't get it!
Will you guys get it! I -
I'm just a twelve year old kid!
Ginny, I'm sorry, but... I'm alone!
It's hopeless, alright?
I've been alone
Surrounded by darkness
I've seen how heartless
The world - can be
I've seen you cry
You felt like it's hopeless
I'll always do my best
To make - you see
That Harry you're not alone
'Cause you're here with me
And nothing's ever gonna take us down,
'cause nothing
Can keep me from loving you
And you know it's true
It don't matter what will come to be
Our love is all we need -
to make it through
Now, I know it ain't easy
No it ain't easy
But it ain't hard trying
So hard trying
Every time I see you smiling
And I feel you so close - to me
Tell me
That baby you're not alone
'Cause you're here with me
And nothing is ever gonna bring us down
'Cause nothing can keep me from
loving you
And you know it's true
It don't matter what will come to be
Our love is all we need-
to make it through
But I'm still in trouble
I trip and stumble - try
To make sense of things sometimes
I look for reasons
But I don't need them
All I need is the look in your eyes
And I realize
Hey Harry
Baby you're not alone
'Cause you're here with me
And nothing is ever gonna take us down
'Cause - nothing can keep me
from loving you
And you know it's true
It don't matter what will come to be
Our love is all we need-
to make it through
Guys...
I'm so glad you came back.
I'm sorry I shouted.
It don't matter what will come to be.
Our love is all we need
To make it...
To make...
...through
Now that we've got that four-part
harmony out of the way,...
...why don't we look for that horcrux?
Yeah, that's true.
Well, it could be anywhere.
If I had a horcrux, I would drop it
in the bottom of the ocean.
Or I would put it in the pyramid with
king Tut and all of his jewels.
Or I would blast it into space with a monkey,
who knew nothing about horcruxes.
Or it could be hidden somewhere around the
mundane british countryside.
Our search could [???] months
of depressing camping...
...breaking into Gringotts and drinking
boatloads of Polyjiuce potion.
Well, the medallion says: that's dump!
So we're not gonna to that.
But it does say it's in one convenient place.
Get this: Hogwarts!
That's awesome. I love Hogwarts.
And it's even better.
It's in Dumbledore's office.
Ah, bitching!
So let's go! - Oh wait a second!
Wait a second! Hold the phone!
How did you get here? The Death Eaters
are all over Hogwarts.
Oh, I had help.
From whom?
Oh, it's over here...
Malfoy!
Oh, no, no, no! He's really nice now.
Oh, I - I - I just wanted to say, that song
#you guys sang was really beautiful.
And ah... while - while I was backstage,
I was...ahm... working on my [singing].
And I thought, ahm... maybe if I could...
maybe I could join you, but you - wrapped
it up before I could chime in there.
Maybe if you're - do a reprise,
I could have a little - go at it.
And ahm - but as - as Ginny said:
I'm really nice now...
...and I just feel awful
about what happened.
But, I mean: could you argue that
this was my fault?
Absolutely - Yes - Oh yes!
Yeah, that would be a save argument,
ah...
But - let me ask you one question:
Do you thing - I'm happy about this?
Oh my god, Malfoy! Just because
you're upset doesn't mean you're
off the hook.
Yeah, and furthermore: you wanna kick
your own ass, or should we do it for you?
Oh...Aaaah...
Well, I guess, if you're - giving me the
option, I'll - I'll kick my own ass.
But first, I should teach you how to get
into Dumbledores office. It's ironically
the same way, the Death Eaters got in.
Okay, alright.W..w...w why don't you boys
head off to Dumbledores office, okay?
Ginny and I will... will take the invisibility
cloak and ah - we will see if we can contact
the order of the phoenix...
...we really haven't seen them
the whole play. So...
That's a good plan. Malfoy, don't touch me!
Let's get out of here! Let's go!
Ahm...hey! Hey, Hermione! Come here!
Come downstage...
Ah...Listen!...Ah... Shit!... Ah... alright,
ah...hey...aaah...
So... I've been acting like a
jerkass lately...
you know that...and, aaah...
...and I'm sorry. It's just: seeing you
dance with everyone at the Yule Ball
just made me kinda jealous, ah...
I was...I was jealous.
You were jealous?
Yeah, that's the third time I say
I was jealous...
Oh...Ro...Ro...Ron, we don't really have
to talk about this right now!
Well, what if the Death Eaters get us?
What if we don't come back? You know?
Don't say that...
Oh, my god...
Oh, no way...
It's blueberry.
Yeah, I can taste that...
Gotta let it settle?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, spud gum.
Take two, take two...
You chew it...
Awesome!
Let's go kill Voldemort!