Did you guys see this Zefron Poster?
Yeah, we know, Malfoy...
We know about it...
Listen Malfoy, it's not
that big of a deal.
Can we just look for some horcruxes,
please?
Roger.
This thing, the pencil is a horcrux?
No. That's no horcrux.
No.
That is a horcrux?
Pack of doughnuts?
No.
Those are Snacks, those are Snacks!
Is this a horcrux?
No, it's not.
Aaaaah!This could take forever!
The on... There are so many
things in this room.
And the only thing of REAL value:
That Zefron poster.
Wait a second...
No!
You think... no!
No...
Anything related to Zefron could
never be anything evil.
Ron! Kill it! Kill it, it's the last horcrux!
No, Weasley!
Don't kill it, it's Zefron!
Kill it, Ron!
Oh no, it's so charismatic...
Don't kill me.
I'm not you enemy...
Potter is the enemy...!
No no no, Harry is my friend...!
You gotta get your head in the game,
Weasley!
He will betray you! He will take that
which you want the most...
It's a lie, Ron! Don't listen to him,
he's lying!
I know your thoughts,
Ronald Weasley...
I know, what you truly desire...
Hello, Ron...!
Oh my God, Hermione you lost weight!
That's right! And in shape for
Harry Potter.
What?!?
Wait...
That's right! As long as Harry's around
you'll always be second best,...
least loved, but if Harry Potter
were gone...
then we could be together forever...
Ron, that's not true!
It's not true, Ron!
Yeah, Harry is my friend...
But don't you WANT me, Ron?
Yes...
Don't you LOVE me, Ron?
YES!
Then you know, what you gotta do,
Ron!
Yes... I must kill Harry...
That's right, Weasley!
No! No! It's a Trick, Ron!
Don't listen to her!
Stop it! Listen, Hermione is my best,
you're my best friends!
I'd never do anything to hurt
you or her!
Lies, Weasley! All lies!
You are covered in hell.
Ron, it's not true,
you're my best friend...
Kill him....KILL HIM!
NOOOOOOOOO!
Do it again!
If you put some tape on this, it's fine...!
Ron! You had me going there
for a minute, buddy.
Oh yeah... sorry about that, pal,
it was just...
everything she was saying, you know...
It felt like... I couldn't... I don't know...
What?
Even if that's...
how she did feel about you and me...
well, it wouldn't matter...
'cuz you're my best friend.
and I would never...
do anything to hurt you...
'cuz I love you!
I love you, too man...
Well... listen, chaps,
as fun as this was, I thought destroying
a horcrux would be much harder.
Yeah, me too.
So when you think about it, Horcruxes
are just kinda stupid.
Wands down, boys!
How could you idiots get captured?
You were invisible!
Sorry...
Do it, Potter, they die!
Well, looks like we got the backs against
the wall and nowhere to go.
Put your swords down and the wands!
Ooooh! Look at itty-bitty Harry Potter
giving orders to his itty-bitty
diaper friends!
I'm not a Baby! I'm not a  Baby,
I'm twelve!...
What the devil is going on heeeeeere?
Wow, Deja vu...
Victory, Snape!
I love it! We have Potter
and his friends, AT LAST!
You are a very mean person!
Yeah, Dumbledore trusted you!
Yeah, you are a big, fat traitor,
Snape!
Oh! A traitor am I, Potter?
You're exactly right! I am a traitor.
Because I'm about to betraaaaay
someone.
Right - now!
Bat Bogey Hex!
No!
Expelliarmus!
Serpensortia!
Aaaaaaah!
My wiener....!
Snape! No!...
Don't even think about it, ...
unless anyone of you wants a
snake to the wiener!
Now come on, Potter! Come with me!
Only the dark Lord has reserved the right
to kill YOU! Come on!
Kids!
Mom?!?
Mrs.Weasley?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Molly Weasley and those are my kids!
Avada Kedavra!
Aaah! That is not fair!
Die, bitch!
Holy shit!
Mom, you just killed her, I thought you
were gonna tuck in her shirt or make her
do the dishes !
Stupid Kids!
Desperate times call for desperate
measures!
Even the unforgivable can be considered
forgivable sometimes.
What are you doing here?
I came here with the
Order of the Phoenix.
Lupin, Tonks, Mad eye Moody,
Sirius Black and your brother Fred.
Oh, great! Where are they?
They are all dead.
Fred? No!
Anyway, ...
just came here to save your lifes,
go back to what you were doing.
Disaparate!