Snape! Snape! Snape! Snape!
ah... Expelliarmus!
Die!
Oh no, Harry, this is not so good!
That is a coral snake.
And a coral snake is a highly
poisonous snake!
Potter, she's right.
It's to late for me now.
Before I go, I need to tell you:
There is another horcrux.
How can that be?
All six have been destroyed!
No no! There's a seventh!
I really hope it's not an
Ashley Tisdale Poster, I can't do that...
Check the medallion!
It doesn't say anything...
Well, give it to Granger!
Wait, but it... it says there's one
right here, but I don't understand...
Harry, the night Voldemort
killed your parents, ...
he tried to destroy you, but his body
was destroyed instead.
when that happened, a part of his soul
was blasted away from the whole...
and attached itself...
...to YOU!
Voldemort can never truly die, until all
the horcruxes have been destroyed!
But if... if Harry is a  horcrux, I mean...
does Harry have to be...destroyed?
There's got to be another way...!
No. Potter, I'll show you
what you need to do.
Watch ... very...carefully...
He... he didn't even do ANYTHING...
That's because he's dead you
dumb mother fu...
People of Hogwarts!
My Death Eaters have taken the castle!
And your headmaster Albus Dumbledore
is dead!
Continue to resist and you will all be
killed one by one.
But - there need not be war between us.
You've all fought so valiantly ...
...and I'm willing to offer you positions
in my new world-order
as my slaves...
[without loudspeaking...]
Give up now and be forgiven!
I command my Death Eaters
to stand down.
Now, Harry Potter, I speak directly
to you!
You do not wish for those closest to you
to continue to suffer and die
on your behave!
You will come face me yourself!
I'll be waiting for you in the
forbidden forest for one hour.
At the end of that hour you have
not come to face me, have not-
turned yourself in- ...
...the battle  recommences.
This time, Potter, I shall enter
the fray myself!
And I will fight!
And I will murder every last man, ...
...woman and child, ...
who has tried to conceal you from me!
Voldemort out, bitches!
Okay...Alright guys, don't worry...we...
we still have an hour, okay?
We...we...we just need to
come up with a plan...
There's no plan, Hermione, I...
I know what I have to do.
I ... I have to die...
No, no, no, NO!
There's GOT to be another way!
Oh... Ma...may....maybe there's
something ah... maybe there's
something in this book!
Maybe we could find some sort of
enchantment, that will nullify...
No no no, forget about it...!
There's only one thing to do...
I have to die!
I love you all...
except you Draco,
I can't [peep] stand you.
Goodbye!
Harry...
He's not coming, my Lord...
It seems that way...
Well, Death Eaters: looks like we're
going back to seize the castle!
This is what Potter has chosen!
Funny, I... I expected him to...
I expected him to come.
Seems I was mistaking!
You weren't!
Harry Potter!
The boy who lived!
Crucio!
Are you not even going to fight back?
You're weak...
weak...
Just -
like -
your -
parents...
They did not deserve to live in this
world, in MY world!
Prepare to join them.
Prepare -
to die.
Avada Kedavra!
Yeah - woho - Voldy! Voldy!...
You did it, my Lord!
Potter is dead, no one shall ever
question your powers again!
Yes...
Doesn't this please you, my Lord?
Yeah...
Yeah, it's great... it's great...
I just thought it might make me feel
less empty inside.
Well Death Eaters: ...
We go back to Hogwarts to tell them
what has become of their  -
'Hero'!