Hey, Harry!
Wha... Dumbledore, wha... ?!?
What am I doping here? Where am I?
I thought I was dead, I got shocked
by Voldemort, I...
Let's just say you're somewhere
between our world and the next.
What?!? Did I survive??? What...w...
Not really the first time, Potter.
Take a seat.
Alright...
Harry, have you ever heard of a love-
SIT DOWN!
Have you ever heard of a love-shield?
Ah...
No, but it sounds kind of...
kind of fruity...
A love-shield is anything but fruity!
It's when somebody loves you so much,
that in fact they were ever willing
to give their life for you,
that love really becomes a shield which
surrounds your body to protect you
from any form of dark magic.
So... ...[???]... and me have
a love-shield?
Harry, it's time for you to learn all the
things you should have known
seven years ago...
which really would have helped you
along the way.
The love-shield protected you
the first time ah, ...
Voldemort accidentally turned you
into the seventh horcrux , ...
the one not even he knew about...
That's when I survived the first time.
...Exactly. And when Voldemort tried
killing you this time, ...
he was actually unknowingly killing
a piece of himself inside of you...
ah... and I've known the whole time!
You knew this the whole time?
You're the best!
Hey! Hey! They don't call me the
greatest wizard who ever lived
for nothing.
Harry, it's time for you to get your
cute little butt back there and fight
him as a mortal man!
Except this time, he will be
a mortal man, too!
Dumbledore, I care what you're saying.
I know what I have to do.
Good boy, good boy!
Hey, before I go, ahm...
So you're a clairvoant now, right? You
can see the past, the present and the
future, all the same time... [Oh yeah!]
Can you tell me how 'Lost' ends?
[A series on TV]
Harry, there are some questions
that even I can't answer.
Thanks, man!
Hey, no problem. Get out of here!
The door on your left! Yeah.
Are you ready to go, Dumbledore?
Sure am, Rumbleroar!
And you're sure you don't want to
et Harry Potter know that you're
really still alive?
Oh no, Pigfarts has been a closely
guarded secret for thousands of years.
It would be a shame to let the cat
out of the bag. No pun intended.
I suppose you're right.
Do you have your space-suit,
Dumbledore?
Oh! Thank you for reminding me!
Ready to go, Rumby?
I sure am! To Pigfarts!
RUMBLEROAAAAAAR!!!
People of Hogwarts!
It's me.
Harry Potter is dead!
He was killed while running away,
trying to save himself, ...
...while you layed down
your lifes for him.
The battle is won!
My Death Eaters outnumber you!
Continue to resist and be slaughtered!
Come out of the castle, ...
... kneel before me, ...
...and you may - be - spared!
Oh shit... Okay... aaaahm...
alright, ah, you guys, you guys
barricade the door!
Go with ...with ah...the French...
go, go do it right now!
Ahm... Cho! You...
you will see if Neville's dead.
Aaahm... you guys:
Ah...Go get Snacks!
Ah shit, we barricaded the door...
Me, I will... I will quit...ah, ...
wow, there's only one thing
we need to do. We're gonna fight!
Oh, come on, I'm tired...!
Can't we just be Death Eaters...?
No! No, we can't just be Death Eaters!
Okay?
We're gonna fight! Okay?
And we're gonna fight SO HARD, ...
...that we're gonna win!
He thinks that we're finished
He thinks that we're done
He thinks that it's over
His battle is won HA!
He thinks that we're finished
No!
but we aren't through
stop and think my friends
what would Harry do for you?
Harry never gave up the fight
Harry stood up for what is right
Well, now its our turn
our turn!
make a joyful sound
Voldemort is going down!
We must unite
so we can fight,
turn the battle around
time's running out
it's time to shout:
Voldemort is going down!
Can't you feel a fire burning?
now it's time to be a man!
a great big muscley
super big super hot man!
We won't be pushed around anymore!
we'll be a force you can not ignore!
we'll be an army for Dumbledore!
For Dumbledore!
We must unite
so we can fight,
turn the battle around
time's running out
it's time to shout
Voldemort is going down!
Hey Guys! I'm alive!
I'm back. Guys, I know how
to defeat Voldemort.
Everybody follow me, okay?
We must unite
so we can fight,
turn the battle around
time's running out
it's time to shout:
We must unite - so we can fight
Voldemort is  goiiiiiiiiing...
Voldemort is going down!