No! No, no! Cho, come here!
It's okay we barricaded the door,
nobody can get through that it's
impossible. It's alright. It's alright.
That's right. It's impossible.
Impossible!
Avada Kedavra!
WHAAAAT?!?
Potter?
How many times do I
have to kill you, boy?
Really more then once!
But it's all over Voldemort.
cuz you can't kill me this time.
Nobody help me!
I gotta do this by myself.
He doesn't mean that! It's not how
he operates, is it, boy?
Who're you gonna use as a human
shield this time, Potter?
Ron!
Oh!
Nobody! 'cuz this time it's just you
and me!
Means all your horcruxes are gone.
I destroyed them all.
WHAT?!? Ah...
Even my ZEFRON Poster?!?
Especially the Zefron poster!
No! Curse you, Potter!
You'll die for that!
No, I won't.
I won't. Because you can't kill me.
And you can't kill any of these people.
What the [peep] are you on about?
You don't learn from your mistakes,
do you Voldemort?
I was prepared to die
to save these people.
But you didn't!
Yes, but I meant to.
And that's what did it.
I've done, what my mother did for me,
for these people.
I've given the magical ...[???]....
You can't hurt me or these people
ever again.
So what?
Who cares about these children?
It's you I want dead, Potter!
What's to stop you from dying
when I strike?
Just one thing...
Think about all the people you've hurt,
Voldemort, all the lifes you destroyed.
The people you've s...
The people you've killed.
Why don't you try a little slice of
remorse pie?
What???
There's got to be ONE person, ...
ONE thing in your life that you miss.
That you regret.
Well... maybe there's one...
NO!
There isn't!
The joke's on you, Potter!
I don't care about anybody!
I know. That's what makes you
such a piece of shit.
'cuz here at Hogwarts we all
stick together.
We love one another - we're friends!
My love's protecting these guys-
and their love is all I need to protect
me from you.
So let's put that theory to the test, Potter!
Avada Kedavra!
Expelliarmus!
Well, chocolate frogs!
Harry Potter did it yaw'll!
Wow, wow, wow,wow,..., wow!
Wow, listen! Hey!
I just wanna let you guys know:
That I'm totally cool with it. Go on!
Come here! Let's make out!
Well, Guys... I mean...
I guess that ties up all the
loose ends!
Yeah. Everything's cool!
Oh, except for the
house-cup-tournament.
I found Dumbledores will.
Dumbledores will?
In case of my death, Gryffindor wins
the house-cup.
It's also set that Hogwarts goes to
Harry Potter, ...
... my Chocolate-factory goes to
Charlie [a movie], ....
...and toontown goes to the toons!
[Roger Rabbit]
Hey, Guys. Well, I guess all our
professors are dead, so...
...butterbeer's on me!
You're free to go.
Thank you.
You know...
while I was devouring every single one
of your happy thoughts, ...
they all seemed to be about a certain
friend of yours. Care to talk ?
No! No that's behind me now!
Sorry.
Well, did you hear the news?
Voldemort is dead!
Yeah! Good luck getting off this
[???] island!
Dead?
Hey, you!
Voldemort, is it - is it really you?
What's left of me.
But I just heard that y...you were
...destroyed?
Yeah.
But Quirrell, there's - there's
a part of me,...
that's still here. And I can't go on
to the next plain without it.
It's a part of me that can't be
destroyed.
Because it's right...
...in...
...here!
In my heart?
So you came back?
I came home.
And you don't want to kill
Harry Potter anymore?
No.
Because I learned something when I
had my body back, Quirrell.
I learned that life is...really messy.
complicated and... it doesn't turn
out the way that you think it will.
and...ahm...
...you think killing people might make
them like you, but it doesn't!
It just makes people dead.
I got...I got killed by a two-year-old!
And that's really embarrassing.
And ever is this: when you're gonna
come back, Voldemort?
When you're gonna take over the world?
It's on me. It's all on me!
And I think then by myself:
('cuz no one is there)
And I say to myself:
Maybe with Quirrell things would be okay.
Is 'okay' good?
Quirrell!
Okay is wonderful!
Baby, you're not alone!
'cause you're here with me
...