Mission log.
Officer February of the galactic league
starship ranger corps
starship15A2.
After x
number of years in space
we have reached the uncharted alien world
and are now prepping for human colonization.
Upon arriving in an exploration pod
it appears as though the planet's surface is
stable
and there seem to be no signs of intelligent life forms anywhere.
I will now analyze the air to see if it's breathable.
Hm,ahm... contains copious amounts of
oxygen... but
I think I should be okay.
I will now remove my helmet...
Let record show that I'm super ahead of schedule.
As the ship's head shience officer
I will now scout the surrounding areas
looking for any and all signs...
[sounds of animals]
Mission log.
I think I just heard a spooky noise!
And against my basic instincts
and everything that I learned at the academy training camp,
I will now approach the noise
for further investigation.
Alright noise:
On behalf of the galactic league of extraterrestrial exploration
I demand you to show yourself!
Pika pi! [reference to: Pokémon]
Aaaaaaaahhhh!
You are the cutest thing I've ever seen!
Mission log.
Total plot twist!
That creepy noise I thought I heard
turned out to be the cutest effin' noise I've ever seen!
Mission log:
Get out! there are more of 'em.
My stars!
I seem to have landed in a field of these aminals!
Hi! And what's your name?
[noises]
Oh, I'm February!
Mission log. I've successfully made contact with the planet's indigenous life forms!
And they are ultra friendly!
In my professional opinion
this planet is ready for human colonization by...
this afternoon!
That is if that's alright with all you.
[noises]
Oh, I'm so glad to hear it.
You see,
today is a really big day for me.
Can I tell you guys something?
See, you might not believe this,
but this is my first mission.
Yeah. It's my chance to proof to everyone back home that
I am smart enough to get the job done.
Yeah.
And you know, back at the academy
I finished the last in my class.
But it wasn't my fault! I mean how did they expect me to pass all those tests
if I didn't know any of the answers?
But being here with all of you guys,
it just really makes me feel like I'm doing something great!
Oh, hello!
Are you alright?
HOLY SHIT,
IT'S A BUUUUUG!!!!
Was that thing what I thought that thing was?
I don't know.
But we better get it back to the boss.
Come on!
So.
First day being a wrangler bug, huh?
Yeah...
I just got assigned this morning... [sigh]
Hey why the long slime hole?
Well, I just really had my dorsal tube set on being
nourishment.
Oh, I see.
Hey! Well, did you know that every egg in our swarm
starts out
by parasitically chest eating in one of these mammals?
And who do you think wrangles those mammals?
Mammal wranglers?!?
Ha! That's right!
The whole process starts with us!
So, you still think being a wrangler is lame?
No! Now I think it's kind of neat!
Yep, it sure is.
-Now, come on! Let's go!
-Oh boy!
Starship 15A2!
Come in, Starship 15A2!
I need evac [military for evacuation]!
There are hostile eeky bugs down here!
Ah, where did it go?
Ey,
where's it go?
Me thinks it went that away!
I'm with you!
Alright. Are you ready?
Now the first thing, you're gonna wanna do is lay down a base code of slime.
Go for it!
FML! [short for 'Fuck My Life']
Hey Mister, what are them weird noises coming out of its mouthparts?
Hey! We don't talk to them, we just wrangle them!
Now here's a tip:
Go ahead and secret a nice thick layer of mucus on to the mammals eyes
to temporarily blind it.
We find this relaxes the mammals.
HELP!!!
-HELP ME!!!!
-Hey, wow!
You're doing great!
Are you sure this is your first wrangle?
You're just saying that...
Hey! I don't just say stuff.
Now come on, let's get her back to the hive.
Starship Rangers!!!
I need the Starship Rangers!!!!