Right away.
Thank you.
If Ani is gone back home that means he's returned to Tatooine.
So that's where I'm headed.
And nothing is going to trip me up!
Reporting for duty, Sir!
Emily!
I hear you need a ride to Tatooine.
So you're the first pilot that they found? What is the chance of that?
Ahm -
Yes.
Well,...
I - I look forward to riding you to Tatooine. I mean -
You'll ride me to Tatooine. I mean -
Oh dear!
We're now approaching the surface of Tatooine.
Begin docking procedure into the space port of Mos Eisley.
Alright Mara, you'll stick with me.
Okay.
I'll show you the ropes.
I grew up on the mean streets of Tatooine.
Gotta watch yourself.
Lot of crazy characters around here.
I'm back on track
Ready for the world to come at me
I'm stepping up to bet
Not gonna let anything get past me
I've got my eyes on the prize
Gonna do what's right
Take what's mine
Strike back!
Hey, look at these guys!
Ani?
Well, [???] fellows, look!
Ani's back!
Hey, don't let me interrupt, keep going.
You know these guys?
Of course! The old Cantina band!
I swear they get better and better every year.
Say, can I have a smoke?
Five, four, three, two, one chance
Is all you get
To show the world your best
You better make the most of it
You gotta go for it
No one's gonna do it for you
No one's gonna hold your hand
You gotta understand
Enough is never enough
Strike back
So you guys like Star-Wars jokes?
You know!
Oh, great!
So I have talked to a group of Tusken Raiders and I say: Wow! Those [???] Banthas are really tough to take care of.
They say: Tell me about it, they shit about four times a day.
I say: Don't tell me you guys count Dooku.
I don't get it, Ani.
Well, come on, Count Dooku was a Sith Lord in the clone wars and Dooku kind of sounds like dookie.
Which is another way of saying poop.
It's a double meaning.
Humorous play on words, and -
that's where the comedy comes in.
Yeah, I understand.
I just don't get why it's funny.
Would you sing the song or something?
Oh yeah...
Cause you gotta face your fears
You gotta fight for what you believe in
And you forget about your tears
Cause it's time for you to do something
Strike back
Strike back!
Yeah!
Hey, how is it going guys? Hey wait a minute, who was touching my butt?
Me! Me, me. Me!
I hate that guy.
Ugh! Loud...
Ani???
Oh my god! Ani Skywalker?
You fat bastard, come here!
Ahaha! Boby Fett!
How in the heck are you? Why, I haven't seen you since that day in the arena, remember this?
When Mace Windu gave your paps the old shave and a haircut?
Oh Yeah!
Those were some good times.
Hey,
How is old Mace nowadays?
Papi and I threw him out of a window years ago, Bob - should have been there. It was a hoot and a half.
Ani!
Ani, you are looking good my friend!
What brings you back to these parts, eh?
Well, Bob, you're gonna think I'm crazy, but ah -
The Boonta-Eve's coming up and...
Oh yeah! You need tickets, right? Listen:
You call me!
I'll get you the best deal on box seats. You and your lady.
Oh.
No, Boba, it's not like that. I mean my wife's dead, but ah -
she's not gone, you know?
Oh yeah?
You sure about that?
You've been feeding her the old lines? Hey, this guy call you an angle?
No. No. We're just friends.
No, we're just friends. I'm old enough to be her father in law.
You know Mara's - actually is to be a slave girl at Jabba's palace. You know, Bob works for Jabba.
Really? Could you get me an audition?
I'm just kidding. But like, could you?
Yeah,  yeah -
I'll see what I can do.
Now Ani. These tickets man...
Won't be needing them, Bob. I was actually thinking about -
entering.
Racing again.
[Boba laughs]
This guy! This guy always with the jokes!
Hey Ani, what was that joke about the Wampa? I never understood it, but Wampas are funny to me.
It's no joke, Bob, I'm serious.
I really wanna do this, look -
I'm not looking to win or anything, just wanna be in the pod again.
Alright, alright, hey, you ah -
you take care of yourself, alright?
If you ever need anybody bounty hunted or disintegrated you call me.
[???]
[???] Bobarina.
Alright, bring it in the air, Ani.
And ah -
Ani, old pal -
here's 50 bugs.
Oh Bob, I can't take this.
Ani, republic credits are no good here, you know that, take the money.
Well, thanks Bob.
Alright. You'll take care now.
That's Bob. He's a little rough around the edges, but he's a softy.
Eh!
You!
You think you could bring your sourly butt back around here and the threes of us wouldn't hear about it?
I don't think so!
Sorry, pal!
Hey guys, I don't know you, but I'm not looking for a fight or anything.
[talking across each other]
Yeah!
Now make way!
Make way!
For the master of disaster!
No, not him!
Talking 'bout the harbinger of BOOOM!
It's my greatest enemy.
The podracing champ of the galaxy.
Sebulba!
Okay, okay, I get I put on a few pounds, so what?
Ani, that's your greatest enemy?
Oh yeah, without a doubt.
He's just a weird little thing!
He's not a thing, He's a Dug.
A particularly dangerous Dug named Sebulba.
Let me explain what just [???]
I - I think I got it.
Oh, you speak Dug?
I speak budgie.
[???] to Dug.
Yeah.
So we are cool just to talk, and...
Everybody will understand everything?
- Yeah boy!
- Yeah
Okay, great.
Yeah.
Oh yeah? Well let's just see who wins the Boonta-Eve THIS year, buddy!
Settle down, I'm not looking for a fight or anything, I just wanna compete.
Besides, you and I both know the chance of me winning this thing are one in a million.
Ahm - In your dreams, pal. In your dreams.
Hey, don't talk to her like that!
We will take you on right now, Sebulba! I'll take on you!
No!
Mara, not here.
They've got the high ground.
Don't listen to him, Ani.
My, he's right.
I'll never fit in my old pod again.
But it's not cause I got fat. It's cause I was laid the last time I raced.
Yeah.
Of course I'm not gonna fit, I knew that going in, I'm gonna have to make it - bigger.
Well, I can help you with that and I can stay and help you train.
No, no, Mara, you go to Jabba's palace, you do what you came here to do.
I wish you luck, but -
You don't need any/Ani.
I'm the one that needs all the luck.
Thanks, Ani.
Hey Ani?
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
Absolutely.
I let to know a friend of mine. He's living on Tatooine now.
He'll be all the help I need.
He's the best friend I ever had.
And the funniest guy I ever met.
Aaaah...!