You son of a...
You son of a bitch!
Joey, I'm sorry.
No!
No, no, no!
You dumb dick! You're ruining my life. You're ruining my whole damn life.
Well, yeah. But…
- ...but not on purpose.
- What the hell, man? What the hell?
I don't know. It didn't feel right.
Right?
Right.
Getting a boner...
...in class is not right.
Getting a boner while my doctor is giving me the cough test, is that right?
But getting a boner while I'm about to have sex with the girl I love...
...is the only right time to have a boner, you asshole.
Hey, don't compare me to those guys! I said I was sorry.
You even had a boner with Sally today, arrgh!
So, what wrong with that?
Excuse me?
What's wrong with that is...
...that Sally is a gross ass Sally.
Vanessa...
...is the hottest bitch I've ever seen.
She is the hot little Jewish girl.
Okay, I know.
Look Joey: if you wanna try to have sex again, ...
...maybe Sally is not such a bad idea.
I mean, okay, yeah I know, she's a Sally. But...
...her Miss Cooter...
...she's something kinda...
...something.
I hate you.
What?
I hate you. You're nothing to me.
Joey, don't say that.
I wish I were born without a dick.
Or as a girl or something.
Well, ...
...I wish...
...that I wasn't the dick of someone who's such a smartass all the time!
You go to hell.
- Hey, hey hey! Where do you think you're going?
- I go and find Miss Cooter.
- She's the only person who understands me.
- Oh no, you're not! We're going back to Vanessa's...
and we're gonna bend for forgiveness and you are gonna work this time!
No way, shithead! It's never gonna go down like that.
- I'm gonna find Miss Cooter!
- No, you're not!
Yes, I am!
No!
- Yes!
- No!
Yes!
I'm outta here.
Fine! [high pitched]
Get out.
Who needs you?
He's gone.
Oh, he's gone!
Why, hello there, Joey.
I thought that [???] would never leave.
Who are you?
Who am I?
Why, I'm you, Joey.
Or at least a part of you...
...that maybe you forgot about.
Here, ...
...pick a card.
- What's it say, kid?
- Three of clubs.
What?!? Give me that!
Sorry.
It's a new trick.
But just imagine who neat it would have been, if It had said this.
- Wow, the nine of hearts.
- That's right, the king of hearts.
I'm your heart, Joey.
Blood pumping extraordinairst.
Strongest muscle in your body and...
...certified expert in the field of love...
...and all things romantical. My degree.
- It's blank.
- Well, you don't need an degree...
...to know that everything you've been doing with this Vanessa girl is all wrong.
Stupidly wrong!
Dreadfully, dreadfully wrong, Joey!
Hey, I almost had sex with her!
Arrgh!
Wrong, Joey.
You just look like a boob.
While waving your...
...waving your wiener around in a base like a...
...like a hot dog bender.
With the hot dogs, Joey?
- Yeah.
[???].
Ugh!
Besides, Joey, ...
...girls don't mind to have sex.
It's a common misconception, made up by...
...somebody.
- Well, what do girls like?
- What do girls like?!? Joey, ...
...what do all of history's greatest lovers have in common?
Romeo and Juliet? Anthony and Cleopatra? Jack Dawson and Kate Winslet's character?
All the guys die horribly first.
Ahem... bad examples! But how about...
- ...Spiderman and Mary Jane?
- Oh, yeah! They work out perfectly.
They sure do.
What ties them together in a beautiful turn of fate, Joseph?
Romance, Joey. Romance.
- Romance.
- Something you're going to have to acquaint yourself with.
Here... read this! It's a Jane Austin novel, Joey.
Because if you want this Vanessa, you're gonna have to [???] the girl a bit.
Yeah, I don't know, Heart. I looked like a real jerkass back there, and I don't even think she likes me.
What?!?
Joey, that's silly.
You're just the cutest boy I've ever seen. With a...
- ...[???] I just wanna kiss.
- No, she hate me.
Oh, that's certainly possible.
But remember Joey, what Jane Austin once said:
Sometimes your one true love turns out to be the person you...
...initially...
...disliked.
- When did Jane Austin say that?
- In one of her [???].
I'm sure, Joey.
Now, Joey, just listen to me and I shan't stir you wrong.
- You're really help me get Vanessa?
- Absolutely!
Wow.
That's my boy, Joey. So what do you say?
Are you ready to romance this girl? Are you ready to give 223 percent to this effort?
- I sure am!
- Huzzar, Joey!
Now listen up! And listen good...
...as I illuminate the possibilities.
You look a little down, Joey.
You look a little blue.
It looks as though your dick has run a little way from you.
He hung you out to dry, Joey.
I think you will agree, ...
...the world would be much better, ...
...If you listened, a little bit, to me.
Listen to your heart, Joey. Listen to your heart.
Comb your hair and smile, that's a start.
Wipe that schmutz right off your cheek. Give her a glimpse of that fine physique.
And a splash of cologne will delight. Treat the lady right, Joey.
Treat the lady right.
Take off your hat and always be polite.
Offer your handkerchief, give her your pin.
Open the door when she wants to walk in.
Shell never resist, mon cheri. Take her to Paris.
And look up at the tower. Every night on the hour.
Let the lights have their way.
Take her in your arms. Speak of life and devotion.
Then propose by the ocean.
So she'll promise to stay.
So she won't go away.
Don't let her get away, Joey.
She can't get away!
Show her that you care, Joey. Show her that you care.
Pass her a note that says: "You're beyond compare".
Make her a mix tape with songs about love. Knit her a sweater that fits like a glove.
The two of you will never be apart. Joey, listen to your heart!
Come on, boy. Come on.
How are you doing this?
But how am I doing that?
Then use your [???], Joey.
- Pretend you're a [???].
- But I don't have a [???].
[???]
- Oh my god, my heart is so talented.
- That's right.
Come on, kid. Bring it home!
And soon shell love us, like we love her.
Who knows what tomorrow could bring?
The time is right, to make your/my move.
It's time to give her the ring.
- So, Joey. What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna listen to my heart.
- Oh buddy, it's my big debut.
You're gonna listen, ...
...listen...
...to your...
...heart.