Hey Nessi, Nessa, my loveless monster.
I've got a surprise for you, hold on.
Flopsy, what's with the long face?
I mean I've seen some salad pussies in my day, but you - you take the cake!
I am upset with Vanessa...
...and I am not speaking to her!
Still sour about that new dick coming your way?
Honey, I am still sour from the last one.
So I was kinda afraid you might go all [???] on me and have a spasm attacks, ...
...so I brought you something that's totes gonna get you through this.
Ta-ta-ta-da!
What's that?
It's a box of all the essential tools you need to make...
...any guy go 'Lady Gaga' in a matter of minutes.
Have a look, see!
Uh, these always working perfect for me.
Oh, you know...
No, no, nyeah, no.
But the [???]...
The guy at the liquor store totally has the [???] hots for me.
And sold me this!
What's that?
It's beer, you fucking hipster!
If the night is turning into an epic fail, ...
...take a couple of these and you'll win-win-win.
Oh, I'm so corrupting you right now and I love it!
- Oh, but - I do gotta go.
- Okay.
I told that Sally guy I'd meet him at the library.
- Bye, good luck.
- Bye.
- And text me once you start fucking!
- Yeah.
This is just fine. I'm about to be reduced to a sperm hotel.
- Flopsy, face it. That's how it's always turns out for us broads.
- Yeah.
Just keep a stiff outer lip...
...and try to enjoy it before you go completely numb inside.
I mean that literally.
- Sure.
-Toodles, doll.
- Okay.
- Don't be a stranger.
- Never!
So, ahem...
Nessa?
- What are you playing at?
- Well, ...
- ...Joey is coming over soon and we're supposed to be studying.
- Oh, studying. Yeah, okay. Cool.
You've got condoms in that box?
Yeah.
Puh! You gonna need condoms for studying all the sudden? Why is that?
I don't know, Flopsy. Look, I've gotta do something to get back at Rick. I just -
I look at him and I get these pains in my chest. I can't eat, I can't sleep...
You think you've got it bad?
Try getting a full eight hours, ...
- ...when you're being pounded by penises.
- Oh, Flopsy, look...
Just - this is very important to me. Maybe to get back at Rick, ...
...maybe I'll proof to myself, that I can get with someone who isn't him.
So would you please -- just try to be nice and help me out here a little.
- It really means a lot to you, huh?
- Yes, it does.
Well, when you look at me with those puppet [???] eyes, what am I supposed to do? Okay, yes. Alright.
- Thanks Flopsy.
- Just remember: I'm doing it for you, ...
...not some nasty old penis!
You are the best vagina I've ever had.
Sing it, sister.
Let me dust off a few of my old trick and maybe I'll pick up a trick or two from that hip young Liza Minelli.
- Let's go practice in front of the mirror.
- Just like the old days.
Hey, dude, do you think 24 condoms will be enough for one night?
I mean like: how often to you replace them, every like, every like, ...
- ...two or three minutes or so?
- Yeah, I think so.
I'll throw in another 30 pack, just in case.
If she wants to go to ‘over time', you know?
Have you seen my body spray?
Oh yeah, I think it's underneath the sofa.
Oh cool. Can't forget this either.
Hey, Joey, uhm...
I just wanted to apologize for earlier.
Yeah, when you jumped out of my pants and touched a kid.
Come on dude. I mean at least like - you know - make it a girl.
Yeah.
Actually I ahem... I was talking about Sally.
Sally?
Aww, come on, dude. You don't need to apologize for that. I'm used to getting boners at really, ...
...really, really inappropriate times. So, you know...
...at least it was with someone I care nothing about.
Yeah.
But you know, ahem... well, you guys, ...
...you guys hugged so close that I actually ah...
...well, I actually meet her Miss Cooter.
Her what?
Her Miss Cooter.
- She's actually a really nice vagina.
- Yeah?
And she's super sassy, ...
...she's got this cute southern accent.
And she's got long beautiful flowing hair.
On her vagina?!?
Yeah.
It works somehow.
Speaking of which, I think that Sally is dyeing her hair.
Which reminds me that maybe...
...maybe we shouldn't completely rule out having sex with...
...Sally.
- Sex with Sally? With salad Sally?
- Yeah.
That's disgusting, are you nuts?
A little.
Listen, dick, ...
...I know that was the closest thing you've come to a vagina since you came out of them.
It was an extremely close hug and I apologize.
But no matter how much you like that Cooter, ...
...she's always gonna be the bowl to a larger salad.
With spinach, beets, little carrots...
...and all that other shit we don't eat.
We have been waiting years for a moment like this.
Years!
And if you like Sally's Miss Cooter, just think how great Vanessa's is gonna be.
It's gonna be the most glorious, gracious, delicious, filet mignon vagina you've ever seen.
And you're gonna be on the plate with the mashed potatoes, and the veggies, and you mix them all together...
with the filet mignon, and you bite in a little veg in there, even though...
- ...you don't like ‘em, you'll eat them anyway.
- Yeah, so good.
- [???]. It's pink.
- Oh, pink! -
It's great. It's gonna be great!
I know. Trust me, it's gonna be awesome!
You're right, Joey. I don't know what I was thinking.
Right, now. Trying to getting a sexy time now.
I need to know, that you're on my side.
Joey!
I'm your dick! I'm always on your side. We're an unstoppable force.
We're like Batman and Robin.
Or Superman...
...and his dick.
Well, that's all I needed to hear.
So, let's put on our Roller-blades, skate on down to Vanessa's, ...
...kick down that door, slowly take off of her shirt...
- ...and fuck her ‘till we're man.
- Nice!