- Oh, there you are.
- So sorry.
Wow. I was beginning to think I was gonna have to do this project on my own, huh?
I wouldn't totally give up on that idea.
So, what are we doing here? A posterboard? A video on Spanish? What's up?
Well, actually the idea that I had with Joey was that we work on a soulable compound...
...such as silver nitrate for example, AgNO3, except we make ours a film noir detective type story...
...with elements.
Oh, like Saw!
Uhm, no.
Let me explain: See, the trend film noir is used to describe a stylish Hollywood crime drama, ...
...mainly popular in the 40th and 50th...
[Miss Cooter is humming "I've seen you around here before"]
Pst! Hey kid!
Kid.
You're gazing out in the space like you see a bunch of Martians out there.
What gives?
Were you talking to me?
I couldn't hear you over the sweet sound of love in the air.
Oh-oh(s). It's worse than I thought(s).
Martians I can handle, but love, uagh!
That's a threat you can't fight off with a bunch of rough fighter jets and a Will Smith taking care of it.
So, may I be so bald(s) ass to ask(s) whom...
...or what says you wouldn't search rare forms?
Ah, it is some handsome young packer I've met today.
Here(s) we go(s).
And by packer, I assume you're referring to a p-p-p-p-p-p-p...
A cock.
A cock? [???] is more I like it.
Man, I just can't stop thinking about him.
I'll tell you something, honey.
I've seen a lot of dicks in my day. I mean...
...a shit load of dicks.
I believe you, I believe you.
Of course you do. I'm the Old Snatch, everyone believes me.
I've seen every shape and size...
...from here to Timbuktu(s).
And you know what I learned about them?
They're nothing...
...but a bunch of bumps!
All of them!
All they care about is taking a dip in our secret sauce.
Yeah, they might say pretty things, uagh!
But every one of them bump(s) let(s) me down(s).
No ma'am! No ma'am, you are wrong.
My dick is different.
Miss Cooter, ...
...let me tell you a thing or two about dicks.
Take those:
A dick can act real sweet.
A dick can bat his eyes.
He can tell you you're the one...
...but that dick's just full of lies.
A dick's a dick's a dick's a dick's a dick, it's true.
But you ain't never gonna find the dick for you.
- A dick can hit you hard.
- Ooh, a dick can hit you fast.
- A dick can bring you love.
- But that dick won't make it last.
There's a dick for every puss alots of fish in the sea.
But they sure as hell haven't found a dick for me.
- There ain't nothing like a dick.
- And the dick I found is the best!
There ain't nothing like a dick. They leaving you itching with a rash.
You can play with a dildo 'til it makes you sick. But at the end of the day, there ain't nothing like a dick.
Now you're getting it, Miss Cooter. Preach baby, preach!
My Dick's a different breed. He's got class he's debonair.
His voice is gravelly and soft. And baby, he's got quite a pair!
When he talks to me I get all hot and bothered, you see.
I'm positive that he's the only dick for me!
Ooh, that dick's got you good. He's got you under his spell.
Well, at least I have a dick. And at least I don't smell.
Make the same mistakes, through thin and through thick. But at the end of the day, there ain't nothing like a dick.
- I want that shaft in me today.
- There ain't nothing like a dick.
Hey look, a baby on the way.
- Ooo, the way he makes me feel.
- Oh, they sure(s) are(s) slicks.
But at the end of the day there ain't nothing - like a dick!
And they'll fuck ya too!
You know something, kid?
You're alright! God!
I haven't had that much fun since I was a tiny [???].
Oh god!
- Help! Help! Help!
- Oh, shit. One, two, three...
Ah, there it is.
So tell me.
Who's this Schmendrick that(s) got you so confound?
Just the dick of one Joey Richter.
Do(es) my ears deceive(s) me?
Did you just say Joey Richter(s)?
The very same, why?
No, kid.
I don't know how to break this to you, but...
...that Dick is playing you like a fiddle!
For a sap!
What are you going on about?
You old snatch?
That's right, I am the old snatch.
Kid(s), I got the forewarn once that...
...one Joey Richter(s) is doing the horizontal hockey pockey with one Vanessa.
On this very night.
I don't know what that Dick told you, Miss Cooter.
But it aren't(s) the truth.
He's a no good two timing bump!
- Just like the rest.
- No, I don't believe you.
- That's impossible.
- Oh, you must really be wet.
Behind the ears.
Quit naiveté!
I had a dick like yours once.
Ah, my first time.
Made me feel like I was the only vagi(s) in the world(s).
Real special, until...
Until what?
Well, ...
...one day he was there, and the next - he(s) was gone(s).
Without a word.
Left me high(s) and dry(s).
And I haven't seen him since.
Well, I feel real bad for you.
But that ain't gonna be my story.
I sure hope(s) you're right, kid. I sure hope(s) you're right.
…and it's only when the silver and the nitrogen find all three oxygen's. Then they solve the case!
Oh, I'm pulling up. I'm pulling.
It's a text message from Nessy, thank god!
Can you please answer that later?
Oh, I would, but Nessy's in a really delicate situation and might need some of my sexpertise.
What does Vanessa need sex expertise for?
She's working on her project with Joey.
Sally, you are smarter then you look.
Oh... alright. I don't want to give out too many dets, 'cause Nessy's like my best [???]...
...and I don't wanna break her trust, but...
...she's hooking up with Joey right now!
Wha... wha... what does Vanessa see in Joey Richter?
Why do you think she want to work on this project with him?
Anything can happen during a school-project.
Thank you for your time and your precious day!
I'm going to work on this project by myself!
Cool.
See(s), I told you, kid.
- They're all the same.
- No, you shut up!
I don't know what's going on with my packer right now, but I do know, what I felt.
What we felt! And it's something so special that probably no one else...
...in this entire universe has ever felt so before!
Nobody except the millions stupid enough to believe a dick.
No. You just want everybody to be as miserable as you are, 'cause...
...you're a worn out, smelly old, mean old snatch!
Come on, Sally!
Damn!
She's right(s).