Hello?
Hey Vaness, OMG, would you guess, that I'm not wearing undies today?
Eww. Oh Tiff, LOL, what's the diff, you would still take 'em off anyway.
- IKR [I know, right]?
- BTW [By the way],
Where are you right now?
- We need to talk.
- Oh, I totes see you.
BRB, ciao ciao. [Be right back]
How is you doing, Flopsy?
Oh, hey there, you old snatch!
- So, you know how the [???] act party at my house this weekend?
- Yeah.
- I hooked up with the [???].
- Really? I've heard you hooked up with the running [???].
Oh yeah. Him too!
- Sounds like you had a rough weekend.
- Ah, no. It's just business as usual and [???].
I tell you, I've been with so many members of the football team, ...
- ...they're gonna give me an honorary position.
- Oh yeah?
What position they're gonna give ya?
Wide receiver.
I thought you was gonna say: tight pants.
Oh honey, it's been a long time since I've been a tight anything.
Now, who am I kidding? What position haven't I tried?
When you've been around the block as much as I have.
- You feel just like a CEO.
- How's that? That must feel good.
You see, I'm done with all these cocks, but they're not letting me retire.
I tell ya, I'm ready to go!
Tiff, you gotta stop playing with all these stupid guys. They have feelings, you know?
Oh, we are just having fun.
I guess you wouldn't know what that's like, cause you're in that whole relationships thing.
- And that's me: Miss Monogamy.
- Let me tell you something, sweetie.
Just because there's one horse in this staple, it doesn't mean he don't care.
Flopsy! I didn't know you listen to horse riding.
I... what?!? I AIN'T! The horse has been riding me!
I tell you, you old snatch, you're lucky.
- Oh, I'm one? Oh, I'm one? Me?
- Yeah, you are. Yeah. Yeah!
This ought to be rich. Why's that?
Well, let me tell ya.
It's like living the same way that an old pair of shoes do.
Every day's a one man show.
They start to stink, and then there's holes, and they don't FIT the way they used to.
I've had it! I'm ready to go.
Look at us.
- We're just a couple of stiffs.
- Now you're just being cute.
- With a lifetime of if's.
- Don't be so hard on us.
And I wonder, with someone else, ...
...could life be more fair?
- It's not like we're some one-dick pony.
- Oh, now you're being cute.
We could be more, if only...
...someone out there, would answer our prayers!
While(s) we(s) wait(s) to be delivered. Go ahead, cry me a river.
We agree that there's no 'quid pro quo'.
- So until that great vacation.
- Save your tears for lubrication.
And lord have mercy, are we ready to go!
Mercy, are we ready to...
...go.
So what's up with you and Rick? You guys [???] separately [???] to school today.
- Is everything okay?
- Oh-oh, shouldn't have said that.
No, it's not. We... He and I actually... broke up.
- Here comes the waterfall.
- Okay, pinky-swear you won't spread this around!
I heard from Stacy that Daphne was with Valerie when she saw Rick - cheating on me!
It's that...! It's like the best thing that's ever happened to me. I'm on vacation!
WT...
FUCK!
Oh, that asshole!
You know what you need to do?
- You need to re-cheat that motherfucker, for the win.
- What?
- You need to find a guy.
- What? Why do I fell like I'm gonna get the short end of this?
Not just any guy. A guy who's barely existence will drive Rick insane.
He should be like a total loser.
[???] a definite step down.
Like...
- ...like that guy!
- Joey Richter?!?
He's perfect. This is gonna be so epic.
I don't know if I can just hook up with some random guy and revenge.
Uh uh. Epic revenge!
Listen up, Vanessa, sweetie.
- I do this 'cause I care.
- I know.
This is war. Forget your peace treaty. Justice is right over there.
I guess I could use a new guy. ‘Cause it's been a while...
...and I am still so young. Why not give it a try?
At the very least it could be kinda fun.
Hey now, Vanessa, that's the girl I know and love.
I've been so boring, boy I'm glad - I had a little shove!
Tick tock, while the iron's hot. There's no time to take it slow.
We gotta be ready, so ready to go.
I'm ready to go.
We're finally ready and the time is right for us to light a spark.
We're keeping it steady. With our eyes on the prize, to get us through the dark.
I know there's so much more to what I think I see.
I feel a change, and the strange thing is: it's part of me!
My hormones are freaking out, and I think I'm gonna blow!
- We're locked and loaded.
- Oh, so devoted.
- Low and demoted.
- Totes, just toted!
We're finally ready, so ready to go!
Alright, let's go to class.