I wake up in the morning.
And it's nothing new.
You run through my mind for hours.
Still I just want you.
You're all I want, you're all I need.
My love for you just grows the way you do!
When I love you!
I wanna hold you all night long...
...and cuddle 'til we're blue.
Hold you in a tight embrace, ...
...I know it seems taboo.
But I have to have you with me now.
I have to have you quick.
I love you more than anything, ...
...my Dick!
Hello!
Good morning, Joey.
Well, speak of the devil.
Oh I've been up for a while
but I didn't want to wake you.
When mum walked in -  I just said: Hi.
Dick, I told you: If you wake up before me and someone comes in, just roll us over onto the side.
No one is supposed to see you, especially my mum.
Geez, Joey. How is a guy supposed to have a sex-life around here, if you keep him covered up all the time?
I mean, I'm feeling a little [???].
You want to have sex with my mum?
Maybe.
Joey, I'm kidding!
I don't wanna have sex with mum. Dad would ground us.
But seriously, we've gotta punch in that V-Card sooner or later.
I mean, you're a senior in high school and never even seen a booby.
- But...
- A girl booby.
Well, you don't think I wanna have sex?
Did it ever occur to you that it's hard for a boy to loose his virginity...
...when he's the biggest looser in school, because he has an out-of-control dick...
...that always gets me into trouble?
Joey! You're not a looser.
It's just that nobody really likes you.
- Good grief.
- Aww, I'm sorry. I don't mean to be dick.
But hey: Look at the bright side.
- I like being with you.
- You like being with me.
Were just the best of friends.
As anyone can see.
People say: 'It’s quite unlikely'. The two of us should stick.
But I just tell them:
Hey! It's me and my dick!
Sorry about this, Joey, but I kinda drooled on your sheets last night.
Oh, come on! I just washed those!
Well, sorry! But I'm not the one that's having sexy dreams about that hot little Jewish girl from school.
Oh yeah. Vanessa.
You're doing it again! You're [???].
It's not just ass. Instead she's cute and fun and...
- intellectual...
- And hot and little and Jewish. I know.
She's got those dancing legs, those nice round...
...BOOBIES!
Oh, alright, alright, alright, Dick. Just calm down. Besides: she's got a boyfriend!
And they've been dating for three years.
And she'll probably gonna get married to him and have a million little babies that are all...
...hotter and more Jewish than I am.
Woah, woah woah. Where do you think you're going?
You've got to take care of this, you got me all exciting!
Dick, we don't have time today!
It'll hurt if you don't!
Okay!
- We'll stick together.
- Fight through thick and thin.
- Fight through thick and thin.
If we stay side by side, there’s no way we can't win.
- Any girl that’s out there.
- Any girl that’s out there.
- Any girl at all.
- Any girl at all.
When she gets going with us she's sure to have a ball!
Hey!
Be careful with that joke.
It’s an antique!
People say: 'How do you do it? How can you be so slick?'
But I just tell them:
Hey! It's Me and My Dick!
- Yeah, there she is.
- Oh I see her.
Leaning on her locker with those big brown eyes.
- And she's taking off her shirt and her pants.
- Yeah keep going!
And we're doing a sexy-time dance!
And she’s running her hands, down my underpants!
Buddy, this is our chance!
Joey! Are you ready to go to school?
Yeah, hold on!
Ugh, is that ugly-face Sally, your ugly-faced neighbor?
- Get her out of here!
- Shut up! [whispered]
Joey, I just wanted to let you know, that...
...in order to not be late for school we should have left seven minutes ago.
- Okay, Sally. I'll be done in just a second.
- Okay, I'll just be waiting for you outside of your house.
- Okay.
Geez, Joey! You've got to get some drapes for that window! I'm sick of all these interruptions.
- I was just about to cum....
- Joey! I just wanna let you know, ...
...you can take as much time as you need. And if we're late for class, I guess that's okay.
- Okay! Okay. Fine, Sally. Shut up! Shut up!
- Okay.
- Is she gone?
- Yeah. I'm gone.
Yeah, she's gone.
Alright. Well let's keep going!
- I don't know, Dick. I'm not in the mood any more.
- WHAAAT?!?
Why the hell not?
Well, because all I can think about is Sally.
And that's just the least sexy thing I can ever think about.
Joey! Now you got me thinking about her.
I'll never gonna  be able to cum now. I'll never gonna be able to cum ever again!
Ugh Sally, uh! She's so...
She's just like -! And you know I'm like: - !
I can't even describe her with words! It's like she's just - she's just a Sally.
Exactly, she's just a Sally.
Sally!
I know exactly what you mean. But, hey man, we've got to get ready for school.
You made me tardy for class three times last week.
Class! I hate class!
Huh, whatever Joey. You know we don't go to school for class.
We go to school - for ass!
Hey, I've got an idea. Why don't you introduce me to Vanessa?
- No!
-  Come on, it'll be fun.
All you have to do is cut a hole in this box. And...
...put me in the box and then give it to Vanessa.
And then she'll open the box and I'll pop out and I'll say:
'Hello! It's sausage pizza!'
- That's the stupidest idea I've ever heard.
- What?
One: She has a boyfriend.
Two: She probably won't even open the box.
Well, that's ridiculous. Of course she'll open the box. Jewish girls love pizza.
The only thing that Jewish girls love more than pizza...
...is big sausage pizza!
- No?
- No.
Fine, you don't like that idea. Whatever! Forget about that, I've got a billion of them.
So you really like this Vanessa girl, huh?
Yeah, more than anything. She's the girl of my dreams.
Well, Joey, I want you to be happy. Cause when you're happy, I'm happy.
Joey, I'm your dick! I love you!
And you know, I know that sometimes I get you into hilarious misadventures.
But I just want you to know that - well, I'm always gonna be there, buddy.
I know.
So what do you say that we stop taking the shaft and we grab life by the balls?
- Yeah!
- Yeah! So who cares if Vanessa has got a boyfriend? Screw him!
What does that asshole deserve her more than us?
That's right! We're gonna win her over.
Joey, I'm gonna get you laid if I have to do it myself.
Thanks, buddy. Up-top!
People say: 'It’s quite unlikely'. The two of us should stick.
But I just tell them: Hey! It's me and my dick!
- I like being with you.
- It's me and my dick.
- We'll stick together.
- Hey man.
- It's me and my dick.