Scene four:
[sobbing]
Lights up on the girl's bathroom.
[more sobbing]
Noooooo...
Prrrreeeeeeaaaaasse!
[Reference to: Who framed Roger Rabbit]
Please don't let it be tru-uh-uh-ue!
Hey!
Shut up over there!
People are trying to use this bathroom, and they're not doing it!
And I think it's your fault!
I - I'm sorry, Moaning Myrtle.
I'm just h - heart-bro-ken!
Oooooohhhhh!
Oooooohhhhhh!
poor Baby!
Harry Potter's girlfriend is sad.
Because she's still alive!
Does Baby want some wine with that cheese?
Oh, f*** you!
I guess that's it!
I'm not Harry Potter's girlfriend anymore!
I might as well be dead!
Well, don't do it here!
The last thing this castle needs is a whiny bitch,
stalking the hallways and the bathrooms. And your voice is annoying!
Okay...
Diary time.
Okay... Dear diary,
It's me.
Ginny uuuh!
Today my whole world fell apart.
My boyfriend dumped me!
And you know what?
I'm done with him!!!
*harrumph*
I hate him!
Do you hear me, diary???
I HATE HARRY POTTER!!!
[Laughter out of thin air]
Tell me about it.
Huuuuuh???
Huuuuh?
Who said that?
Somebody who understands you, Ginny.
Somebody who knows what it's like to be filled... with hate!
Diary...?
I'm a journal.
Not a diary, diaries are for girls.
But yes, Ginny.
I'm a magic diary - Shit! Journal!
I'm a magic journal.
Enchanted with the spirit of it's former owner.
Harry?
No!
But Harry gave it to me.
*sigh* read the name on the cover, stupid.
Oh. Okay.
Tom!
Mar...Mar...Marvel... Mar... Mar...
Okay, just... *sigh* just skip that name.
It's a made up name for this letter re-arranging trick. You'll... you'll find out later, just...
Go to... Go to the next name!
Oh! Ridle! [No mistake ;-)]
...Yeah. Tom Riddle!
I'm a piece of his soul.
Separated from the whole and bound to this diary. Shit! Journal!!!
Bound to this f****** JOUR-NAL!!!
Oh, but what do you want, diary?
To help you, Ginny.
That's what journals are for.
See: I once was like you.
Alone,
angry,
The world had... turned it's back on me.
Oh, what did you do, diary?
Let me show you...
In a magic flashback...
It all started, when I was a boy.
An orphan boy
[Reference to: A Very Potter Musical]
Lights down on Ginny.
Lights up on the magic flashback.
We find ourselves at Wool's orphanage.
Many years ago.
I think you'll find Wool's orphanage is a first rate establishment.
We have seven different breeds of orphan
including street urchin,
rosy cheeked,
delightfully small,
and one little evil telekinetic Antichrist.
Now, what was it you're interested in today, Mr. ...
Dumbledore! Albus Dumbledore.
But you could call me Dumby.
Or ah... Big D.
[Reference to: A Very Potter Sequel]
You know, ah... The D stands for, aaah...
...my doctorate.
I'm a Professor at a school for very magical children, ah f***ing shit!
I mean: Very regular children.
oh!
Well, you're in luck, big D, because we've plenty of those in stock, follow me.
Yeah, well just listen doll-face: I'm here to see one little cutie in particular.
That ah... Tom Riddle!
I think he might be just right for our school.
Oh... Tom...
...Riddle... ?!?
Suit yourself.
But I warn you: This boy's a monster!!!
Tho- Thomas...
You ha... you... you have a visitor, Professor Dumbledore.
How do you do, Tom?
Professor?
Like a Doctor?
So they've come here to take... a look at me, have they?
Well, there's nothing wrong with me!
Just stop shouting, Mr. man! He is from a school!!!
He might just take you off my hands, you filthy little heathen...
Thank you very much, Mrs. Cole! I think I can take it from here, now get the hell out of here, please.
Why don't you get out of here too?
You're not gonna want me.
She's right, you know?
I'm evil.
You are not evil, Tom.
Yes, I am. Mrs Cole told me.
That my mummy died when I came out of her tummy.
The first thing that I ever did was kill somebody.
Well, Tom, you know sometimes...
...sometimes you accidentally kill your family.
It's nothing to beat yourself up about.
Hey!
Listen:
You know who accidentally killed his sister while he was in a fight with his boyfriend?
This guy right here.
You've killed people too?
Oh yeah, tons of times!
But it doesn't make me bad.
And it doesn't make YOU  bad! There are just...
...some things you don't know about yourself yet.
All you need is a big, strong hand to put you on the right path.
Tell me, Tom: Do you ever feel like you're a little bit diffrent from the other little boys?
[Sound of agreement]
Sometimes you can make extra-special things happen, silly,silly funny things.
Well... Uh... sometimes when I'm really happy...
... I can shoot sparkles out of my fingers.
Gasp!
You know what that means? Tom! That means you're a magic boy!
What?!?
That means you're a magic boy, those sparkles from your hands! That's magic!
You're a wizard, Tom!
Oh boy! I knew I was special!
And you're gonna come with me and I'm gonna take you to a magical school for wizards with a silly name. You wanna know the name?
Uhu!
It's Hogwarts!
That's funny!
And at Hogwarts the professors are giant people and tiny people and werewolves and...
...cats!
And we play games! Oh! And there's no f***ing homework!
All we learn how to do is sing and dance!
YAY! YAHOO! Sparkles!!!
Tom! Look at that sparkling magic!
YAAAAY!
You look as gay as the fourth of July
[= Independence day in the USA, where it's very common to set off firework]
YAAY! I'm magic!
I'm gay!
Me toooooo!
Tom, from this moment forward you're turning over a new leaf!
Now you are a boy,
an orphan boy
And deep inside of you
A broken soul,
A gaping hole,
Has left you feeling blue
But you're not like the other boys,
You've got that magic flair!
'Cause when you start to sway
You get carried away
And no one can compare!
I've been watching your play,
I've been listening to the things that you say
And I've come to tell you today
You're no ordinary blighter.
You've got a broken heart
You keep reaching inside to tear it apart
But I'm here to give you a brand new start
and to make your spirit brighter.
When all the other boys start to laugh and jeer
I know a secret way you can make them disappear
You've got that talent, kid, so here is your chance:
They might not understand
But just stick to the plan
And show them all it's time to dance!
Always dance, always dance,
Though they'll try to stop you, always dance!
Shut your mouth and stop your yapping.
Take your foot and set it tapping.
You were born a magic boy, so leap and twirl and prance!
And Tommy, always dance!
Are you ready to go to Hogwarts?
I've been waiting to go
For how long, I really don't know
But one look at you and I know
That you would never fool me.
I've been living a lie
Ever since I made my poor mummy die
I've been softly wondering why
They all choose to ridicule me.
When all the other boys start to laugh and jeer
I know a secret way I can make them disappear
You've got that talent,  kid!
This is my chance!
They might not understand
But just stick to the plan
And show them all it's time to dance!
Always dance, always dance,
Though they'll try to stop you, always dance!
Shut your mouth and stop your yapping.
Take your foot and set it tapping.
You were born a magic boy.
I was born a magic boy, I leap and twirl and prance!
So Tommy, always dance!
Tommy you'll always dance!
Slytherin!
Wait Tom! Your sorting is not done yet! The scarf of sexual preference!
Oh! Interesting! I could see you going a number of ways.
Hello there.
Uhm, hi.
My name is Lucius. But you can call me Luey.
When I grow up, I want to be a rocket.
And I'm Trixie. I like Hogwarts 'cause there's lots of nice friends to make and yummy food to eat!
Are you making fun of me?
Noooo..?!? You wanna be friends?
Uhm... Back off!
Gasp! What a man!
We'll see how much of a man you are!
Care for a friendly dance-off?
Do I?
Why not. Yeah.
Hm... That's pretty good. But can you do... this?
Oh!
Look at his style!
Look at him go!
Watch his technique!
Check out his flow!
My, how he leaps!
Oh, what a prance!
Look at him, look at him, look at him dance!
Always dance, always dance,
Though they'll try to stop you, always dance!
Shut your mouth and stop your yapping.
Take your foot and set it tapping.
He was born a magic boy, so leap and twirl and prance!
Always, always, always, always, always, always dance!
So.
You see, Ginny,
when the world sucks...
...just dance.
And the world always sucks.
So, always dance.
Dance with me?
Oh boy, yeah!
You've got the talent, kid
So you're my nominee.
You may/might not understand.
But you will dance with me.
Al - ways - dance!
Always dance!
Though they'll try to stop us, always dance!
You were born for my controll
So step into my trance.
Always, always, always -
dance!
[evil laughter]