Scene five:
Lights up on Gilderoy Lockhart's autograph line.
Several kids wait to meet Gilderoy.
Including Hermione, who stands at the end of the line.
Gilderoy finishes signing a headshot for Luna.
There you are, miss Lovegood, thanks for stopping by.
Okay, who's next?
Oh, why, hello, Neville! It's nice to see a boy in my line for a change.
Oh, thank you, sir! Katniss Everdeen is my idol!
Here you are. Next!
Hello,... Gilderoy Lockhart.
Why, hello there. It's fourty Dollars for a headshot and thirty Dollars for an autograph.
If you could just sign my copy of 'breaking dawn' that would be great.
[Reference to: Third book of the Twilight-saga: Stephenie Meyer]
Oh, no, no, I only sign the fourty Dollar headshots.
Oh!...
So...
...really an autograph is just seventy Dollars.
Well, aren't you clever?
You must be Hermione Granger.
You know who I am?
Oh yes, Professor Flitwick says you're an aspiring young writer.
He says your translations of Beetle The Bard's boring stories had him on the edge of his seat.
And... that's saying something, because if that small man were to fall from a chair, he could die.
Oh...
Well, I don't know how good my writing is. I mean, that Beetle The Bard translation was just something silly for fun.
My...my true passion is... is fanfiction!
Based... [stops because of big cheerings from the audience]
Based on your work!
Oh, really?...
Yes! And in fact here's one fanfic I'm working on right now.
In it you're a captiol person and you are dating Effi Trinket, but then you fall in love with sort of massy underspoken Avox.
And then the Avox regains her ability to speak, and uh... she has a beautiful voice and, uhm...
she's kind of like the coolest girl in the whole wide world, so... If you wanted...
...to read it you could, butifyoudon'twanttoit'sokaytoo...
A mousy girl, eh?
Well, let's have a look see.
Hm...
uhum...
Oh...
O...Oh!
Oh my...!
Uh!...
Oh my god!
Hermione, this is absolutely deprived!
I love it!
Really?!?
Hell, yes!
This makes '50 shades of grey' look like a f***ing book for kids!
[Reference/Trivia: Emma Watson (Hermione in the 'HP'movies) was suspected to act in the movie '50 shades of grey'. She denied.]
With writing like this... with writing like this you could be going places.
I, in fact I have been looking for someone to write my autobiograph - I mean...
... my biography.
You mean me?
You would want ME to write YOUR story?
Perhaps...! But I'll need to see some more samples of your writing.
Oh, I can bring you some more of my fanfics!
I have this one where I'm Cato and you are one of the wolf-mutations, and you... graphically eat me...
...uhm...
among other things...
No, no! Fanfiction won't do. I, I need to see how you craft real life into drama.
Aaah, what do you say, you write me a few essays... on someone you know...
Someone at Hogwarts. So... I don't know...
Harry Potter?
Harry...?
But... Didn't you say yourself, sir, that Harry's life is repetitive and mundane?
Well, if you don't think you could do it, I suppose I'll have to find someone else, it s... sounds funny to say now, I...
I thought you were special.
I AM special!
No. You're not.
Yes! I am! I'll... do it!
I'll write about Harry!
Better, girl! Why don't you just write me an essay on each of Harry's years at Hogwarts?
Alright. I'll do it, Gilderoy Lockhart!
And I won't let you down. In fact: I'm gonna go get started right now.
[laughs]
If I'm going to win this head boy election I've got to have a strong campaign platform. Something like...
End house elf slavery!
Begin muggle and mudblood slavery!
Something inspiring like that. Goyle,
candy lady,
how are those campaign posters coming?
A candidate is only as good as his placards.
Goyle?
I drew an old, majestic owl.
Hm, yes...
Yes, it's a fine rendering, but, ahm...
It has very little to do with me... or... the election.
But, perhaps maybe if you had a speech bubble coming out of the owls mouth that said: 'Vote for Malfoy, he's a hoot!'
Hm...
I don't think the owl would say that.
And sometimes I think: Maybe... Ma...maybe Hermione doesn't want to kiss me...
... because... Oh my god! Do you think... do you think she likes someone else?
I don't know. Maybe she likes, ah... maybe she likes Fluffy?
They'd be a good couple, 'cuz they're both dogs.
Hooo!
Haha! Haha! Haha!
But you, you know, I'm just worried, 'cuz she's not hanging out around us lately, and she's so busy with those stupid books...!
Well, I mean... She better remember to do my potions essay, 'cuz it's... it's due tomorrow.
Hey! This looks like a good spot.
Huh?
Right here.
This looks like a really good spot, ah... Got the campaign poster?
Right here!
Great!
Alright, so the rules of this election are that you can only run positive campaigns, that's why no one's gonna be expecting this!
Good work, Mr. campaign manager! Now let's see who votes for Malfoy!
[laughter in witch Ron and Harry join in]
What are you... what are you laugh... what are you laughing at?
This!
What? Wait... why... hold on. What... What are you laughing at. This is...
Potter stinks? Haha! That's... Wait a sec... ey!
It's not funny at all! Wait, Lavender, where'd you get that button?
Someone's just passing them out to everyone in school.
WHO?!?
TELL ME!!!
Oh! That was really mean, Harry!
You stink! And not just 'cuz of your toots!
WHO MADE THAT PIN??? Ron! Do I smell like toots?
Well, dO I?!?
No! No! No. No...
Why is everybody saying I stink? Who's responsible for this?
Hm...
Malfoy is a snobbish, racist, elitist brat. Hm...
Sums up my entire campaign perfectly.
Who's responsible for this beautiful placard? Goyle, is that yours?
Malfoy... You must be behind all this Potter stinks crap!
Hey!
Get rid of the buttons, Malfoy, or I'll kick you off my street team!
Then we'll see who checks your tumblrs.
Harry Potter!
I would never make up a rumor about you!
I treasure our friendship!
Don't you remember all those times at school when we...
As Draco speaks, the lights dim and his voice fades away.
In it's place Harry can hear an eerie mysterious voice, that echoes from somewhere in the distance.
Ssssssss!
Ssssnaaaaake...
I'm a snaaaake!
Oh, where'd my arms go? Just kidding, I'm a sssnaaaake.
Wowowoah! Did... did you guys hear that?
Hear what?
I'm gonna eat so many of you stupid humans now that I'm free.
None of you can even hear me!
Oh! There's one!
Take thisssss!
Aaaaahhhhhh!
What the devil was that?!?
It came from down there! Come on!
Harry and Draco run off to investigate.
Ron, Goyle and the candy lady follow.
The gang eventually run into Colin Creevey, who stands motionless in the center of the stage.
Ginny stands there, her hands covered in blood.
On the wall behind her is a message WRITTEN in blood.
Ginny?!?
Huh? Uuuuuuh!
Hey, Colin!
Are you okay, little buddy?
W... w,w,w,w,... w-what is that?
The Chamber of Secrets has been opened.
Enemy of the heir beware!
Uh! That's quite good.
Now... just add:
You're next, mudbloods! Vote for Malfoy!
What's going on in here?
Wait! Listen, Professor, I'm... I'm not lying this time! This really was like this when I got here.
Oh boy! Is Colin dead?
Uh... Ah, no. He's still alive, but he appears to be petrified.
What does that mean, Professor?
Just what the note says, Miss Chang.
The Chamber of Secrets...  has been opened!
Professor, what's the C-c-c-c-c-chamber of Secrets?
A hidden dungeon somewhere inside Hogwarts build by Salazar Slytherin himself.
The legend goes that one day Slytherin's heir would use Parseltoung -
snake language - to open the chamber and unleash - a monster!
Uuuuh! Coool!
No! No, no, no, no! Not cool!
E-everyone back to your dormitories! I'm taking Mr. Creevey to the infirmary.
Huh! Woah, Harry!
This can't be good. The Chamber of Secret's monster, wha...?
You're right, Ron.You're very right. This isn't good at all.
It's great!
Huh?!?
Don't you get it, Ron? All I have to do is save this school again, then everyone is gonna forget about this Potter stinks crap,...
... and I'll win the head boy election and prove that Harry Potter is still the number one wizard in the world!
Awesome! Where do you want to start?
Wait, wait, wait, what? Did... did you want me to help? Because I... I figured you just get this one.
Mr. Campaign manager, you got it!
Besides: I can't help right now.
I got a date with Cho Chang.
[starts singing the title melody from the smurfs]