Scene Two:
Lights up on Hermione.
Who stands outside Gilderoy Lockhart's office.
Well, here we go.
This is my chance.
This will show Ron!
[Knocks]
Hello, Mr. Lockhart. It's... it's me.
Hermione Granger.
Took you long enough, get in here.
Whatever you say, Professor!
I wanted to talk about these essays of yours.
Oh, you've already read my Harry Potter essays!
Yes. I think you have quite a gift.
Your witty prose delivers a sophisticated
humor packed with plenty of ghoulish giggles.
That being said...
This is awful!
Awful work!
What? I thought you like it! I thought it made you ghoulishly giggle!
Giggle, yes. But chortle? Hardly
Why, I can't even remember a single
guffaw escaping my lips whilst reading this...
garbage!
This trash!
Oh yes! This is just like one of my fan fics!
Alright, Hermione. Here is your chance!
Ron's gonna feel so stupid after this!
Oh yes, scold me, Professor.
Teach me a lesson I won't ever forget.
Oh, I intend to do just that.
I'm going to teach you a thing or two. About dramatic flow!
In your Harry Potter essays everything exciting happens in Harry's first
and second years, but the rest of it is extremely boring.
So I've taken the liberty of
tweaking your essays a bit!
Oh, feel free to tweak anything you'd like, Professor.
I want you to.
Good! Because I've tweaked plenty.
I had to rearrange everything!
I changed Voldemort, of course. He's arguably Harry's main villain, but in your story he's defeated at the end of year two.
That's moronic!
I made sure he was in it throughout, and only gets beat at the end climax!
Well, I'm sure that it's better.
I bet you're good at making things climax.
Well, I did the best I could.
I did the best I could, but this one still stinks.
Harry just bounces the killing curse back off him! It's lame!
But hopefully I've killed enough side characters to make some people cry.
Oh, you can make me cry.
Oh, my eyes are already wet...
and that's not all.
You're right that's not all!
I'll tell you what else is boring about your stories,
All these human characters,
Why aren't any of these characters dogs?
What?
Do you have any idea how many people in the world are dogs?
Why do you think Twilight sold like hot cakes? Cause I had the wolf market cornered!
Uhm... Okay, I'm sorry, I-
guess I just don't know how to write for dogs.
Maybe you could teach me a thing or two about doggy style, Professor.
No! I can't!
No! If you don't know how to write for dogs by now, you'll never learn!
I've already made the changes for you. I took one of the less interesting characters,
Sirius Black, and turned him into a dog.
You see, you have to give the pooches out there
a character they can relate to;
throw them a bone, so to speak.
Well, I wouldn't mind a bone!
Quiet you!
I also made Professor McGonagall a kitty.
A fancy cat.
And that Peter Pettigrew, he's a kindred spirit;
I turned him into...
a mouse.
Alright well, if you've already done everything, then why did you call me in here?
I mean, didn't you want me?
Don't you want me, Professor?
I do want you,
To sign this release form.
Turning over all creative rights of your Harry Potter essays.
Alright, fine.
Can we talk about something other than Harry Potter now?
Yeeees.
Great. Let's get to know each other.
I mean, You already know everything about me;
I'm just a young innocent girl who's never done anything crazy.
But you, you're like a mystery. I mean, What are your hopes?
What are your dreams?
What are your deepest fantasies?
My fantasies?
Yes!
Oh,
Professor, if-
you wouldn't understand my fantasies.
If you could do anything right here, right now,
anything at all,
who would it be?
If I could do anything?
Yeah.
If I could do anything, I think I would...
...shrink myself,
to the size of a mouse.
I'd leave the world of men behind me... forever.
And live amongst the mice.
And I would bring technology and... and art, to those uncultured swine!
I would... I would build tiny tools for their mouse hands; made from toothpicks, and marshmallows!
And I would be their king. Neigh,
their prince!
Gilderoy! The mouse prince!
Ruling from my grand castle, inches high!
Carved from the finest cheeses!
And there I would dwell, with my three mouse wives.
And my twelve mouse concubines!
HAHAHA! But the wars we'd have with the frogs... terrible.
Just terrible.
Those meadow-mice warriors;
the atrocities they've seen.
Yes,
That is my dream.
My secret dream.
Wait a minute,
I'm not alone. What the hell are you still doing here, Potter?!
I'm not Harry Potter.
Oh yeah? Then why do you dress like him?
Uh, wha-
You'll have to wake up pretty early
in the morning to fool the mouse prince!
Well, I'm going to sit down in my chair for the next eight to twelve hours.
And when I open my eyes, you'd better be Zzzzzz.
What a f*cking idiot.
Hey Ginny, what's up?
Huh?
Is everything okay?
Wuuuuuh!
Duuuuuh.
What is that girl up to?
[Reference to: Disneys Little Mermaid]