Scene six.
Harry, Ron, Draco, Neville, Luna, Seamus, Dean, Cho, Lavender, and the other kids of Hogwarts...
Stand in a tight group in the girl's bathroom.
There. That picture of a snake. Speak parseltongue at it and the chamber opens.
Let's do this. Voldemort is going down. Come on!
The door to the chamber of secrets clanks open and they step inside.
The chamber is dark, wet and cold.
Alright, everyone. Stick together!
[Voldemort is laughing]
Harry Potter, the boy who lived.
So... we meet again.
Woah, woah! Is that a flying diary?
Oh shit!
[Piano guy makes fun of Joe Waker]
That's so weird! Ouch!
Hrrgh!
Argh.
Shit!
I came back to stop you! How many times do I have to kill you, Voldemort?
Clearly more than once, Potter!
You really think you stand a chance? I already beat you! The real you. And all you are right now is a ghost.
Not for long. Soon I'll find the Resurrection Stone and I'll be back.
You mean...
This bad-boy?
Yeah!
I hate to rain on your parade, but it doesn't even work, Voldemort. It only brings back spirits. It doesn't even raise people from the grave.
I don't know what you've heard but it's just a piece of shit.
Ah, but it's not a piece of shit.
You're a piece of shit!
In fact, it does work. Dumbledore just didn't know how to use it.
In order to truly regain a life, you have to take it from somebody else.
[Ginny making Zombie noises]
Why, I think I'll use hers!
Ginny! Ginny, snap out of it! What did you do to her?
I've been possessing her all year.
Now she's my slave.
And I really should thank you, Harry.
In fact, you're the one who gave her to me.
She belongs to me now.
And once I have that stone, I'll be able to fully steal her life.
And then I'll have returned. And her skeleton will lie in this chamber forever.
You're not gonna get the stone, Voldemort. I've got a whole school backing me up. This isn't just between you and me.
You're right. This isn't between you and me.
It's between you... and me... and my GIANT SNAKE!
I'm gonna get you, stupid humans!
Take thisss!
Bloody hell!
That snake is almost as big as this snake!
Ahh!
Seamus! He's petrified!
[Screaming]
Don't look at that thing! It'll petrify you if you do.
Okay. How do we beat the chamber of secrets monster? We can't even look at it.
That creature is called a Basilisk.
The sword of Gryffindor is the only thing strong enough to penetrate it's scales.
Listen! It is said that the truest Gryffindor could pull the sword from within me.
Huh?
Let me try!
How'd the sword get up in you, Sorty?
Well, I may have had something to do with that.
Let me try!
Nothing.
Alright, I'll try!
Harry, you're still afraid.
Still unsure of yourself.
Found ya!
[Screaming]
Well, if we want a fighting chance, somebody's gotta go blind that thing.
Get out of the way, kids!
Scarfy!
Why do you have to be so brave?
You're the one that sorted me into Gryffindor.
And you're the one that taught this old hat how to love.
Be careful!
I will!
Take this you tacky snake!
Ha!
Oh! I can't see!
Who turned out the lights?
He's blind! Everybody shot magic at it!
[Magic, Magic, Magic... Pow, Pow, Pow]
Ow! Ouch!
Hey, did you guys come here just to hurt me?
I liked it so much better when my chamber was a secret.
Our spells aren't doing anything. His scales are too strong.
Well, at least he can't see us. Everyone, be quiet!
Huh? Hey...
Where'd they go?
Marco.
Polo.
Got you, sucker!
Shit!
You!
Argh!
Well, well. Tom Riddle.
Ah! How dare you use that name?
Now, you may have cut your hair, lost your shirt and added a fabulous cape...
But you're still that confused little orphan boy from all those years ago.
Shut up!
But you were wrong about the world, Tom.
Just like you were wrong about yourself.
People did care about you.
Dumbledore did. I did.
And I think you care about people too,
Hrrr!
Deep down! And I think you know it.
Oh, yeah?
How is this for caring?
Hrrr!
Avada Kedavra!
Ah...
Scarfy!
Noooo!!!
[Voldemort laughing]
Yes!
Now give me that stone, Potter!
Snake!
Yes, master.
Ugh! Give it!
[Voldemort laughing]
Hand it over!
You're finished, Potter!
You can't stop me!
Remember? You've lost everything that made you the chosen one.
Face it! You don't even know who you are.
Ah.
Oh yeah?
I'm...
Harry...
Freaking Potter
Argh!
HARRY FREAKING POTTER!
Yea! Ha, ha, ha.
The Basilisk and Harry fall to the ground.
The Basilisk is dead, but Harry is dying.
Voldemort walks to the Resurrection Stone.
And picks it up.
At last!
You are mine!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, slave!
Rrrr!
I want the last thing for Harry Potter to see...
To be me, sucking the life out of his girlfriend.
Oh, thanks babe. It's been one crazy year. Ha, ha, ha.
Hey, Harry...
Tell me! How does it feel...
Knowing that you failed?
Knowing that I'm gonna walk out of here and rule the world forever?
And knowing that when I do, I'll have wiped every trace of your story from the face of the earth.
Nobody will remember you!
Nobody will care.
While I will live forever...
For you... this is your end, Harry Potter.
Well, Voldemort...
If Harry Potter can't live forever...
Then neither... can you!
What?!?
Harry lifts up the sword of Gryffindor and stabs the diary.
Duurrrr!
Nooo!
Blood begins to spurt from the diary as Voldemort convulses.
Ahhhhh!!!
Voldemort's chest explodes open.
A blinding white light shines out.
Pieces of Voldemort's body begin to break off, as he desperately wails.
His face flakes away, revealing a grotesque screaming skull.
Soon all his skin ignites into flame.
His burning scelleton crumbles into a mess of gore and green goo.
Joe Walker dies!
[No mistake!]
Cool...!
Oh! Harry!
Oh no. Harry!
Harry, no, no, no, no, no ,no, no, don't die! Don't die!
Everything has an end, Ron.
This is mine.
Ey... Thanks for bringing me back.
No... No problem pal. I... I just didn't think I'd have to say good bye to you right now!
Well, I guess now would be the time... to say good bye, dude...
Not if old Hagrid has anything to say about it!
The end'll come, Harry. But not today, not today!
From within his coat... Hagrid reveals Fawkes the Phoenix.
Who begins to cry into Harry's wounds with his magical healing tears.
There you go, Fawkes!
Give him a good cry, that's it! Let it out.
Oh! Huh?
Whoa, wipe out!
Well,... Chocolate frogs! Harry Potter did it, y'all!
[Cheers (first from the cast, then from the audience)]
Oh, Harry Potter!
Oh, Ginny. Ginny, I'm so sorry, I was in such a hurtful mood all year.
I was thinking... I was thinking dumping you would really... that dumping you would bring me some good, but I was totally wrong. Do... Do you want to date again, maybe?
Huuuh... You.... You mean it?
Well, you know what they say.
There's nothing really wrong with an old hat.
Oh boy!
I can't wait to go write about this in my diary!
But Hagrid,
What about Scarfy?
Sorry, kids. The phoenix's tears don't work on cloths.
Scarfy...
He died how he lived: Throwing caution to the wind.
And he wouldn't want you kids to be sad for one moment.
He would have wanted you...
To be gay!
Look!
You see, Mr. Shacklebolt, Harry Potter has defeated the Chamber of Secrets monster!
The school is safe, it doesn't have to be destroyed!
It seems so.
But you kids...
Rushing past my men...
Fighting a giant snake all by yourselves,
and going directly against the orders of the minister of magic...
Those are magical felonies! Why, I think I just might...
Give magical medals to all you little heroes!
[Cheers]
Call off the air strike, boys! Hogwarts is here to stay!
Word!
Yay!
It's a miracle! All the students who were petrified have magically come back to life.
Except for Colin Creevey, who unfortunately died.
Yay!
Woah! Wipe out!
I can't believe that the Chamber of Secrets was in the girls' bathroom all along!
I guess the rumors are true.
Salazar Slytherin built this place so he could watch little girls pee.
Hermione!
Wait... What's this? A ring?
Just as a true Gryffindor can pull the sword from within me, it is said...
That someone who is truly in love can pull a magical ring out of Scarfy's folds.
It's his last gift to you, Ron.
I think I do.
I've gotta explain things.
No, Ron!
You don't have to explain anything.
I could see and hear everything while I was petrified.
I've already told the wizard cops what Mr. Filch did to me while I was petrified and he's being arrested at the moment, so...
But I also know, that it was you, Ron Weasley,...
who brought Harry back to save the school... and me.
Yeah. I... wait, what did Filch do to you...?
Ron... I've been thinking about it, and you know what? Gilderoy Lockhart is a creep.
And his books suck!
Would you mind staying with me...
Even if I am... waiting 'till marriage?
Well,...
You won't have to wait long!
Hermione Gene Granger,...
I wanna get another kiss.
So will you marry me?
And me!
Yes!
Yes! Wizard god, yes!
I did it! She said yes! Hey!
Shut your fat face, you fart mouth!
She said yes to ME!
No, good sir!
Oh my!
Two boys want my kisses. Now I know how Catniss feels.
Yay!
Well. That's it, guys.
Senior year... is over.
I think we all graduated.
And Voldemort is gone forever.
Unless there's... some other... unrelated piece of his soul floating around out there...
I... I doubt it.
So I guess that means, ah...
Butterbeer's on me!
Yay!
No, no, no!
What kind of a headmaster would I be if I allowed that?
Butterbeer's on me!
Yay!
Don't want to see you go
But it's not forever, not forever!
Even  if it was, you know
That I would never let it get me down
You're the part of me that
makes me better wherever I go
So I will try not to cry
'cause now it's time to say good bye
*sigh* Oh, good bye, Seamus. I'll miss you, man.
Alright.
Dean! The sunny guy.
I love you, man!
I love you!
Oh, you crazy woman!
Neville, I'm gonna even miss you, pal.
Good bye, Mr. Potter.
I see you, buddy.
Bye, Luna.
Sayonara, Harry Potter...
Bye, Cho.
Well... Suppose this is good bye?
You sure showed Voldemort, didn't you?
*sigh* Yeah, it's pretty dangerous to be one of my enemies.
That's why it's a good thing, that we're... we're friends.
Well, guys... Let's go see what's next.
You ready to go, buddy?
Yeah, yeah, I'm, I just, ah...
*sigh* Take it easy, Hogwarts.
It has been...
totally awesome.