Harry runs out of the great hall into the hallways of Hogwarts.
Harry! Harry, wait!
What do you want?
To talk.
I - About the diary you gave me.
Tom's diary.
Harry we need your help!
Oh yeah, like-like you helped me in the great hall?
You didn't even try to stick up for me!
Just sat there with Seamus and Dean.
Tell them about your diary, I'm done helping people! Never again!
Harry... You may not be popular anymore, but people still need your help!
You're Harry Potter!
No I'm not! Okay?
At least not anymore.
Everything that made me who I am is...is gone!
I WAS Harry Potter.
There was a time, when life had meaning...
Not so long ago.
I knew the lines, it was easy being...
The star of the show
There was a time...
When things were fine...
I could make wine from water
There was a time, when I was happy  when I was Harry Potter!
Tom,
I think I understand you now.
You can't put your faith in anyone anymore.
The world is a terrible, lonely place!
I'm ready to see what happened to you after you killed your father.
There was a time, when I was hopeful
When I was good inside.
Everyone said that I was evil.
Maybe they were right.
I changed my name
I went insane
I never felt so little.
I was a fool to think they could love me....
When I was Thomas Riddle.
I've fallen
From up high
The world has said good bye
I'm not an angel
Not the answer
I'm just going nowhere faster
There was a time I was a hero...
But that hero's gone.
Looking back, I can hardly see him
Everyone's moved on.
Cast me aside, throw me away
Go on, forget yesterday
And I'll try forgetting too
But I wish it was just like it was before
Harry!
Where are you going?
Away from here.
No, don't say that, Harry. Let's just... let's go back to the great hall and we'll try to explain things...
I'm not gonna go back to the great hall, don't you understand, Hermione? I never gonna go back.
What...?
I'm leaving Hogwarts forever. You saw what happened back there! Nobody wants me here!
And you know what? I don't blame them!
Who would care about... a loser like me?
Losers like us, that's who!
Harry-
[stops because the audium is applauding (I had too if I had been there)]
Hogwarts is your home, Harry!
It used to be.
Bye!
I've fallen
From up high
The world has said good bye
I'm not an angel
Not the answer
How did life become one disaster?
I'm just going nowhere faster
There was a... a time before
I was adored
By every son and daughter
There was a time, when I was happy,
when I was Harry Potter
And so I left Hogwarts, never to return.
For years I wandered, mastering the Dark Arts, becoming something all would come to fear.
And now, tonight, I call on the wizards and witches who entered my service long ago.
Now we will know, who will be brave enough to return and who will be foolish enough to stay away!
Tonight I begin my war on this world.
Tom Riddle is no more.
I AM LORD VOLDEMORT!!!!
[Tom Marvolo Riddle = I am Lord Voldemort]
Sparkles!!!!
No! It can't be you!
Duh, Ginny.
I'm back. I'm not dead. Nor am I alive... yet!
Don't try to stop me, Ginny.
You haven't got any choice in that matter anymore. I've become far too strong to resist.
Now... my slave...!
To the Chamber of Secrets!
Come, my basilisk!
Snake!
Yeah... Yeah...!
For far too long you've fed on mere vermin. But you will have finer prey.
Lord Voldemort shall provide.
[more evil laughter]