Aaaah!
Heavens to Betsy, what's all the hubbub-
Oh my. Not another one.
Oh dear me, it's Hannah Abbott.
Poor thing, she's been petrified!
Just like the others.
How many is that now, Headmaster?
341...
Now, I'll have to send word to the Ministry.
The fate of the school is in their hands now.
Well, take Miss Abbott to the
infirmary. Spit spot!
Attention Hogwarts Students!
Hogwarts is no longer safe.
There has been yet another petrification,
Putting us over the allowed limit of 340 student casualties each school year.
As a result, new safety regulations must be implemented immediately.
Students shall, henceforth, report directly to class from their dormitories.
All lollygagging privileges all dismissed until further notice
Beware, Children.
unless the Chamber is found, and the monster inside destroyed
The ministry may close the school
...forever.
Wizard God, help us all.
Close Hogwarts?
Forever?
Oh d-d-dear.
You know, I heard all this wouldn't be a problem if the school's entire supply of Mandrakes didn't get destroyed
when somebody mucked up the Herbology Room.
Yeah, and it's too bad those were the last Mandrakes in the whole world.
You know, Mandrake juice is the only thing that can cure being petrified.
Or if somebody kills the Chamber of Secret's monster!
That would break the petrification spell!
Yeah, but who's gonna do that, Looney?
You know whose fault all this is?
Harry Potter's.
I heard it was him that wrecked the greenhouse.
The school just blamed it on
some Latina chick, cause they're racists.
But it was actually Harry that did it, and probably
on purpose so as no one else could save the school.
Bloody darby, couldn't handle not being the hero for once.
Well, where are you now, Harry Potter?
Where are you now?!
Shame on you!
Huh?
I said, shame on you,
Seamus!
Shame on all of you!
Look at yourselves!
Sitting around,
complaining,
spreading gossip.
Harry didn't destroy the Herbology Room.
It was like that when he got there!
Do you guys wanna know why Harry always saves the school?
Because he doesn't wait around for someone else to do it.
Do you remember our fourth year, when Igor Karkaroff was bewitching exchange students?
Making them compete in the Tri-wizard tournament, not to be confused with the House Cup tournament.
Who was it that unmasked Karkaroff as a Death Eater and sent him to Azkaban?
Harry.
And - and - and - and - and Cho, what did you do that year?
Fooled around with Victor Krum.
Me too.
Yeah, me too.
Shooting marbles.
Tag.
Ordering all them pizzas to Filch's office.
We did some right fooling around that year.
Yeah, remember our fifth year,
When Umbridge became the Minister of Magic and appointed those incestuous Carrow twins as the Dark Arts Teachers.
Luna, what did you do when the Carrows told you to shoot the cruciatus curse at Neville?
Ask if I could try the killing curse?
And who was the only one of us who didn't raise his wand against a fellow student?
Harry.
And when the Carrows tried to torture the location of the DA out of Cho,
who tricked them into walking through Devil's Snare where they were torn asunder?
Harry.
And then united the giants against Umbridge's evil ministry!? Who was that?
Harry!
That's right. Harry!
And how do you repay him, huh?
Tell him he stinks.
We drive him away. Well...
The school's in bigger trouble than ever now.
And I hope you're all proud of yourself.
Because the only person standing between you,
and whatever's in that chamber of secrets,
is your new headboy.
Malfoy.
Slow, slow, slow.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the ignorant mob that handed me supreme power.
They all look so tiny from up here. Don't they, Goyle?
Yes, me lord!
Alright, The Head Boy Draco Malfoy will now hear your questions,
concerns, praise, worship...
Rabble! Rabble! Rabble!
Order!
None of that sounded like worship
So what's your plan to save the school Malfoy?
For dealing with this Chamber of
Secrets thing?!
Plan?
What do you mean plan?
I already have a four-step plan in place.
One,
Watch mudbloods get petrified.
Two. Laugh. Repeat.
And I promise, that my administration will do all it can to ensure we aid this Heir of Slytherin hero!
Draco Malfoy will bring change you can believe in!
Booo!
Silence.
Silence you worms!
I wish you had one neck, I'd hack it through!
Now, I may not be as deft of politician as that Fozzy Bear.
But I think we can all agree,
that I fill the position much better than that Harry Potter ever could.
That's not true, Malfoy!
Your rule is a pathetic sham!
Silence yourself, Weasley!
Why don't you stop wasting my time,
and go cry to one of your...
...two girlfriend?
Gasp!
Ron?
Girlfriends?
Oh, what?
Didn't he fess up? Don't you know?
Or... or is he a liar as well as a fat, ugly, cheating scumbag.
It's true, Hermione.
Lavender and I...
choreographed an affair behind your back
I'm so sorry,
I tried to tell you so many times... well, I tried to tell you one time.
And then I lied, so you wouldn't break up with me.
Oh my god! Could you please not break up with me?
Ron,
I have been so hard all year writing these essays for Gilderoy Lockheart, working on my future.
On our future!
Our future?
Where... where you're just bored with me and you - and - and you won't kiss me?! Where you're just busy with those crappy adult novels?
Ugh, I hate Gilderoy Lockhart!
Ron, don't you remember how the Scarf of Sexual Preference sorted me?
"Waiting for marriage"!
And I thought you understood that!
I'm sorry if I wanted our next kiss to be our wedding day.
I don't think I'd better be around you anymore.
But I-I'm...
Just go!
Tut. Tut. Tut.
What a shame.
You know, Miss Granger,
I know how it feels to betrayed by someone you love.
When I found Paddington Bear's big floppy hat in mine and Dora's crib, well... it tore me apart.
But I just want you to know.
If you ever want someone to talk to, or just have comforting sex with,
you can always...
come to me.
In your dreams, Malfoy.
Filthy mudblood!
You could have joined me up here, Granger.
If only you had the courage.
Candy Lady!
to Potion's class!
Show me the meaning of haste. [Reference to: The lord of the rings]
Aaaaaaaah.
Hey, Herman.
Hey, Cho.
Looks like you could use head girl advice right about now.
Okay.
Well, you wanna know what I would do?
I would find someone that Ron really hates.
And I would re-cheat that little scrub for the win.
Okay, girl, now go get him.
Re-cheat Ron?
But who does Ron hate more than anybody else in the whole world other than malfoy?
Miss Hermione Granger!
Oh, there you are.
Ah, Professor Gilderoy Lockheart requests your presence in his office immediately!