Harry, Ron and Hermione follow the trail into a den or nest.
Alright...
I think they went this way. Keep up!
I'm frightened, Harry!
Quiet, Hermione!
This is it.
This is the Chamber of Secrets monster, I can feel it. Usually it takes me all year to solve a mystery.
But not this year. No way, man! I'm on fire!
The boy who is on fire,  that's what they'll call me!
[Reference to: The hunger games]
Yeah!
Did you guys hear that?
The kids huddle together.
They can see something moving in the shadows.
A spidery noise grows,...
...as a large figure closes in on our heroes.
Well, well, well...
Three little PYTs have found their way into my humble abode.
[PYT= pretty young thing]
You must be the ones chasing my children through the forest.
No way, whoever you are. We were chasing some disgusting spiders. Not little kids.
Wait a second. We're chasing your children... Does that mean you are a...
Giant spider!
Aaaaaahhh!!!!!!
The name's Aragog.
Welcome to my crib.
YES!!! I DO have the magical ability to talk to spiders! I'm - I'm BACK!!!
No. I'm just a spider with the magical ability to talk to humans.
Damn it!
Let's - get - out of here!
Wait, wait, wait!
Where are you all off to so fast?
Make yourselves comfy, grab a web. Stick around.
Hey
Please
Don't run away from me.
Oh no, Baby
I cannot breath
Without you inside of me.
When I look at you I think of one thing
I feel embarrassed 'cause I know it's obscene
I want you! I need you! I'll teach you what it's like to party with me
I'm getting hungry, Baby, it's time to feed!
Get in my mouth
Get into my mouth
I know you want to, Baby
Don't even try to escape me
You know I got this feeling, it goes wherever I go.
I'll never let you go, you're mine!
You're mine!
You know I gotta taste you, 'cause you look so fine
Can't get you out of my mind, so won't you get on into my mouth?
Oh no! It's a big fat spider! I'm so scared!
Get  in  my mouth!
Get in my mouth
He's gonna eat me and I'm gonna be so tasty, oh no!
Get into  my  mouth
Oh no! Get in my mouth.
My life is over, oh my god this spider is so cool!
Get -
I want you! I need you! I'll teach you what it's like to party with me!
Baby, it's time to feed.
Would... Get in my mouth
Do you hear it? It's very simple, follow along!
Get into my mouth
And I want you to, Baby!
Get in my mouth
Come on with me. This way. Follow me.
Get into my mouth!
And now I'm going to eat you.
There's no one to save you now, you haven't got a friend in the world! Except my mouth.
They still got one friend left, you old bastard!
Hagrid!
Kids!
Oh, Hagrid! You're such a mouthkill. Me and my millions of children are n... we gotta go starving! We need to feed!
Now, you know that's not true, Aragog.
I just don't let you eat defenseless creatures who don't deserve it.
I'll bring some more puppies by in the morning.
Oh, puppies! We love puppies!
[agreement of the 'little' spiders]
Well,...
...if it isn't Harry, Ron and Hermione.
What a sight for sore eyes, yeah!
Now come on! Let's get out of this spider's nest and I'll take you to a place you might find...
A wee bit grosser, actually.
Hagrid leeds the kids out of Aragog's nest...
and into a small shag on the edge of the Hogwarts grounds.
Yeah! Come on in, come on in to Hagrid's hut.
Ah, sorry, the place is a bit of a mess, I...
I haven't cleaned up or...
...or showered since you were last here, so...
But it's not just me, you know. I've added another roommate to the mix.
You all remember Fawkes, the Phoenix!
Dumbledore left him to me when he died.
Yeah, Fawkes is a great roommate, keeps to himself, sleeps in the fireplace,...
Unlike that sleepy dragon over there.
WAKE UP, YOU BASTARD!!!
He's fine.
Woah.
Wait a minute.
Harry?
Where's that glowing smile of yours?
Wait. You're acting like something's wrong.
Something IS wrong, Hagrid.
Oh! That's not right.
I tell you what.
You come right over here and sit on old Hagrid's lap, best seat in the house!
[Reference to starship by team starkid]
Come here!
There you go.
Now here's a warning:
I'm gonna bounce you.
There.
That feels good, doesn't it? Yeah!
Yeah, that feels good. If you have to spit up just do it right into Hagrid's beard. That's what I always do.
Now tell me what's wrong.
Harry?
What's the matter?
[:-DDD]
Oh... it's NOTHING, Hagrid!
[Massively breaking the fourth wall ;-P]
Well, life just sucks, that's all, okay? It's like people don't even care that I'm Harry Potter anymore. Neville doesn't even stutter around me anymore, he's just...
...he's acting less like he's got a schlong-bottom, and more like he's got a big old shlonky dick.
I've saved the world like a million times. How can everybody just forget that.
Harry, don't you f***ing talk like that!
You might be wee, but you got a greatness in you!
Whether you're flying around on that little broom of yours
or singing a song or two,
or maybe reminding us all, that we're not alone...
Like... for some people, Harry, you are the light.
At the end of a very dark, lonely, shameful tunnel.
You're a hero, Harry!
As timeless and unforgetable as the VR Troopers.
[VR=virtual reality]
Who?
The VR Troopers.
What, you never heard of this? They're like three little kids superheroes with this mechanical suits.
Oh, you mean like Beetleborgs
[the in-official follow up to this series]
Beetleborgs...
No!
Beetleborgs are shit! I'm talking about... ah!
The VR Troopers!
They were cool! They had this amazing ability to travel through the power-lines... or the inter net, or... you know...
... ah, I actually can't clear remember what they did, but my point is:
You're like them, cherished for all time.
But Hagrid, all my life I've only been known as the savior of Hogwarts, so what does it mean when I'm not at Hogwarts anymore?
Uhum...
I'm scared.
Yeah. Alright.
Harry,...
I was once in the same position as you.
A senior, pacing down the inevitable end of school and childhood...
And I didn't want to let it go.
So what did you do?
I didn't let it go, I never left.
You never left Hogwarts?
No.
Oh, they wanted me to leave. But I refused to attend graduation.
I'm tecnically still a student.
But when you love something
so much
And you see it slipping through your fingers, Harry
You just got to hold on tighter!
You're hurting me, Hagrid!
Oh! Harry! Sorry!
My advice to you is: nevery change!
It's fun living at Hogwarts!
Sure, all your friends'll grow up and start families of their own,
but eventually their kids will come to Hogwarts.
And you know...
It'll... it'll be sad.
So sad to see them.
You'll probably just sit down in your hut most days, watching NetFlix or Hulu Plus,
waiting for... three rosy cheeked little angles to come down for a visit
maybe ask for a dance-lesson or advice...
Soon they'll grow up too, and...
...they won't come around as much anymore.
And you'll wonder...
...why you keep going.
Before you know it...
...your only company...
... is a dragon that's been asleep for five years...
...and a Phoenix.
That's just to remind you how short life is.
But we don't get second chances like that Phoenix, do we, kids? No.
Once we've burned, we're toast.
Well, pep talk's over! Thanks for coming down to cheer me up!
Thanks, Hagrid! This has been fun!
We'd better get back to the dorms.
But wait, you don't have to go yet.
Haha! Bye, Hagrid!
I... if you...*sigh*
Oh, Hagrid always has the best advice!
Well, Harry, we didn't quite find the Chamber of Secrets monster, but do you at least feel a little bit better?
No. Like hardly no, not at all, I feel terrible.