Scene seven:
Lights up on Nearly Headless Nick.
Welcome! Welcome one and all to my death day-party.
This Hallows Eve marks my 506th death day.
It's going to be a night to remember.
So: Grab a drink, enjoy the music,...
Hello, Mr. Weasley.
Oh... hey, Nick.
Happy...
...death day.
You look glum, Mr. Weasley. What hales you?
Well,...
Hermione really wanted to come to your death day-party, because she thought it would be intellectually stimulating, so I told her we can make a date out of it, but...
...she didn't show!
Oh, Ron, Ron, Ron!
Why don't you talk to some of the other girls?
Just don't talk to the Grey Lady, okay?
I'm trying to get up enough nerve to buy her a drink.
You should go for it.
By golly, you're right! I should!
No.
I'll do it next year.
I'll be fine so long as she doesn't make out with that bastard the Headless Horseman!
Huh! Well, thank you Harry Potter, bless your heart.
Yeah, no problem.
Hey Cho, I'll be waiting right over here for you all night.
Okay.
And you look really pretty by the way.
Oh! Bless your heart, Lavender!
But you don't have to lie to me.
I know I look awful.
Just awful.
Oh, Cho! You're like the prettiest girl ever.
Wanna sit down?
Sure. Bye, Lavender.
Well, thank you for taking me out, Harry.
Although I know I must not be very fun to be around.
I know I'm boring.
Real boring.
You're fine.
No, you're just saying that to make me feel better.
You know, when I was dating Cedric Diggory...
...he always used to say really nice things to me.
But he was probably lying too.
I know I'm ugly and boring.
You're fine...
Okay. Well, you know what, I'm just gonna go to the bathroom and gonna powder my nose...
My face is probably all oily and splotch, ain't it?
You're fine, okay?
Okay, well, I'll just be right back, in just a moment.
Hey there, good buddy.
How are you doing?
Ron, Cho Chang SUCKS!!! All she does is just... fish for compliments. It's the most annoying thing a girl can do. You know...
... when me and Ginny dated we'd stay up all night...
... talking about my fame and my fortune and how busy I always am...
Why can't Cho do that?
Maybe when you... were dating Ginny, you kind of took her for granted.
Ladies first.
Right this way, Miss Weasley.
Oh, thank you boys.
Wait a second. Wai... Is, is that Ginny?
On a date with Seamus and Dean?
I'll take care of this, I got this.
Oh, Harry, I'm back.
Although I probably still look ugly, don't I?
You're f, YOU'RE FINE!!! Now just *sigh* just grab a drink.
Oh.Okay.
Oh, you guys. Thanks for taking me to Nearly Headless Nick's death day-party.
This is the best day of - duuuuh!
Come to me, slave!
Now is the time.
[speaks like she's drunk) I have to go to the bathroom now.
That's cool. We'll be here.
Alright, Dean. So here's how this is gonna work:
We is gonna wine and dine this honey.
Alright. Yeah. [goes on agreeing]
We is gonna get her hot, and mad bothered.
Yeah! We is gonna make her fall in love with us. And then...
You'll snog her.
Ha! Sounds like a plan to me.
Hey,hey,hey, quit trying to snog my girlfriend!
Say what?!?
Yeah, bugger off, Potter!
She ain't your girlfriend no more, HP.
You stay out of this, Seamus. Dean...
Br...bro, don't... don't play me like this!
I would never do this to you.
remember all this times that we...
Hey Ron.
Oh.
Hey there, Lavender Brown.
So,...
I was wondering if *gets more silent with every word* maybe we could go out for a bread to eat...
And we could just...
What?
...back to my place and then maybe we could get a drink together... [too silent. Not able to understand it]
What did you say to me?
[mumbles about babies and so on]
I can't hear you. What?
Oh no!
I cheated on my girlfriend!
I did it.
I'm nothing but a no-good, low-down, rotten, fat, ugly cheating scumbag.
I better go tell Hermione.
NO!!! You stay with me, we're dating now.
No, Lavender Brown!
We need to talk about our relationship.
Why?
I don't know if things are gonna work out.
Hm... This night doesn't seem to be working out for anyone.
Oh well... I won't let that get me down.
I'm going to go and buy the Grey Lady a drink!
Huuuuh! What?!?
Horseman! You bastard!
You knew I liked the Grey Lady!
Horseman, what do you have to say for yourself?!?
Nothing, just as I thought! You coward!
Way to ruin it, Grey Lady!
... that's w... that's how I saved the school and the world. Remember that?
You know what, HP?
You did us a solid when you saved the school from... all those times.
But: Ginny is NOT your property!
But that's not fair!
Well, I can see, that I'm just getting in your way.
Stupid me thinking that someone as ugly as me could have fun on a date with Harry Potter!
Bullocks! Your face shines brighter then Dumbledore's patronus, it does!
Cho, stop fishing for compliments, okay? Nobody cares!
We're, we're, we're trying to talk, so just... just shut up!
Ho! You best check yourself, HP!
Now I see, why Dinny... Ginny dumped your ass!
No! No! I... I dumped her... ass.
Dean, you know what? You what... We've got beef! We've got beef, Dean...
[brawl]
Now we've got beef, Potter!
We've got beef!
Nobody talks to me like that!
We've got beef, Harry! We've got beef!
Now take this!
So we're on a break now?!?
You are always like this!
Oh! Well, then let's just call it quit, Ron Weasley! Take this!
Aaaah!
That's it! You're going to face me in a duell, Sir! Heya!
Oh, this looks like a fine spot for my roller skate...
Aaaaah!!!
Happy death day!
Hope you like banana cream.
Uhu!
And this looks like a fine spot for my marbles...
I finally finished the ice sculpture!
Uaaaaah!
Oh no, the ice sculpture!
Harry!!!
Great job, Potter, you ruined the death day-party!
Thanks, Harry!
No! No! But... but I, I was...
Come on y'all, let's get out of here.
Are you okay, pal?
Don't touch me!
Hey, guys.
Sorry, I'm late.
Haaa! Hermione!
I've just been so busy with all these extra credit essays, I'm doing for Gilderoy Lockhart.
Well...! Freaking well!
If it isn't... Hermione Stranger!
Or should I say: Hermione the traitor?
You didn't do my potions essay!
Because that I had to do it.
So it never got done!
And I failed!
Your plan to ruin my life is working out pretty nicely!
I'm sorry!
Yeah, yeah! You're sorry! You're a sorry excuse for a friend!
You know what, Harry? You need to calm down!
You're acting way too angsty for your age and this is just like how you were in fifth year. You know when that...
Hermione's voice is drowned out as the lights change.
And we hear the echoing mysterious voice yet again.
Ssssnaaaake.
I'm a snake, I'm huuuge!
A huge snaaaake! I'm a ton bigger then you'd expect!
You could make like a thousand shoes out of me or a million little purses!
Or two really big boots or something, snaaake!
Wait, wait, Hermione! Hermione, quiet, quiet down just for... for a second. Do you guys hear that?
Hear what?
It's that voice again!
Oh shit! I think that kid hears meeee!
I'd better get back to the Chamber of Secreeeets!
The Chamber of Secrets! Come on, guys, we gotta follow that voice!
I-I didn't hear anything.
Yeah, what voice, Harry?
Oh no!
Huh!
It's Nearly Headless Nick and... he's petrified.
Ginny, what's going on?
Huh? What.. Huh...
I don't...
What hap... what happened?
I dunno...!
What do you mean you don't know, you're standing right there! Some help you are!
Why don't you go snog Dean or something?
Fine. And maybe I will!
Whatever!
Harry, what are you looking for?
*sigh* I heard a voice back there, the same voice I heard before Colin Creevey was petrified. I think...
...I think it was the Chamber of Secrets monster. Just...
... Just look for a clue or something, I don't know.
Do you find anything, Ron?
No. Nothing.
Just an endless parade of spiders leaving the castle.
Good riddance!
Damn spiders. I f'''ing hate spiders.
Wait!
Maybe one of those spiders saw what happened down there. Damn it!
Ah, if I only had the power to talk to spiders instead of the useless ability to talk to snakes, that I never use!
Come on! Let's follow them!
But Harry, I'm... I'm afraid of sp - sp - sp - ...
...sp - sp - bugs.
I... a - a - a- - a - a - and it looks like the're heading for the forbidden forest.
They could lead us to the monster. I have to save the school, or... I might as well be dead. Come on!
Huoah!