Scene six:
Lights up on the girls bathroom.
Ginny furiously tries to wash the blood from her hands in the sink.
How did this blood get all over my hands anyway?
Hey, Ginny. Are you washing blood off your hands too?
No!
Hey! Did you hear that the Chamber of Secrets has been opened?
How excising!
Well,...
See ya.
Chamber of Secrets opened?
Hands covered in blood?
Message written in blood?
Wait a second...
I must be having a...
Nope. I lost it.
Oh, Ginny, you think too much. Diary time!
[laughs as if she's mad]
Yum!
Okay. Dear diary, I need some help.
Something weird is happening. Do you know anything about the Chamber of Secrets?
Maybe...
Ooooh...!
Can you tell me about it, or show me in another...
...magical flashback...
Another magical flashback begins.
Lights go down on Ginny and come up on Dumbledore and Madam Pomfrey.
Who stand in a hallway looking down at a young girl's dead body.
I'm sorry, headmaster, I've done everything I could.
But I'm afraid... she's dead.
Ah, f***!
Aaah!!!
Do you think it's true what the children are saying?
That this is the work of the monster of...
... the Chamber of Secrets?
Well, let's not jump to any conclusions, Madam Pompom.
We keep a lot of killer monsters in this school. This one might not have been from the Chamber of Secrets.
At least I hope not...
[Music and dancing-reference to: Westsidestory]
Cool!
[Name of a song from Westsidestory]
Professor Dumbledore, you wanted to see me?
Ye-yes, Tom. Just... just one second please.
Alright, slaves.
See you later.
At the club meeting.
Sure thing, Tom.
Malloy!!!
How many times do I have to tell you to call me...
...My Dark King, right, right...
Thank you! That wasn't so hard, was it? I mean, I remember your name... [yes, you just spell it wrong though ;-)]
Now scram!
Well, Pompom, I...
I guess you could just take this poor girl down to the kitchen and feed her to the house elves.
Actually, wait. Just give me a second, I wanna try this thing one more time.
*harrumph*
f***ing work!
Oh, come on, worst Deathly Hallow ever!
What is that?
Oh, ah... this? It's ahm... It's just called the resurrection stone.
Supposed to bring people back from the dead, but I, ah...
[XD...]
... supposed to bring people back from the dead, but I can't really get it to work.
Stone?
That brings people back from the dead?
I want that...
Hey, hey, hey! Hands off, you little scamp! This is going back to my office, where it belongs.
And speaking of little Miss Dead Pants:
You wouldn't happen to have anything to do with her death, Tom, would you?
I don't think so MUAHAHAHAHAHAH!
[more Deathnote]
[laughs too] 'Cause I heard from Slughorn that you were asking about the Chamber of Secrets.
A lot of people are saying I should kick you out of school.
How dare they speak that way of the Dark King!?!
That might have something to do with it.
All this dark magic stuff... This... little club of yours that follows you around. What's it called?
Huh! The he-man women haters.
But we're thinking about changing the name.
You're creeping people out, Tom!
But...
I know you've got a lot of fifth year angst going on, but we've gotta get to the root of what makes you so unhappy.
Eeeeer, I don't... I don't like this.
But you don't ever talk about your feelings.
Well,... I do to my... journal.
But that's top secret!
Well, just pretend I'm your journal for a second. What fills you with so much rage?
Aaaaah,okay, uhm...
Well, I hate all that normal things,ah... Muggles, mudbloods, the ghostbusters, but ah...
But the- ... There's some weird things too.
Ah, things like...
...Snickers!
Oh!
You mean when people laugh at you?
No! No, I... I like to make people laugh.
But what I hate is... Snickers!
You know: The bar.
The candy bar?
Yeah.
The chocolate treat?
Yes. Snickers!
Wait, you don't like chocolate?
Of course I like chocolate!
What, you don't like nuts?
Oh, I love nuts.
Wait, then what don't you like?
I don't like SNICKERS!!!
Listen, Tom. I think I know exactly what you're going through.
I don't think you do!
You feel anxious Tom, confused.
You have funny thoughts about your guy friends that upset you....
What...?!?
So you take it out on the rest of the world.
My family never really accepted me...
Yeah, well, at least you HAD a family!
[starts to cry]
Oh, there, there, Tom!
There, there!
How were you ever supposed to learn how to love when you had nobody there to teach you?
Well, I've got good news for you, Tom.
I'm suspending you.
But that not good news...
I'm suspending you, so you could take a little vacation to Little Hangleton.
You're  gonna spend this christmas with a very special family there: The Riddles.
What?
I found your dad, Tom.
His name is Tom too. Tom Riddle senior.
Tom Riddle senior?
That makes me Tom Riddle - junior!
Little Tommy junior!
He lives with your grandmother and your grandfather!
Oh! What kid of wizards are they?
I always dreamed that my daddy would be something... incredible.
Like a - like a fiend-firefighter, or a magical astronaut, or a ballerina!
Tom, it doesn't matter what kind of wizards they are.
If you want them to accept you, you have got to accept them.
You're right.
I'll accept them, whatever kind of wizards they are.
Just so long as they are wizards.
So pack your bags, boy, 'cause you're leaving right away.
Wait! But - I can't leave now, I've got a club meeting with my slaves.
We're voting on a new name.
Forget the name! Now is your chance to find a new path!
Maybe you're not supposed to live your life consumed by darkness.
But that's all I know.
Well, it's time to get out there and learn something new.
Something you can't learn in a classroom. Tom!
It's time you go home.
You're right.
Oh!
You're right!
Hey, good luck, boy.
You know there are only a couple of things in life that I love.
And one of them is you.
Thanks, Dumbledore.
When you have to go
All the way home
Just to find what you need
And know what to be
When you have to go
All the way home
Just to find who you are
And know your own heart
Singing na na na nana...
Tom!
My king, you can't leave, you're going to miss the meeting!
Where are you going?
I...
I'm going home!
when you have to go
All the way home...
[Gospel singing, we can't differ all of that apart, sorry]