Scene five.
Harry enters the village's square of Godric's Hollow.
In the middle of the square stands a huge statue of Harry.
Well, here I am. Godric's Hollow.
The place of my birth. The one place of this wretched world where I'm remembered for all time.
Ah, look at you.
You're not going anywhere anytime soon, are you buddy?
Alright! Let her rip!
A wrecking ball flies into the stage, smashing the Harry Potter Statue into a million pieces.
What? Wait, what? Wha... what'd you tear that statue down for?
What? That old eyesore?
The city has been getting too many complains about that thing.
We had to make room for this: a new statue...
Of Spiderman!
Well, if I'm being replaced by Spiderman, I guess I can live with that.
Yep, Andrew Garfield. Love him.
Wait, what? No, no, no.
No, Toby Maguire is... (Spiderman)
Who?
You know. Toby Maguire.
F*cking Spiderman.
Oh! You mean from... those old movies?
Yeah, I saw those once. Who's the bad guy in those?
That, ah... Green Gremlin guy with the little, ah... robot wormies on his back?
Could turn into sand  and had those f*cking... he had that thing on his thing.
Yeah, that was pretty cool.
You know they did all of that with computers?
Hey kid, why the long face?
Well, I... I guess not even the Spiderman movies are sacred, are they?
I thought people would remember those forever.
You know what? I take back all those bad things I ever said about
Spiderman 3. Sam Raimi did the best he could, given the circumstances.
Studios breathing down his neck. That idiot Avi Arad making him put Venom in it. It's like...
Sam did so much good.
And in the end... everybody throw him out like he was yesterday's garbage.
Hey come on, kid. They're just movies. They're not that big of a deal.
Well, if the Spiderman movies aren't that big of a deal, then...
Then what is?
I guess that all depends.
Take it from me! A professional monument destroyer and re-builder.
In the late 90s, I was tearing down statues of B@tman all over the place.
Now I'm building them back up again.
You liked Toby Maguire's Spiderman.
But this...
This Andrew Garfield Spiderman is gonna mean a lot... to a lot of kids.
With bad taste.
But...
One day I'll come and tear him down too.
If I get the contract, god willing.
Things come and go.
Nothing lasts forever, kid.
And nothing is build to.
But what do I know, huh?
I'm just you everyday, working class, blue-collar, gay guy with a beard.
Hey.
We're about to bulldoze this whole historic Potter house, you know...
This ah...
Whole Harry Potter craze is about to over in about 30 minutes, so...
Why don't you go take one last look around?
Thanks.
Hey no problem, Harry.
You know, there's two things in this world that I love.
One of them is you.
How'd ya... huh?
Harry!
Harry, Harry!
Ron!
I knew you'd be in Godric's Hollow.
But man, what are you doing here?
I came to get you. Come on, the school's in trouble!
Again?
Big trouble this time.
Harry, they're gonna destroy Hogwarts.
And that's not the worst of it. Harry.
It's Voldemort!
He's back! He's the heir of Slytherin.
Voldemort? That's... that's impossible.
Well... just bounce his own killing curse back at him! That usually works.
No, no, no! He's got the Chamber of Secrets monster this time! And half the school is petrified.
Well that sucks for them.
He's got Hermione!
Harry, Hermione is pertrified.
And I can't do anything to help her.
Ron, I can't come with you.
Why? Because you're afraid to fight Voldemort again?
No!
Or is it cause no one thinks you're cool?
Who cares?!?
You haven't changed. You'll always be cool.
Cause cool doesn't come from other people. It comes from you!
Here.
This is yours.
Remember what it mean?
The house of the brave. The house of the good guys.
Harry, you got sorted into this house for a reason.
I can't... I can't go anymore!
You can end this!
It must be nice...
Having someone to come cry to when you can't do things for yourself.
Yeah, it was nice...
Having a friend you could rely on.
Harry Potter was my best friend.
But you know what? You're not Harry Potter.
That's right.
Well.. whoever you are...
You don't deserve to be my friend.
My lucky Snitch.
I open at the close.
You don't know what you're hiding from
How did life become such a sad song
Dad?
You don't know what you're fighting for
What you came here for feeling all alone
You have loved
You have lost
How could this be happening
All alone
On your own
But you shouldn't give up
No you shouldn't do that
Never ever give up
No no never do that
Dad! Sirius! Lupin!
Hello son.
Hey Harry.
What are you guys doing here? I thought you all died.
We did. But you brought us here, Harry.
How?
That thing you hold in your hand.
That's what Dumbledore left you.
It's called the Resurrection Stone.
It brings people back from the dead?
No, not really. It just sort of lets you talk to ghosts.
But everybody at school could do that.
It's kind of a piece of shit.
Oh! I mean poopy.
Nothing... nothing can stop death, Harry,
Nothing is made to last
The sun goes up and falls so fast
The clock looks still, still the hours pass
And all that time is never coming back
Everything has an end
Even the lives of family and friends
Even when it doesn't make sense
Mum? You're still with dad in heaven? That's... that's so beautiful.
Actually, Harry. Your father and I separated.
He's kind of immature.
But I found someone new in heaven.
I'd say we've found each other.
WHAT THE F*CK?!?
Mum? You're dating Cedric?!?
No, Harry. We're not dating. We're married.
Looks like I'm your heavenly father, eh Potter?
MUM!!!
Mum! This is the stupidest thing you've ever done!
Hey!
Now you can talk to me however you like. But when you talk to my women that way, that's when we're going to have words.
Alright. You suck so much, Cedric!
We'll agree to disagree.
I'm glad we could find some common ground.
Argh!
I can't believe you're still doing that!
Well, if it isn't broke, don't find a way to fix it.
Man, I hate that guy.
Yes, you're telling me.
Harry, Harry.
Harry.
Snape!
Harry. Dude. What's going on, man?
Listen, we've all been looking over you cause we think you might need our help.
For a while I really enjoyed your suffering.
But now it's just going to bumming me out.
So come on, man, tell me what's the deal?
Snape - I've lost everything that made me who I am. I lost my fame, my purpose... and I'm about to loose Hogwarts.
What do I do? How do I make things go back to how they used to be?
That's just it, Harry.
You can't.
You can't hold on to what's gone
Don't try to fix it, just move on
Only then you'll see the world all brand new
Harry, the end comes to us all, but some of us get to chose how we go.
Look at me, Harry:
I could have helped the Dark Lord take over the world
and ruled like a half-blood prince.
But instead I chose to give my life...
Protecting the last trace of the only woman I've ever loved.
Harry,...
Did I do that so people would like me?
No, I hate people.
Did I do it to be remembered?
No. I did it, because it was right.
You have a choice, Harry.
You can run away and hide, until you eventually peter out of existence...
...or you can go down in one last blaze of glory.
Everything ends
Snape, if I go back and I do face him again... If I'd do that... that'll be... my end!
Yes, Harry. Yes, it will.
But you have to ask yourself: would you rather attend any other way?
After the sun has had its rest
It will arise and light up the sky
You can't hold onto what's past
Nothing is made to last
Underneath these skies
I hear the groans, I feel the eyes
Of my teachers, my mother and my dad
And I know how right they are
And it stings my lightning scar
To know I could never ever mess things up so bad
Now the school's in danger
And my friend Hermione Granger has been - petrified
Voldemort's been plottin'
But there's one thing he's forgotten
I'm still alive!
I've got a plan that I've been kicking around
My friend's in trouble, so I'm skipping this town
Hey it's no mystery!
It's all so clear to me now!
F*ck the tie!
I've got to get back to Hogwarts!
I've got to get back to school
I've got to get myself to Hogwarts
How could I've been such a fool?
Back to witches and wizards and magical beasts
To goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
It's all that I love and it's all that I need
At Hogwarts! Hogwarts!
I think I'm going back!
I'll save my friends, gonna laugh till we cry
Take my firebolt, gonna take to the sky
No way this year anyone's gonna die!
And it's gonna be totally awesome!
I'll cast some spells with a flick of my wand
defeat the Dark Arts. Yeah bring it on!
And do it all with my best friend Ron,
'cause together we're totally awesome!
Yeah, 'cause together we're totally awesome!
Ron, you came back!
Just in the nick of time. I was on my way back to Hogwarts but then I ran into some guy with a beard and he told me you probably changed your mind, then you started singing, so...
Ron! Sorry I forgot who I was, but I remember now.
I'm your friend.
Best friend.
Now come on, pal. Rev up that flying car. Let's go.
Let's go, buddyyyyy!
We don't have long, but we're going back
Don't go for work, don't go there for class
As long as we're together we're gonna kick some ass
And it's gonna be totally awesome!
We're sick of sulking and this moping around
It's like we're sitting in the lost and found
Don't take no sorcery
For anyone to see How
We got to get back to Hogwarts
We got to get back to school
We got to get ourselves to Hogwarts
Where everything is magi-coooool!
Back to witches and wizards and magical beasts
To goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
It's all that I love, and it's all that I need
At Hogwarts! Hogwarts!
I think I'm going back!
Back at school Kingsley Shacklebolt and the wizard cops are finishing the evacuation of Hogwarts.
Keep moving, kids. Get as far away from the school as you can.
Who would have thought that after all these years it would end like this?
There there, Scarfy...
Beep-beep! Beep-beep!
D'you hear that?
Sounded just like... No. It couldn't be!
There is a woosh! As the flying car swoops over the kids heads and flies towards the castle.
Bloody hell! It's Harry Potter!
He's back!
He's b-b-b-back?
Well, then there's still a chance that we can save the school, y'all!
[cheers]
Come on, y'all!
And just where the hell you think you kids are going?
We're going to help our friend.
If you step one foot inside that castle, you'll be in direct violation of the ministry of magic!
Oi, stuff it, you old geezers!
Word!
Come on!
[screams and shouting]
Who knows how fast this year's gonna go
Our one last chance, it's the end of the show
Grab the whole cast, Neville, Luna and Cho
Oh no, this is totally awesome!
We're back to do anything that we can
To save the place where our story began
And here we are! And ALAKAZAM!
Here we go, this is totally awesome!
This school has taught us everything we know
The wait isover and we're itching to go
I think we're ready for
Our favorite Gryffindor!
Aaaaaaaah, aaaaaaaaah
Welcome both of you to Hogwarts!
I welcome both of you to school!
Did you know that here at Hogwarts
We've always known that you are cool.
You'll always have a home at Hogwarts
All you hotties, nerds and tools
The time has come to fight for Hogwarts
So let's go and beat these nasty fools!
Weasley! Oh, good. Oh, you found Potter! I've found the Chamber of Secrets.
Turns out it was in the girls' bathroom the whole time.
Excellent work, Mr. Malfoy.
Harry Potter, you've got to get down there and slay that monster or else the school and everyone in it will be destroyed!
I'll try and stop the wizard cop air strike.
Prepare my flying machine!
Alright guys, let's go! Nobody has to come, who doesn't want to.
This is our home too, Harry!
We're with ya!
Then it's time to take it back! What do you say?
Back to witches and wizards and magical beasts
To goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
It's all that I love and it's all that I need
at Hogwarts! Hogwarts!
Back to spells and enchantments, potions and friends
To Gryffindors, Hufflepuffs, Ravenclaws, Slytherins!
Back to the place where our story beginns!
At Hogwarts! Hogwarts!
I'm sorry, what's it's name?
Hogwarts! Hogwarts!
I didn't hear you guys!
MAN, I'm glad I'm back!