Scene three: Lights up on the headmasters office.
The place is in shambles.
Poor Ginny holds the diary in one hand and rips through drawers and cabinets with the other.
Voldemort looks up at a portrait of Hogwart's former headmaster Albus Dumbledore.
AHHHH, Dumbledore! You old fool!
I know that you hid the resurrection stone in here somewhere. And I'm gonna find it!
Keep looking, slave!
Ginny, what is going on?
Oh shit!
Get - get rid of her! Get rid of her!
Oh! Hahahaha, that's right, I forgot, she can't see me unless she touches the notebook.
Just the same rules as 'death note'...
[No reference necessary ;-)]
They sure are.
Anyway, I just thought I'd say that out loud for your benefit.
Ore anyone's, really.
The hell are you looking at me for? I said: Get rid of her!
Ginny, destroying the headmaster's office is definitely against the rules.
You know what, you've been acting like a real rule breaker, ever since you got your hands on that...
Diary!
Journal!
Wait a second... I remember. The deatheaters where after that thing for some reason.
You know what, Ginny? I think you'd better let me hold on to that.
Uhuhu!
Gimme the diary, you spaz!
Accio, diary!
Tom Marvolo Riddle.
Wait a second. If I take this letter and I put it there, and then...
[mumbeling that's drawn out by the laughs from the audience]
It reads:
Am I Lord Vorldemort?
No! I AM!
Lord Voldemort!
No! No! Y-y-you're dead!
No!
But... Harry killed you!
Dumbledore destroyed all the horcruxes!
Ah, Dumbledore only thought he destroyed all of the horcruxes, but he missed one. One that was hidden until now!
The diary!
That's right, the journal!
That means, that you're the heir of Slytherin!
You're the one, who's been letting out the Chamber of Secrets' monster!
Ooooh, oooooh, oooh - Yeah!
So why are you petrifying everyone?
*laughs* You mean besides for the fun of it?
Well, I hate to break it to you, but...
It's a red herring!
To keep you idiots distracted while I search for the real prize:
The resurrection stone!
And once I find it, I'll be back and there's nobody left who can stop me!
Now the bitch is back, and there's hell to pay.
You do realize, now that I've completely divulged my evil plan, you have to be... silenced?
Are you gonna... are you gonna kill me?
Nope!
I think, I'll just keep you on ice.
Save you for later.
Slave!
Summon my giant snake.
Oh!
And Hermione,...
I'd run if I were you.
To anyone who finds this note:
Destroy the diary! AHHHHH...