Scene 7.
Lights up on platform 9 ¾, 19 years later.
A wizard conductor blows a whistle and calls out:
All aboard!
All aboard to the Hogwarts Express!
Alright, son.
This is it.
It's your first day at school.
Dad, I'm scared.
Could you come with me?
No, no son. My time at Hogwarts is done.
But you listen to me:
You don't have to be scared of moving on to something new.
Why...
You're named after two of the bravest men I ever knew.
So go ahead an get on that train, Albus Scarfy Potter.
Cause now you get to go to Hogwarts
Now you get to go to school
Now that you get to go to Hogwarts
I hope you find that swimming pool.
Off to witches and wizards and magical beasts
To goblins and ghosts and to magical feasts
It's all that I loved
It's all that you'll see
At Hogwarts, Hogwarts
Man, I'm glad you get to go.
Thanks, dad.
I'll see you next year, boy.
I love you.
Oh no! I'm going to miss the train to Hogwarts.
Come on, daddies! We're so late!
Coming, coming, coming...
Excuse me! It was my fault.
No, no. Not all. That was my fault.
Hey!
Hey, I... do I know you?
No! No. Oh, no.
That's so funny. My scar kind of tingles.
Well, see ya!
Voldemort.
Voldemort, that was Harry Potter!
Ah.
I know, Quirrell. I hear everything that you hear.
Should... should I...?
No! No.
Just... let him go.
You know, Harry Potter, he...
He helped me once.
He taught me something.
He  taught me that...
It's alright to let go...
Of things that hurt us.
He taught me to open my heart up...
To what's new.
Harry Potter gave me a new family.
He taught me how to love.
I guess that's kinda what Harry Potter is all about.
But you know...
There comes a time...
When you have to move on, Quirrell.
A time when we have to let even Harry Potter go.
And that's okay.
Voldemort...
Yes, squirrel?
Okay is wonderful.
[♥♥♥]