Lights up on the great hall.
Attention, all Hogwarts students!
The last day of the term has arrived and it's time for the head boy election!
Please report to the great hall immediately, as the result ceremony will begin as soon as the final votes have been tallied. How exciting!
Alright, Ron. Today's the day. I think we should be fine, right? I mean...
I could beat Malfoy, can I?
Oh, you're gonna beat his pants off.
Hey Neville, Luna! My loyal DA. Did you guys vote for me?
Well, not exactly. Good luck.
H-hey, guys! I-I know I've,ah...
we have trouble, we haven't been getting along lately, but ah... I can count on your vote, right?
Yeah, don't hold your breath, Potter.
Come on, Ginny.
*sigh*
Hermione! There you are! You're the best, looking good, always, indeed! You voted for me, right?
Uh, well...
Alright children! Silence! Silence!
I just received the voting results, and it's clear to me that some of you did not take this election seriously.
In second place, receiving a total of two votes...
Mr. Draco Malfoy!
Oh! Two votes!
That's more than I was expecting!
Aren't I proud as a peacock?
HA!!! Hahahaha! Take that, Malfoy!
Yeah! Yeah! Two votes! Who looks stupid now?
And tying for second place, also with two votes, Mr. Harry Potter!
Wait... What? What? What? I - I voted for me!
As did I.
Ron, who did you vote for?
Just... just wait for it, Harry.
What?
And winning the election in a landslide...
...with 867 votes...
Fozzy Bear!
[Cheers]
I hope you children are proud of yourselves.
YAEH!
I hope you think this is funny.
[Laughter]
You children had a chance to have your voices heard and you wasted your vote on that silly bear!
YEAH!
Silence!
Now Fozzy Bear can't very well be our newest head boy.
BOOOO!
Silence, because Fozzy Bear is a puppet, who fancies himself a comedian!
And even if he weren't a puppet, he's a bear!
I'm sorry, but all votes for Fozzy Bear must be thrown out!
Boooo!
Oh, silence!
Now, I'm not sure who's behind this prank, but because of your own landish immaturity...
... this election has ended in a disastrous draw!
YAY!
Tisk, tisk, tisk... for shame! On you all.
I myself took this business very seriously, why, I voted for Draco Malfoy.
As did my brother, Lidaroy Gockheart.
There's only one way to break this tie, headmaster.
As Defense Against The Dark Arts teacher I suggest... a wizard-duel.
Gasp!
Yes, a wizard-duel.
With our darling, little Draco, in one corner and that tootastic stinker Potter in the other.
The winner will be head boy and the loser will be just that: A big, fat loser!
A wizard-duel, well...
... it seems fair, but putting the children in unnecessary danger for sport?
Oh dear, what would Dumbledore do?
It's okay, Professor, I'm not - I'm not scared of Malfoy.
Oh! Alright.
Alright children, clear these benches! Back away as far as you can!
You know, Goyle... I've been thinking.
What does this election really mean to me anyway?
Is it worth endangering my friendship with my oldest friend Harry Potter?
What say you, campaign-manager?
No.
Hm. Well,...
then it's settled! I shall march over to the headmaster and conceit my candidacy!
Malfoy.
Harry. I've done some thinking and I've come to a decision.
And so have I. You better get ready, 'cause I'm gonna kick your but so hard that you burp out farts!
Harry, now... I know this green eyed election monster has gotten the best of us, but...
Let's not forget that... we're friends.
No! No! We're not, Malfoy.
Don't you get it? I never was and I never will be your friend. I hate you.
Oh... I see...
So it is to be war betwixt us.
Alright boys. I want to see a good, clean duel.
Okay, on the count of four!
One, two, three, four
Harry Potter, lover of only himself...
Do you recall the memories we shared?
You never once where nice.
You never cared at all.
Now you will! I'll have you running scared!
Draco Malfoy, you know nothing of my life
All I am is what I do.
I can not let you win...
You snobbish evil  brat.
Surrender now, before I come for you!
At last the lines are drawn into the sand.
At last I know exactly where I stand.
You may think, that I'm on the decline...
But tonight this school is mine!
Yes, tonight this school is mine!
You've had luck in duels before, but now we know...
You are just a shadow of a tale from years ago.
If you find yourself you're doubting all, then take it as a sign.
That tonight this school is mine!
No, tonight this school is mine!
Yes, tonight this school is mine!
Everte Statum!
Ah, e-expelliarmus!
Uh-uh!
You think you're close to beat me, but you never will.
The more you try to climb, the more you're slipping down the hill.
Look into my eyes and know...
This is the bottom line.
So, tonight this school is mine!
Dig that, Malfoy?
Tonight this school is mine!
You served your time
Punchify!
Hu-uuuh!
That was it.
Not so fast... SERPENTSORTIA!
ASssssss!
Hey, listen snake...
I know your life is kind of rough.
If I  was in your shoes or scales...
I wouldn't be so tough.
But I can see the girl inside...
Oh babe, you really shine!
There you go, snake. That's a good girl, yeah just, just sh! That's right, just...
The snake dies.
'Cause tonight this school is mine!
I beat the snake!
Did you guys see that? ...[???]...?
You talked to a snake, that's what I saw!
All we did hear was a bunch of hissing!
Yeah!
He's a parsel-tongue!
Just like Salazar Slytherin!
Oh, d-d-d-d-d-dear!
Oh my! What if Harry Potter is the heir of Slytherin?
Gasp!
That's ridiculous!
That would mean that Harry was the one opening the Camber of Sec-rets...
It would make sense, wouldn't it? What, Potter, were you so desperate for attention?
You just need to be the main character of everyones life, don't you? But no mystery to solve this year.
So you decided to make one.
Open the Chamber, petrify students all year and then save the day at the last minute and everyone will cheer you like you're some sort of hero?
No, that's not what's happening!
You guys believe me, right? D-Dean? Luna?
Take a look around, boy.
Get it through that thick skull of yours!
Nobody likes Harry Potter anymore.
Whatever spell you've had over the world... is faded. We've... all moved on.
So why haven't you?
I'm out of here!
Harry, wait!
Well, I guess by exiting the dueling-arena Potter has forfeit. That means the winner and newest Hogwarts' head boy is none other than Draco Malfoy.
Thank you, Professor.
Draco Malfoy shall rule over this school with peace and love for thousand years.
But first comes a time of swift retribution!
For I shall rain down a vengeance upon all those who have teased me in the past. Welcome to my nightmare, slaves.
The age of Harry Potter has ended.
The reign of Draco Malfoy HAS BEGUN!!!
[evil laughter]