Scene 1.
A dark stage.
We hear the ding of an elevator as it comes to a stop.
An elevator voice says:
Bottom floor. The department of mysteries.
Lumos!
Luna, wait for me!
Come on, Neville.
Sorry, it's a nervous tick. I slow down whenever I have to hurry up.
Wow, we're here. The department of mysteries.
Isn't it wonderful? All the world's most mysterious and magical anomalies in one booby trap labyrinth.
I wanna see the room death.
Smile, Nevile!
Can we just find...
Can we just find the rest of the DA before the Death Eaters...
*gulp* find us?
Oh, yeah we're on a mission.
The very last of the Death Eaters broke in and we've got to catch them.
Maybe I should turn my flash off.
Uah...
Ups, that was a good one.
Neville!
Don't be such a guppy! What's the worst that could happen?
[The Little Mermaid]
We could get caught by the Death Eaters.
I think you mean killed. We'll get killed by the Death Eaters.
Uah...
That would be a lot worse.
Oh d-d-d-d-dear!
It's been a long time coming
But tonight is the end of the war my friend
Tomorrow only one side will remain
We will win or we will lose the fight
Either way it's the end, no use to pretend
It's the final show, we've gotta go
Meet our destiny
This is the end
[Death Eaters chattering]
Oh no! Death Eaters!
Oh, be merciful and kill us quickly!
Well, well, well...
If it isn't Luna Lovegood.
And Neville Schlongbottom.
*Gasp* Fenrir Greyback?
Can we kill them now, Sir?
Ah, ah, ah.
These two little piggies are going to make a yummy snack.
But not yet.
For now, they'll serve as hostages.
The rest of Dumbledores army must be here.
*lick* Somewhere.
You won't get away with this, you villains.
Oh really?
You DA brats have been a sword in our side for your sixth year at Hogwarts.
But tonight we reclaim the ultimate weapon.
And the Death Eaters shall rise again.
Your time is running out
Where is your hero now?
You can look everywhere but he's nowhere to be found
You look to your right
You're not gonna find him
You look to your left
He's not even there
Don't even try
He doesn't care about you
He's moved on
He's gone. He's gone. He's gone
This is the end
Here it is
At last!
Finally. The ultimate artifact of evil is within my grasp.
Now all of wizardom shall fall to the dark mark.
You two however...
You won't be around to see the show.
Oh. I've been working on this evil plan for so long.
It's gotten to get a healthy appetite.
Ah, and you two are gonna make a nice little weirdo sandwich.
With an extra side of moron. Ah ha ha...
Did somebody say Ron?
No, no, no, no, no!
I said moron!
Stupefy!
Woah!
Yes!
Come on, guys. Let's get out of here!
This is the end
Of all the fighting
Of people dying
This is the end
There's no trying to deny it's gonna be us or them
Okay.
We're supposed to meet Hermione in here.
Ron! There you are!
Wait a second.
Where are your guys's Death Eater disguises?
Neville, a deatheater. Protect me!
Take this, you deatheater!
Ouch.
This is for my family!
Neville. stop!
Stop it! That's Hermione. That's my girlfriend.
Oh d-d-d-dear!
Oh, god damn it, Ron. I think my nose got broken.
What's the damage?
Woah!
Hermione, I - I mean... I don't wanna scare you or anything, but...
You look hot!
Well...
I may look different...
But you all should just treat me like the same old Hermione you know and love.
And that goes for all of you too.
Ron, is that a book?
I've never seen you carrying one of those before.
No, it's a diary.
We're trying to keep it away from the Death Eaters.
And it's really fun.
[Deatheater screaming]
Deatheater!
It's been a long time coming
But tonight is the end of the war my friend
Tomorrow only one side will remain
This is the end
Our time is running out
Where is our hero now?
This is the end
He is nowhere to be found
Of all the fighting
This is the end
Of people dying
There's no trying to deny it's gonna be us or them
This is the end
Ah! I finally caught up to you little bastards.
Now hand over the journal, you nerd!
No!
Struggle all you want.
Hermione!
Neville, help me!
Expelliarmus!
Where are you going you cretins? He's just a child!
I'm not a child anymore.
I'm seventeen years old.
Happy birthday to me.
And what better present to get than have the last of the Death Eaters all conveniently in the same place, wrapped in a big bow?
You made a big mistake coming here tonight, Fenrir.
Ah, you arrogant little shi...
You've been trying to kill me all year and now you threaten my friends?
Let's finish this!
As you wish. Avada Kedavra!
Jelly legs jinx!
Oh no!
My legs!
Freeze Motherfucker.
We're the wizard cops!
The wizard cops!
Hey, thanks good buddy.
Harry!
Well, chocolate frogs. Harry Potter did it again, y'all.
Kingsley Shacklebolt. The minister of magic.
And chief of the wizard cops.
Word!
Well, now that you all saved the world and rounded up the last of these dark magic turkeys...
I gotta ask you: Why the hell can't y'all kids just let me do my job for once?
Oh no, mister Shaklebolt. You don't understand.
We had to stop those Death Eaters. Harry was having these visions.
Yeah, I already heard the whole story from your defense against the dark arts teacher.
He's the one who let us know to come down here tonight.
Come on in, Alister.
Hello, hello..
Mad-eye Moody!
That's right.
It's some fine work you've done here, Potter.
I taught you well.
Thanks, Professor.
And you've defeated Fenrir Grayback, did you?
He sure did.
Nice.
Very nice.
Looks like the Death Eaters were after this.
But we managed to keep it away from them.
And it's a good thing you did, miss Granger.
If the Death Eaters would have get a hold of that...
The entire world would be in jeopardy.
Best hand out over to me now.
I'll keep it nice and safe.
Oh I'm sure you would, professor Moody. Or should I say: Barty Crouch?
Blimey! All right.
Nobody move!
Wands to the ground! Wands to the ground, right now!
Put them in a pile. I'm not f***ing around this time!
Alright, alright. So, Potter!
How did you know it was me?
I had my suspicions for a while. It was briefly mentioned Mad-Eye Moody had died during my second year. But I wasn't sure it was you until tonight.
Now you gonna answer for your crimes, Farty Crouch.
Oh yeah?
I've got a better idea.
Nobody move a god damn muscle.
Me and mister Shacklebolt over here are going for a little trip on the flu network.
And none of your jive-ass bobbies are gonna follow, you dig?
We dig, mooday. We dig.
Hey, Bartie?
If you're gonna go on a vacation I know a first rate hotel that offers free body guard service and meals. It has any amenity in the world.
One could live there.
Oh really?
Sounds like that would require some reservations.
Nope. You don't need one.
For Hotel Azkaban!
Ha, ha, ha. Potter!
Always a joker.
You self-righteous son of a bitch.
Oh what's the matter, Potter?
Afraid of a little muggle toy?
Well, let's even the stakes then.
It's just you and me now.
Let's settle it the old fashioned way.
Mano a mano.
Man to man.
Face to face.
Come here, you little bastard.
Stupefy!
No!
Oh, that was some quick thinking.
You just saved my life.
But that still doesn't excuse what you kids did here tonight.
Breaking into the department of mysteries,
flying thestrals right through queen's day parade.
You kids may think Dumbledore's Army could take on the world.
But you all should have let me know the minute you heard some funky shit was going down here tonight.
I'm sorry, Kingsley. We just didn't have the time.
You know what, Potter boy bitch boy Potter Potter?!
You're a hot shot loose canon.
It's that kind of maverick attitude...
That makes you perfect for the wizard cops.
Wow!
So what do you say, HP?
You're ready to join the force and take a bite out of crime?
I'd love to, but...
I can't.
And why the hell not?
Cause I'm going back to Hogwarts.
The senior year starts September 1st.
All right. Well, you're right, Potter.
It's a shame, though.
You would have made one good god damn wizard god damn wizard hell of a wizard cop.
Alright boys. Let's get out of here.
Ah, it's beaten again, huh?
You Death Eaters never learn.
Your dark lord has been dead for five years...
Why you guys keep hanging on something that's over?
If it's over for me then it's over for you too.
You see, all you are...
Is someone who fights us.
Once we're all gone, the world won't need a hero any more.
If the dark lord can't life forever...
Then neither can you.
Ough!
Take him away!