Scene 3.
Lights up on the smoking wreckage of the flying car.
Which is crashed into the herbology room of Hogwarts.
Completely destroying it.
Oh, wow.
Wipe out!
Ron, look what you did!
Hey! At least we crashed into the herbology room.
Always hated that class. Let's get out of here before we get in any trouble.
Oh, in the name of stuffy, old ninnies everywhere. What is going...?
Potter!
Professor McGonagal?
Look what you've done to the green house!
An entire crop of mandrakes destroyed. It will take all year to grow another.
Oh and look! You killed professor Sprout!
Oh.
You'd better have a jolly good explanation for all of this, Potter, or I'll expel you so fast your head will...
Spin, spin, faster than a Fizzing Fancy.
Guys, guys. Let me take care of this.
Ahm, hm. Professor, this really isn't... This isn't... ah...
This isn't what it looks like.
Ahm, you see... We couldn't have destroyed the herbology room, because ahm...
Well, it was like this when we got here.
Potter, I know I may not be as hip as Dumbledore was.
But I am headmaster of this school now.
I consider myself to be a very reasonable uptight bitch.
But if you haven't got a witness to back up your story, it's out of my hands, Potter.
Well, well, well.
What a fine opportunity that has fallen straight from the sky.
Right into my diapered lap.
Malfoy.
How fortuitous that I happened to be exploring the next room with my bilingual friend Dora...
[Dora the explorer]
When I witnessed the entire happenings of what happened here tonight.
Oh thank goodness, Draco. Can you please clear up this whole mess.
Indeed, I can.
Oh, but first I'd liked to point out to mister Potter, that I now hold his fate in the palm of my tiny hand.
Malfoy, you little shit!
And I can assure you, headmaster...
That these fellows...
Are entirely innocent.
What?!?
Well, then who is responsible for this severe property damage?
Isn't it obvious?
Sorry old friend.
It was Dora!
Miss Explorer!
I am shocked. You're coming with me immediately!
Looks like this is the end of our adventure, Dora.
I really did love you.
Te amo tambien, y.
[And I love you too.]
Lo siento [I'm sorry]
You kids have better hurry off to the great hall for the welcoming feast.
Spit spot! Off you go.
[Reference to: Marry Poppins]
Phew, that was close.
Alright, Malfoy. What's the deal?
What? Surprised that I could pin your crime on that saucy tart?
I'm not denying it. I did sleep with her.
But she's been seeing my Paddington Bear behind my back for weeks now.
As you can see, Potter.
It's very dangerous to be one of my enemies.
Which is why it's such a good thing, that...
We're friends?
Yeah right, Malfoy!
I'll never be your friend. Come on, guys!
No! Wait!
Alright now. Surely you chaps remember all the good times we had at school together.
Like, when we battled professor Quirell and I destroyed that last horcrux.
Or when I traveled back in time and saved you from my evil father.
No I don't. Can't really remember that. I was eleven!
Well then, surely you chaps remember our third year.
The most memorable and important one.
When we all went to Pigfarts.
I did many important things that year.
And we had so many clean jokes and good songs and nobody swore.
Oh yeah. Yeah, now I remember that year.
F*** that year!
Well...
Well, we've only got one year left, chaps.
What you say we bury the hatchet and enjoy it?
Like good friends should.
Whatever, Malfoy. Just butt out. Scram, would you?
As in: Get your poopy butt out of here!
Alright, dudes.
Until next time. You hang loose.
Bloody nuts! It's Harry Potter!
Seamus!
What's good? What's good, my fellow, my brother?
Zowzers bowzers! Harry Potter!
Oh, mind a few pics for the school paper?
Who's this? Who's this?
Oh, it's Collin Creevey, sir. First year,
I just got sorted into Gryffindor and, ah...
Phew, I'm a big fan!
Oh, is that so? That's what I like to hear. Hey, be sure to get on my good side, huh?
Alright, Jillickers.
I can tell that kid has a long and illustrious career ahead of him.
Alright children. Silence, silence!
Welcome one and all to another magical year at Hogwarts.
Now, before I introduce this year's defense against the dark arts teacher...
I would like to present this year's newly chosen head girl, miss Cho-Chang.
Howdy y'all!
Now, I would have presented this year's head boy...
But sadly the young man who was chosen was murdered at the end of last term by Fenrir Grayback.
So, we can not leave the school head boy less.
So for the first time we will present the first ever Hogwarts head boy election.
We have chosen two male candidates...
Who will campaign through out the first term. At the end of which there will be a school wide vote.
To determine this year's head boy.
So, the first candidate is none other than Harry Potter.
Whew!
And Draco Malfoy.
Ah, ha, ha. Draco?
T'is with a heavy heart that I accept this civic duty.
Of course my vote will be going to Harry Potter.
Whom I believe to be the best man for the job.
Thank you, Malfoy. I'll be voting for myself as well.
You will each be given a campaign budget of 50 Dollars.
Uhhh!
Once you've settled upon a campaign manager.
And for my campaign manager, I pick my most trusted underling.
Crabbe and Goyle!
G... Goyle?
Where the devil is Crabbe?
Me and Crabbe where in the room of requirements.
We started a fire and...
Crabbe is dead.
Oh. Oh no!
I was counting on his vote.
Cheer up, old friend. Take heart.
I met this new guy on the train.
And he seems pretty cool.
Candy from the trolley, dear?
Ugh!
Brimstone and broil. She'll have to do. Come on!
This is great. For a while, I was worried. But without Crabbe, Malfoy doesn't stand a chance, man!
Yeah, Harry. You've got this election in the bag.
Oh, I wouldn't be so sure of that!
Bloody piss! It's...
Gilderoy Lockhart!
Wow!
Yes. Yes, hello ladies and...
...ladies.
Children!
I would like to present this year's defence against the dark arts teacher,
New York Times best-seller,
and all around heart throb, mister Gilderoy Lockhart!
Why, thank you, headmaster, your too kind for your own good and, ah...
a little too foxy for mine.
That's the most famous wizard in the WORLD, that is!
Woow, woow,woow. Guys...!
Guys...! I... I think you mean: Second!
Well, Harry Potter!
We meet at last! Yes, I've.. heard all about your heroic deeds...
... in the past.
[sounds of surprise/disagreement]
Oh, didn't you kids hear?
Harry Potter used to be cool.
USED to be cool?!?
What you talkem 'bout?
I guess you've all been locked up in this horrible school for so long that you've lost touch with the real wizarding world.
Yeah, but Harry just SAVED the real wizarding world from real deatheaters!
Boring!
I mean, how sick are we of seeing Harry Potter beat deatheater after deatheater after deatheater in these long drawn out episodes?
I mean how many years ago did the Dark Lord die, five?
And here's Harry Potter, still dating the same butterfaced girl since he was twelve!
I mean when will it end, so we can all move on with our life?
Yeah!
No! No! No! You're wrong, Gilderoy! People love me!
My adventures are repetitive, they're familiar and they're comforting.
Besides: If the whole wizarding world isn't obsessed with Harry Potter, then what are you obsessed with?
Why, that would be... me!
I'm telling you, children, take one step off the grounds of Hogwarts and you know what they'll be talking about.
A forbidden love between a young girl and a dracula-monster!
Twilight! Now a mayor-motion-picture.
Wooo!
Yes, the world has grown weary of Harry Potter.
He's  nothing more then a passing fad. Entirely old hat.
Old hat?!?
Old ha... I'm not an old... hold... you're an old hat! .. how.... how is this...
for...for an old hat, huh? You know...
Her... Hermione can't draw, Hermione can't draw, Hermione can not draw! She can't draw...
Harry! That's not even funny anymore! That is rude and insensitive!
Wait, but, guys, guys, come on! Come on! COME ON!
No one delivers classical musical hijinks like... like your pal HP, right...?
Oh, why! Anyone could strum that silly old lyre!
It takes a real man to tickle the ivories.
Who's wiser than a warlock
and tougher than a troll
and charming as a candy cane?
Who's faster than a phoenix
and sligh as the sphinx
and always set to entertain?
Here to give this sagging tale
A hero to employ!
Look up to the skies
Now look in my eyes
It's Gilderoy!
Who's handsome as a Hobbit
And manly as a mare
And always gives the girls a wink?
Who's funny as a ferret
And quick as a quill
And always sings without a lip sync?
Here to rid your nostrils
Of that dreadful Potter boy!
'Caus that smell in the air
Is the marvellous flair
Of - excuse me - Gilderoy!
Long ago lived a fellow who caught your eye
Hair that curled in a beautiful fro
Now it's gone and replaced with a suite and tie
Dancing in a variety show
Oh! Where did he go?
Does he even care at all?
Recently he's been acting very queer...
Every day his story grows more and more banal
And Voldemort isn't coming this year...
Gilderoy is here to fill your short attention spans
Why look at that wonder boy,
when you could be looking at a wonder man?
You can be looking at a wonder man
Who was wizard of the year
seven times in seven years?
Who was it? Gilderoy!
Who conquered all his fears
And make a boggart disappear?
Go on, say it! Gilderoy!
[The Lord of the rings - J.R.R. Tolkien]
Who taught a yeti how to sing?
Gilderoy!
Walked into Mordor and destroyed the ring?
Battled a banshee and came out a champ
Gilderoy!
[Disney's Aladin]
trapped Jaffar inside of a lamp
Gilderoy!
Stories of wonder
For each girl and boy
Paperback and hardback
For you to enjoy.
Form an orderly line
It's Gilderoy!
Ladies, one at a time!
Give me something to sign!
It's Gilderoy!
All sales are final!
Soon this school will be mine!
It's Gilderoy!
Yeah... Okay, yeah, whatever... That... that song was okay, but...
...but... check... check this out: I'm... I'm Harry freaking Potter...!
I wouldn't wince at all, you're ah... invinc... I'm... you know ...uhm
... It's Harry... No! I'm... come on, Ou! Ou! Ah...! Oh man, what is this?
Ou! Oh god, I... I feel... something... it's... it's not like a bummer.
It's not even like a... like, ah, it's like a drag but worse. What am I feeling?
Harry! Don't listen to what Gilderoy says. Everybody likes you even if nobody likes you anymore.
That's what it is.
No, he's... he's right.
He's right, Ginny. I'm boring.
I'm predictable. I'm... I keep doing the same stuff, every year I keep on the same dudes, date the same girl...
I'm an old hat!
Well, you know what they say about an old hat:
It fits like a glove!
No, I... I gotta shape things up, I gotta change everything! I gotta... I gotta stay fresh!
Have a forbidden love of my own, then... then people won't forget about me, ever!
Yeah!
Ginny, I'm sorry,...
We gotta break up.
Huh...?
Bu... But we love each other...
Don't we?
It's not that I don't like you. It's that other people don't like ME. It's nothing personal.
B-b-b-b-b... But, but I need you!
MY BODY NEEDS YOU!!!
I gave you five years of my life!!!
Yeah! And... and they were some bonatious years. We had some great times...
I will never through out  all the shit you bought me but I'm sure you'll never forget how hard I rocked your world!
So this is it? Just like this? Just a good-bye?
Ginny! Ginny, this isn't like good-bye!
It's just... you know, you're cramping my style.
Oh, you know what, Harry Potter?!?
You... suck!!!
Ginny, that's not fair! You know I'm self-conscious about that!
What's up HER butt?
Sorry man, but I just... I broke up with your sister.
YAEH!!!!! Oh! Oh!
This is the best news I've ever heard!!!
Oh, my god! I gotta tell you:
I hated pretending to be nice to your girlfriend.
'Cause I can't STAND my stupid little sister.
Oh! Yes! Oh yeah, this feels so good!
I don't know, I just... I just hope she's... she's okay...
Who cares? You're a free man!
You can do anything you want! Oh! You can finally go on that date with Cho Chang, y'all!
Maybe, I don't know. Let's first concentrate on making sure that I'm still the most
popular kid in school. Let's win that head boy election, huh?