Scene 4.
Lights up on the infirmary of Hogwarts.
Madam Pomfrey! Madam Pomfrey!
Oh, Ronald. There you are.
I just got your telegram. What's up?
Ronald, it's Hermione.
Oh no! Hermione!
Hermione! What happened to her, doc?
Well...
I'm afraid she's been petrified like all the other students.
And I'm afraid, if we don't stop this monster...
She won't have much time left.
Oh Hermione!
I don't know if you could hear me in there...
I'm so sorry!
I've been such a lousy boyfriend and...
I should be in that cot not you.
It's not fair
I didn't know
I wasn't there
It's not fair
Seeing you lying there
I wasn't strong enough
To save you from the evil stuff
I wasn't smart like you to do what you would do
I know I'm not a leading man. I know I'm not a star
But I know what makes me special
Is what I feel in my heart
I'm just a sidekick
But I love
Being at your side
I've been in the shadows for far too long
But I'm the leading man of this song
I was a stupid doofus but now that's gone
I'm ready for a change, gonna keep calm and carry on
I know I'm not a pretty boy, but I'm a man
I'll find a way to save ya baby, yes I can
Don't confuse the way I was with the way I am
I'm ready for a change, gonna take a stand
I'm just a sidekick
Oh yeah, I'm just a sidekick
But I love being at your side
I'm always forgotten
Always come in second place
I'll never be the front man
No one can remember my face
If I was in a dinner, I would surely be the less prominent taste
But when I think of how I feel for you
And the love I have inside
I forget about all the things I'm not
And my heart fills up with pride
Am I the strongest
No I'm not
Am I the smartest
Am I the hottest
No I'm not
But am I the greatest
Am I the hero
No I'm not
Am I the one who steals the show
Am I the one that you should know
No I'm not
But am I the one who takes you home
Definitely not
Am I the chosen one
No I'm not
am I the prodigal son
Am I almost done
No I'm not
But I'm the one who's gonna love you with - all of his heart
Because that's what I've got
I'm the one who's gonna love you with - all of his heart
I'm not a great athlete, I'm no good at art
And I know my brain is not my most impressive part
My wand can barely work, and my car won't start
But I know what makes me special is what I feel in my heart
I'm just a sidekick
Oh I'm just a sidekick
Yeah, I'm just a sidekick
But I love
I love
Being at your side
Huh?
What's this?
To who ever is reading this: the chamber of secrets is being opened by...
Lord Voldemort.
Oh!
He's back.
He's the heir of Slytherin.
You have to find one final horcurx.
Destroy the dia... diary!
Oh shit!
Madam Pomfrey! Madam Pomfrey.
Phew! I came as soon as I received your telegram.
Madam Pomfrey? Where is she?
Where is Herm... ?
Hermione!
Oh no!
This is all your fault, Draco!
You're the headboy!
You were supposed to be doing something. But you didn't do anything to find out who was opening the chamber of secrets!
No, no!
Pointing fingers won't solve anything. No matter how true it may be.
Yeah? Well, Hermione figured it out.
It's Voldemort.
He's back. He's the heir of Slytherin.
So why don't you just get out of here? You're the last person I wanna talk to right now.
Wait!
Just hear me out, okay?
I know we haven't always gotten along.
I hate you because you have everything I want. And you don't deserve any of it.
I agree.
And I hate you - because somebody told me to.
But I think despite our differences we can agree on one thing.
Neither of us wanted this to happen to Hermione.
Okay. So what do you suppose we do about it?
Us?
There's very little we can do about it.
You and I are the two stupidest people I know.
But - together...
We - might be able - to be smart enough - to find someone who is smart enough...
To save the school.
You're right. And there's only...
If we're dealing with Voldemort, there's only one guy we can turn to.
The one guy who has the power to make the impossible possible.
We've gotta find Harry Potter.
We've gotta bring him back. He's the savior of Hogwarts. That's his thing.
But, where are we gonna find him?
I mean to find him, it would take literally all the luck in the world.
Luck, eh?
Well, we could always use... this.
It's Felix Felicis.
The most powerful good luck potion in the world.
I got it from professor Slughorn before he got busted for collecting young boys.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! You've had Felix Felicis this whole time and you haven't used it?
Of course I've used it, Weasley!
How do you think I got those two votes in the head-boy election?
Well, hand it over!
Ah ah!
Not so fast.
We haven't discussed the subject of payment.
Payment?!?
Malfoy, you butthead! Isn't saving the school payment enough?
Nope.
I want something else.
What I've always wanted, really.
If you and I are able to save the school and keep Hermione from dying, then...
We both get to date her!
Arrgh!
Or I could just drink the last of this Felix Felicis and hit the penny arcade.
Alright! Alright.
You win, Malfoy.
I guess sharing Hermione is better than burring her.
Excellent.
Ah, ha, ha, ha! Okay, Weasley.
Here is half of what's left.
Now, when you drink that...
You'll have better luck than you've ever had before. But the effects are temporary.
It won't last long.
Okay. Well, you gotta go find the chamber of secrets. Cause when I bring Harry back...
You're gonna need to show us where it is. So we can solve this mystery once and for all.
Got it.
Well...
Good luck, my man!
Bottom's up!
Whoa!
This feels groovy, baby!
Yes, the chamber of secrets. Will do...
Right after I used the bathroom.
The prefects bathroom. No wait!
Filtch has the boy's closed for repairs.
I'll just use the girl's bathroom.
Hmm. I suddenly have the urge to hiss at the graffiti of a snake.
Okay. Okay, Ron. First things first. You've gotta find transportation.
Ah, gotta get a broom. Gotta get a broom or learn how to aperate really quickly.
Ah, too bad that flying car drove off in the beginning of the year.
*Beep, beep! Beep, beep!*
Suddenly the flying car appears and pulls up next to Ron.
The flying car! Now quick. Let's blow this!
Suddenly the flying car's door swings open, hitting Ron in the face.
Gilderoy Lockheart emerges from the driver's seat.
Where are you off to in such a hurry, Sneezley?
Hey, what luck. An adult!
Maybe you can help me. I'm looking for Harry Potter.
Oh, I know exactly where to find Harry Potter.
You do?
Of course I do.
You can find Harry - in your neighborhood book store this fall, motherf*cker.
What the hell is that?
This my dear boy, is a young adult novel.
My latest work. Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone.
Catchy title, wouldn't you say?
The Sorcerer's Stone? Do you mean the Philosopher's Stone? That stupid piece of crap Draco found on Pigfarts?
Yes.
I heard it was safer to call it the Sorcerer's Stone, so it's very clear this is a book about wizards.
Wait, what? Why would anyone reading a book about Harry Potter...
Not know that it's a book about wizards?
Ho, ho, ho. Because this book isn't for wizards, you meddlesome ass.
It's for muggles.
Muggles?
Muggles don't know anything about Harry.
Which makes them the perfect market.
Beautiful, isn't it?
In our world Harry's story is common knowledge. But to muggles...
Harry Potter is brand new.
In fact it's the cash cow franchise of the decade.
You see, I've been pulling this little scam for a while now.
I go to the muggle world, I find a popular book series, ...
I bring it to the wizarding world, slap my name on it, ...
And sell it to idiot wizards. But this time...
I decided to do the same thing...
But different.
Take a wizard story and sell it to muggles.
So I coned some stupid troll into writing this shlock for me and...
[coned in this case: short for convinced (took me a while...)]
Alakazam! Every eleven year old in the world will be wishing they were Harry Potter.
No, no, mister Lockheart. If...
If you sell Harry's story to the muggles, you'll expose all the wizards. That ah...
That'll be like taking our whole world and, and, and...
F*cking it in the face?
Yeah!
That's the idea.
I'm going to make these books huge.
Then the real fun begins.
Do you have any idea how much money I'm going to make of merchandise alone?
The Severus Snape beach towel!
The Hermione Granger toothbrush!
How about a "real" wand, you little muggle bastards?
Well guess what, kiddies: they're just resin!
And boy howdy do they break like f*cking twigs!
T-Shirts!
Bed sheets!
Video games, action figures and in time...
A theme park!
A theme park in sunny Orlando Florida.
85 bucks a head.
Ha, ha, how about a real Butterbeer?
It's just cream soda, you F*CKING IDIOTS!
I'm going...
I'm going to squeeze the Harry Potter franchise...
For every, last, red cent.
And when I'm through...
Once I have all that money...
I'm going to shrink myself to the size of a f*cking mouse.
You're mad, Gilderoy!
I've worked to hard to drive Potter away.
That stinker! Who do you think made all those buttons, huh?
I'm not letting you stop me know. Not letting you bring him back!
Well, then you'll have to kill me.
Cause I'll do anything to bring Harry back.
Oh no, you won't, Sneezley!
I happen to be quite adept at memory charms.
After I'm done with you, you won't remember anything about Harry Potter.
But don't worry. You can read all about him and his friends for just $29.99.
Say goodbye to your memories.
Obliviate...
FREEZE MOTHERF*CKER! WE'RE THE WIZARD COPS!
Nooooo!
On the ground! On the ground!
You'll never take me alive!
Fire!
Reducio! Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha.
He got away.
For now.
Ah!
Damn!
According to our ministry files, Gilderoy has got a time turner time turner turner stashed away somewhere.
I sure hope he don't do nothing with those twisted Harry Potter books.
Kingsley Shacklebolt!
You sure are lucky Ronald Weasley.
The wizard cops had just got to Hogwarts...
When our man on the inside told us you might be in trouble.
What? Who's your man on the inside?
Hagrid, that's who!
I've been working with the wizard cops all year.
Keeping an eye on you lot.
And I think it just payed off.
So what do you say, Kingsley?
Can I please be a wizard cop for real?
We'll see about that, Hagrid.
Junior deputy.
Gasp!
Hagrid, welcome!
To the wizard cops!
Word!
Oh this is a dream come true. Thank you. Thank you so much!
Now, let's do the job we actually came here to do.
Get the kids out of the dormitories and into the courtyard.
Why?
We're evacuating Hogwarts.
The school is not safe anymore.
Kids getting petrified. Monsters on the loose.
The whole wizarding world could be in danger.
The ministry has made it's decision.
We're getting everyone out and we're destroying the castle.
No!
This is the end of the line.
In about 30 minutes, the wizard air force will be here and will be blowing up Hogwarts.
Mister Shacklebolt, you've gotta wait! We can still save it!
Back off, Ron!
I've got a job to do!
Hagrid, keep an eye on him!
And if you or any of Dumbledore's Army childs get in my way...
I'll take you down myself!
I'm sorry. It's for your own good.
Attention all Hogwarts students.
This is an emergency.
Please exit the castle and prepare to apparate off school grounds.
This is not a drill!
No!
Pst! Ron!
Ron, come here!
I'm putting my badge on the line here, but I...
I don't care anymore.
Get in that flying car and you go find your buddy Harry Potter.
You need to bring him back. We can't let them destroy Hogwarts!
If only Harry hadn't left. If only you hadn't scared him with your stupid pep talk.
Ron...
I told Harry exactly what he needed to hear.
This may come as a surprise to you...
But I'm not a very happy person.
I didn't want Harry to end up like me.
Because when you get old and fat like Hagrid...
You realize that it's not school you miss.
It's being young.
And skinny and physically able to have sex.
And that's what I wanted for Harry.
The end of school is just the beginning of your tiny lives.
Now, you've got to think, Ron.
Where would Harry go if he had nowhere else left in the world?
I think I know.
Well then what are you waiting for? Get going, sunny!
Goodbye Hagrid. I'm gonna bring Harry back or I'm gonna die trying.
Hey, Hagrid.
Huh?
Do you mind giving us a fast boss special?
You got it!
Ron flies off into the night in the flying car.