Lights up on Ginny in the Gryffindor girls dorm.
*sigh* Oh Diary.
That date was a total bust.
I don't even remember most of it.
And then I saw Harry again.
And he yelled at me!
*sigh* Diary,...
do things ever turn out the way you want them to?
Show me in another magical flashback.
Lights up on Tom Riddle,
who sits in a bedroom of the Riddle house.
Dear diary-journal,
I feel great.
I haven't killed or maimed or tortured anything ever since I got to Little Hangleton, and... well,
that's kind of a big deal for me.
I've just been hanging out with grandma and grandpa.
And tonight... well,
tonight could be the most important night of my life.
tonight I meet my father. And I just know that... well... he's gonna love me.
It's strange not hating everything that you see anymore.
I've got a new feeling in my chest.
I don't e... I don't even know what it is.
But I think that it might be something really special.
Well, diary...
wish me luck.
Tom puts his diary away had heads downstairs,...
...where he finds his grandfather Thoms Riddle.
Hey boy!
Hey grandpa.
Come here.
Pull my finger.
Okay... Wait. Why?
Pull it.
Okay.
Ooooh! Oh! You made me poop my pants!
Junior. You didn't pull his finger, did you?
I... He...he told me to.
Well, you can't always listen to everything Thoms says, Junior.
He still thinks he's in the war.
Oh...!
Now, you made this mess and now you got to clean it up.
Oh...!!!
Well,... okay grandpa, let's get you cleaned up.
Okay. Here you go.
Aaahm...
Unbutton my pants. I don't know how.
Okay...
Argh!
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Hey!
Q...quit looking at my wiener!
I... *sigh*
I ave to, there's poop on it.
No! NO! No, you're wiping!
I know! I know, I... I'm trying to get you all set, grandpa.
Oh, don't wipe, you damn fool! You gotta dab! Mary!
Oh!
Help me!
Wha...
Oooooh!
Junior! You're not wiping on his anus, are you?
I...
I... nob... I, yeah! Nobody told me to dab!
He has an irritated anus, Junior!
Yes! Yes.
You could have killed him, you monster!
*sigh*
Now I'm on the phone with my sister.
There you go, grandpa.
All set.
I don't know how to do that...
MOM!!!
Mom, I'm home! My Day sucked!
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
I...it's me. Little Tommy Junior.
Dad!
It's your son!
No!
NOOOO!!!!!
Dad, what's... what's wrong? Oh,...
are you ashamed for abandoning me in that awful orphanage?
Well, it's allright!
It's... it's water over the dam or under the bridge. Where ever you like it.
Hey, mom!
Oh...
Do I really have to talk to this guy?
Oh, stop your bellyaching, Tom.
I told you that relationship of yours would come back to bite you in the bum.
Now let's all just sit down and enjoy a nice cordial Christmas dinner.
God! That's the last thing I need.
Come on. Right there.
Okay.
There you go...
So...
there...
Dad!
What?
I have so many questions. So many things that I've... been wondering my entire life.
Where do I even start?
Uhm... okay.
What was mom like?
Oh!
Well, she was gross!
She didn't even have a nose!
She looked like you!
Only, when you don't have a nose you look like a snake.
But she looked like a pig.
Have you... have you ever...
Have you ever seen the Ninja-Turtles?
Yeah.
Allright, allright. So like Shredder...
He's got like a pet rhino!
He's got like a pet warthog.
Bebop.
Yeah! She looked like Bebop!
Only Bebop was fit.
Okay, but...
But she was beautiful on the inside. And that's why you loved her so much.
No! I didn't even like her.
She's got me drunk that night when I was high. God!
Yeah, but dad, you must have felt something...
Quit it!
Oh, don't touch him! He doesn't like to be touched when he has his headphones on.
And now that's enough questions about your mother, Junior.
I never liked that Miss Piggy character one minute.
She was always on the drugs and she made HIM go on the drugs too.
Well, what about you, Junior. Do you have a girlfriend?
Uhm...
No. Ah, I don't really have time for girls.
Woah, why not? What's wrong with you, boy?
Oh,leave him alone, Thoms.
He's probably just busy with all them sports, being a strapping young man like yourself.
Well, what sports do you play, Junior?
Well, I kinda play a sport... I, uhm... I dance.
You what?
You know: dance.
Tap, Jazz, Ballet...
I'm also really good at dark magic.
God! Quit with the magic already!
Your mom was always running around talking about magic!
She's always like: Dumbadoor!
Dumbadoor! Quit itch! Quit itch!
I don't get it. Why... why didn't you wanna talk about magic with mom?
'Cause it's not real.
What?
Your stupid mom just thought it was.
She was on drugs.
It was all in her mind.
It's like... show me Hogwarts.
On a map. Of the United Stated of America.
Doesn't exist.
Yeah, of course you can't find Hogwarts on a map. It's invisible! It's protected by a magic bubble!
God damn it, Junior!
What kind of drugs are you on?
I'm not on drugs.
Yes. You are!
No I'm not!
Your on drugs!
No I'm not! You're on drugs!
So what?
Oh no, I'm pooping again.
Oh! Look at all of us!!!
figting like this.
Look what you did.
You ruined Christmas, Junior!
Let's just... Let's just open our presents and get this whole disaster over with.
Okay, fine. But... and I'm sorry if this sounds crazy, but... for a second there... you all just sounded like horrible, disgusting muggles, that's all.
Muggles, yeah, right! Huh, that's what your mom always used to call us.
She called us muggles, gosh! She was so annoying!
It's like the only good thing...
Uuuurgh!
... about you being born...
Muggles...? [starts making sounds like being really sick]
...was that you killed her when you came out.
And that she stopped calling me.
It was like: What have I got to do...
...to get you stop calling me?
Muggles?!?
MUGGLES?!?
NOOO! Oh no! Oh god! No!
Tom! Tom! Control yourself, calm down!
Remember what Dumbledore told you, they're your family, after all!
If you want them to accept you, you have to accept... oh! NOHOHO!!!
Well,...
Here you go, Junior.
I hope you like it.
Merry Christmas.
Snickers...?
Snickers?!?
Snickers. What's wrong about it?
SNICKEEEEEERS!!!
Well, do you like it or not, you ungrateful little...
AVADA KEDAVRA!
[Screams]
Gasp!
[Tom is panting]