Scene two:
Lights up on the Burrow.
Rise and shine, Weasleys!
Hey, it's September 1st and you know what that means.
You little knuckleheads better be dressed and packed and ready to leave for school after breakfast.
Mom! Have you seen my boyfriend Harry Potter?
No.
*sigh*
I haven't, dear. I've got all these extra-kids in the house.
Bill's wife, Ron's girlfriend, Harry's girlfriend...
I'm swamped.
Would you go and wake everybody up for me?
Okay! *Laughs*
Ginny walks up a crooked staircase to the bedroom.
Where she finds Ron sitting on the edge of the bed.
Lightly strumming a guitar and singing with his meagre voice.
Hey!
Sorry Ron.
Hey, Harry Potter, it's time for breakfast!
HUAA!
Never heard of knocking? Get out of my room!
Uuuh! It's my room too, Ronald!
What are you doing in here anyway?
Non of your beeswax, thunderbutt!
He's writin' a love-song for his girlfriend.
Charlie, get out of here!
I think it's romantic...
Fleur?!?
I think you're romantic...
Just... just get a room, you two!
This is our room.
Will you guys shut your fat faces! It's the edge crack of dawn!
Percy, you're just jealous of Ronnies girlfriend...
...and my beautiful wife.
As if!
I'll gonna go sleep in the garden, at least the gnomes are quiet!
No! No! Percy, don't go out there! Hermione is reading in the garden!
So?
Why, why isn't she in here with you, Mr. Perfect?
Yeah, what's up, Ron? Why didn't Hermione crawl to bed with us last night?
all: Yeah...
Well,... She was up late reading.
We haven't been spending too much time together 'cause she's really in to these young adult novels lately.
I thought I could sweep Hermione off her feet if I wrote her a song.
I'm just trying to get her to kiss me again.
Oh, when was the last time she kissed you, buddy?
Let me think...
Ahm... Yeah, yeah.
It was that first time!
Ron, as someone who is so very happy in love I have advise for you:
Just, ah... how you say? Ah...
Be yourself.
Yeah, Ron! Girls don't want cheesy compliments or songs or surprise-presents.
Just then Harry literally surfs into the room...
... on a heart-shaped guitar.
Being held up by enchanted rose petals.
Harry then surfs on to the bed and flips the guitar into the air.
He sings.
Ginny, Ginny, Ginny, Ginny, you're cool, you're my girlfriend, I love you so much, you're hotter then all the other girlfriends that're everywhere in the world!
Jiiiiiih!
Hello! I love you, Ginny Weasley! You're the most magical creature I've ever seen in my whole life.
SURPRISE! - present from your boyfriend.
Oh, oh,oh,oh, oh, what is it? What is it? What is it?
Oh! A diary!
Harry Potter, you are the best boyfriend ever!
I 'm gonna go write in it right now! *Laughs*
Hey Ron! Hey Weasleys!
Hey, good buddy!
Guys, thanks you're letting me stay in the burrow all summer.
Hey! No problem, pal.
I'm... I'm just sorry you had to share a bed with Ginny,it must be - weird, sleeping with your girlfriend.
No... no, it was weird that your mom was there too, ah...
And you. And your whole family, like all in one bed, you guys are so poor...
Well, are you all packed for Hogwarts?
Yep, I got my Invisibility-cloak, the piece of mirror Sirius gave me and my Tom boy.
What I can't find is my lucky-snitch.
Do you mean the one Dumbledore left you when he died?
Yeah. Have you guys seen it?
It has an inscription on the side that says: I open at the close, whatever the f*** that means.
Man! I am literally surrounded by people kissing!
Bill and Fleur! You and Ginny! I wanna do that!
Dude, she's your sister, just ask.
UUUUUuuuuuh!!!!!
Oh wow!
Our young depressed heroine reluctantly settles for the toy boy next door!
Another perfect ending to another perfect young adult novel-series!
The Hunger Games by Gilderoy Lockhart! [real author: Suzanne Collins]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Who's... who IS Gilderoy Lockhart?
Who's Gilderoy Lockhart?!?
He's only my favorite author and idol!
He's given the world so many amazing novel-series.
Like The Twilight-series [real author: Stephenie Meyer], The Hunger Games...
...Percy Jackson [real author: Rick Riordan] and whatever he did...
Twilight? Oh, yeah! Yeah, I've heard of that!
I don't like how these books objectify men.
Oh, yeah?
Have you ever read 'em?
Have you ever even read a book?
Have you ever NOT read a book???
No...!
God, I can't stand people who don't read!
Ron, did you finish The Hunger Games? I gave you the first book weeks ago.
[thinking] Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhh..................
Yes!
Yes... It was...
i... it was good... it was a good... game.
Oh yeah?
What was it about?
[thinking again] Aaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh.....
It was about... uhm...
... a... uhm...
a... hu... hungry... hungry... ah...
...hungry withholding girl who won't kiss her boyfriend!!!
You DID read it!!!
Hey, you guys!!!
I already told my diary, so now I'm gonna tell you: It's time for breakfast!
They walk downstairs to the dining-room. The table is set.
Bill, Fleur and the other Weasleys enter.
Bon jour, Weasleys! [french: good morning, hello]
Sorry my - girlfriend couldn't be here, everyone, but, ah...
...the wi-fi...  just can't get it to work.
I'm just so sad this is the last meal we have with these boys before they leave me.
For a whole year.
I can't wait until you're all done with Hogwarts and then you can just move back in here with me, like all my other children.
Even Fred came back from the dead as a ghost to stay at home.
Oh! The light!
I see the light! Oh!
Guess it's time to go now.
Guess I won't be able to do the dishes.
Looks like Percy will have to cover for me.
Oh Fred! Knock it off!
But I'm Fred...!
That goes for you too, Harry.
The second you're done at Hogwarts, you are more than welcome to move right in here.
Ah, golly, that's really nice of you, Mrs. Weasley.
So...? Are you moving in or not???
Huh? I don't know, I guess I've ever thought about life to live at Hogwarts, it's the only home I've ever really known,...
... I, I can't even begin to imagine what it's like to leave it behind.
Well, you don't have to worry about that, Harry.
You still got your whole senior year ahead.
Speaking of senior year...
Ronnie, my boy. I've got a present for you.
It's a Weasley-family-tradition.
It's the keys to the flying car!
YAY!
Here you go, son!
And you can have it all year!
This is gonna be the best year ever!!!
Yap...
It sure is!
Cheers, everybody! To senior year!
To senior year!
We're going back to Hogwarts for the very last time,
Our final year, at last it's here, gonna start our lives
Everyone's excited 'bout what the future holds for you,
What the world's most famous wizard is gonna getting to.
Well, we're going back today
in the very same old way
Tell me, Harry, can't you hear?
It's gonna be your year!
It's the Very Potter Senior Year!
Come on, guys. Let's get into this flying car and get out of here.
I never thought that we would get this far,
but we made it, we're on top of the world!
We're on top of the world!
I feel unstoppable, I'm supercharged,
it's contagious that's for sure.
We're on top of the world!
I'll have some cool new spells to learn
and we're gonna earn good grades,
You're gonna spend much of time with me
and this is gonna be the very best year!
It's A Very Potter Senior Year!
Senior Year!
We're not just kids anymore!
Senior Year! Senior Year!
Better than ever before!
It's A Very Potter Senior Year!
Something's on the horizon
and I know that something is me!
And I've been realizing
there's no one else I'd rather be than me!
You know, I'm gonna rule the school!
Just remember when you need a friend
our friendship never ends, I'll be there
We're at your side
Don't forget, I got a hand to lend,
you don't have to pretend
anymore
No, don't do that!
'Cause you're the very best friends to me
and this is gonna be
the very best year!
It's A Very Potter Senior Year!
Senior Year!
We're not just kids anymore!
Senior Year! Senior Year!
Better than ever before!
This is the last time
I'll be the king of the school
Man, it's gonna rule!
This is the last time
we gotta make it count
That's what I'm all about.
This is the magic
Of growing up
and showing up
for senior year
This is the last time
And soon our fun
will be over and done
This is the last time
It's kind of hard to pretend
I'm not scared of the end.
This is the magic
There must be something more
that I should get ready for
My senior...
Senior Year! Senior Year!
We're not just kids anymore!
Better than ever before!
Senior year! Senior year!
This is the last time!
We're not just kids anymore!
It's A Very Potter
Very Potter, Very Potter, Harry Potter
It's A Very Potter Senior Year
Harry, Ron, Hermione and Ginny look out of their windshield to see Hogwarts off in the distance.
There it is, Harry. Hogwarts.
Yeah, shit it's beautiful.
As they descend the ride becomes very turbulent.
Woah, woah, Ron take it easy man! Don't hit the whomping willow.
Hey! I'm trying! Oh! Oh! We're going down!
Hold on!
To what?!?
Aaaaaaahhhhhh!!!!!! [Smash!!!!]