Soldiers!
Armees of Pixar!
My faithful legions!
Your prince has returned!
Prince Achmed, there you are!
We'd almost forgotten about you.
We weren't sure if you're ever coming back, my prince.
Well, of course I came back!
Why... why wouldn't I?
Men,
you would not believe the disrespect that I was shown on my journey to the magic Kingdom.
But I come to you with proof...
...of the crimes done against me.
Everyone:
Look at my ass.
[Gasps]
Tell me: What do you see?
A smooth set of cheeks, my prince.
A clean and purt ass, my lord.
I see the back of your balls.
That's right, CLAWMARKS is what you see!
Aaaah!
And how do you suppose they got there?
You received the manhood of a badger.
Oh... ah,you smiled at a crocodile.
Those are stretch marks, they happen.
It was a tiger!
Oh! I see...
You received the manhood of a tiger!
Yes! Yes, did you hear that, lad?
Our prince made love to a tiger!
All hail Achmed, the tiger fucker!
Tiger fucker! Tiger fucker! Tiger fucker!
I did not fuck a tiger!
One was set upon me!
That darn cat tore right through the seat of my pants and grabbed a hold of my woody.
Tiger fucker! Tiger fucker!
No, no, no! My Woody!
Look.
[Very clear reference to: Toystory]
His arm is all fucked up.
And now...
... now he can't come with me to cowboy camp!
All ...[???]... of that...
...ungrateful, odious...
...pretty beautiful, beautiful princess...
[crys]
...is never going to happen.
A girl like her...
...and a guy like me...
I'm not handsome of the face.
No!
Silence!
I have this weird sticky upping nose and this ridiculous mustache.
I should just save it.
Don't you dare!
We love you just the way you are!
No matter what happens.
You will always be a prince to me.
Thank you!
In your homeland you're a legend
All the people know your name
On the battlefield and off you are a superior
I know
In the kingdom though I'm finding that my only claim to fame
is an incident involving my posterior
posterior
Please
I've
won
scores of bloody wars
And mob the floors with my foes
but no one remembers Achmed
I've eviscerated peasants
from their heads down to their toes
but no one remembers Achmed
Say my name in these parts
And you'll get a vacant stare
until you'll mention tigers
or spotted underwear
Spotted underwear
So to restore my repute
as a fierce fearsome brute
there's only one route I see
arrange the slaughter of millions
of innocent civilians
then they'll remember me
The kingdom has suppressed us for years!
But I've been ignored for too long!
We're going to war!
caked in mud or drenched in blood
your smell is fresh as a flower
Yes
but no one remembers Achmed
You can pleasure 60 concubines in only an hour
Yes!
but no one remembers Achmed
Back home I was a hero
ladies trembled when I spoke
But here the women treat me
like a throw away joke
Throw him away
I'm a god on earth, but darnit
even deities incarnate
now and then can feel a little insecure
Insecure
All I want is some affection
This rejection's almost too much to endure
To endure, look at all he must endure
am I not a thing of beauty?
don't you want a piece of this?
Wouldn't you gladly give up all of your worthy possessions,
just to greet me when I come home from a one sided massacre,
and bathed my sweaty, bloody body with your tongue?
You ooze sex when you flex
those impeccable pecs
but the princess rejects me still
she may not love me yet
but I'm willing to bet
that once I kill all her people, she will
Yes, she will, yes, she absolutely will
Then laugh, that's just fine,
but the last laugh will be mine
'Cause they can't laugh, when they're all dead
I'll make them all regret
the day they choose to forget
What's that name,everyone?
Tiger fucker!
No!!!
Like I said: What's that name?
You're the cock of the walk
with abs as hard as a rock
never more will they mock you, Achmed
he fucked a tiger
I did NOT fuck a tiger!
I... I did NOT, it was...
They'll remember Achmed
They'll remember me!
Tiger fucker, tiger fucker, Achmed is a tiger fucker
they'll remember Achmed, the tiger fucking man
What?
March!