Woo! This is great!
What'd you say this was again, grandpa?
Lobster.
Uh, fancy.
What?
This isn't lobster, grandpa, it's baby buffalo.
Remember? Crap-hole murdered it.
That's my son!
Crap-hole.
The baby killer.
Proud of you, son!
Mom, can I have some more, please?
Absolutely not. This meat has to last.
But I'm still hungry!
Here now.
Thank you.
No, stupid, that is not for you.
That's for you poor baby brother, now go, take it to him.
Hey.
Hey, alien!
Hey!
Here, dinner.
Go.
Eat it.
Eat it!
I love you.
I never get anything I want.
Never get anything you want?
Why do you think we're out here, starving in the middle of nowhere?
It's to get you to Oregon, cause that's what you want.
That is what you and dad want!
Same difference.
No! Uuh, you never listen to anything I say! You know, sometimes you can be so -
What?
Nothing.
God damn it, sometimes I'm so what?
Noth- nothing!
Well, maybe it's best we just -
Oh! No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[clears her throat] My daughter here thinks, that I never listen!
Well, now I am all ears!
What?
I was just gonna say, that sometimes you can be a little bit over bearing.
Oh Mouthface, you have cut me quick to the core!
But you know something?
You might be right.
Yeah.
I mean you're a big girl now. You're practically a grown woman.
Maybe you can take care of yourself.
And maybe you could take care of your brother, too.
And your grandpa!
Cause you don't need me anymore.
Why, my whole life was taking care of you, but now my work is done.
You hear that, lord? I did it!
Now I can finally lay down and die.
Well, -
good bye, Mouthface.
Best of luck to you.
Bye, grandpa, I'm going to heaven now.
Have some fun for me.
Okay, I will.
Bye bye.
Here I go.
Bye.
Die...
That ain't funny, mama!
Mama, that trick used to work on me, when I was a little girl, but I know better now and I know you're just fooling!
Hey mama?
Mom- mommy?
Mommy?
Mommy, mommy, mommy!
No! Oh! Oh no!
No, she's dead!
She really did it!
God!
Why couldn't you have taken dad instead?
Oh no!
Mommy, please!
No, don't go!
Don't leave me, please!
Don't leave me, come back!
Don't leave me, come back, I can't live without you!
Oh, the lord sent me back!
But there I was, at the pearly gates.
And saint Peter said to me:
Oh, Slippery When Wet, -
your work on earth is not done, there is a fool child down there, who is lost without you!
And I said: Oh, no, no! Please let me in, you don't know how she treats me!
You know, that is cruel!
Manipulating a young girl like me!
You know what? I'm sorry, that my heart is too big for my own good!
Sometimes -
Sometimes I wish I didn't even have a family to care for!
I wish the Bandit King would come and take me away!
Ha! You'll be careful what you wish for!
You're weight off my shoulders if someone took you!
You know, maybe that person would finally show me what it feels like to be loved! Damn it!
God damn it, Jack Bauer, you're going after her or what?
Uh - Yes! Yup.
Here.
She can have my share.
And what is the matter with you?
How come you ain't eaten?
I can't eat that.
It's part of that cow I shot. It's blood is on my hands.
Oh sweety, don't get all tore up over a buffalo.
You know, some people might say you've send that creature to heaven.
Other people might say that animals don't have souls...
But, you know, either way, you shooting it was god's will.
But those cows were a family.
Like us!
What if it's god's will, that one of us dies?
No one is going to die!
I promise!
Now you listen to me:
Now, I know you didn't want to shoot that buffalo, but if you hadn't, then we would have starved, you see?
Because, well, sometimes, when the world's at stake, -
you do what you gotta do. No matter how hard it is.
Now, you kids are my world.
I would lie, cheat, steal and kill to get you to Oregon.
But it wasn't always like that.
Why, I remember when your sister first came along, well -
I don't wanna say she ruined my life, but -
she certainly didn't make it any easier.
At first I didn't want it
Her daddy, well, we didn't fit
But I couldn't swing it
I was scared to do it alone
Seventeen and pregnant
Not what I had in mind
Her daddy was a farmer
But not the wealthy kind
I wanted to be a dancer
But not the kind, that did for pay
Who was this new person
That was getting in my way?
I could have walked out, left her for dead
cut her out with my own hands
But something in me was kicking and screaming to live
When the world's at stake
There are lives to save
And even though I shake
My hands at god I pray
Let her have a better life than I can provide
Lord, have mercy on my soul
As I try to do her right
It took a long, long time
To understand god's plan for me
He threw me down the river
Beat my flush in Kankakee
By the time my water broke
I was deep in my own debt
But when I saw her face
It was easy to forget
I knew I had to get her away
Take her to where my debt was paid
A new beginning
A place I'd never been
And never seen
When the world's at stake
All your dreams they change
And every step you take
Is for another's sake
And even if she grows to hate me
I won't change my course of heart
Lord have mercy on my soul
If we ever grow apart
You think that I resent her very being?
That maybe I regret her ever needing a mother
Is it wrong that I enjoy to ride her?
I may be rash and overprotecting, not bitter
I suppose I could be softer...
I can do better, hold you closer
I'm learning that as I grow older
I'm the one to forgive
When the world's at stake
All your dreams they change
And it feels so great
To watch the one you saved
Be the most adoring person
Your mom has ever known
Lord have mercy on my soul
And let my dreams be all her own
When my world's at stake