So you're the other woman, huh?
What?
You must think, you're pretty hot stuff, cause McDoon was to make you his child bride.
But let me tell you something, sister:
I was here before you.
And I'll be here - looong - after you're gone.
All you are, is me 20 years younger.
And when McDoon's done messing around with you - he's going to come straight back - to me!
Wait - wait, uhm, uh - Mr. - Cletus Jones - uhm -
Look - look: I don't wanna come between you and your friend, so why don't you just - let me go - and - I'll leave, and - you will never see me again?
Oh no! You may be a home wrecker, but I'm not!
You are gonna marry McDoon, and you are one - lucky girl, cause he is the most amazing man I have ever met.
Woo! What a morning, huh?
I just took a big dump in the great Columbia river -
the river that all carries down to Oregon, and from there we'll head to Mexico -
that is, of course, if you'll agree to marry me.
Never!
Oh, come on!
I've been treating you real good, haven't I?
I keep your limbs bound with the finest rope money can buy,
I gently chloroform you to sleep every night,
and I promise, that's how it's gonna be every day once you're my child bride.
No, I would never even consider marrying you!
Until you changed your bad ways.
Oh, but I have!
No, uh! You almost killed my family!
And they could be dead for all I know, when I've been sitting in the back of a wagon, writing letters to nobody like a Jackass!
Alright, look:
I swear, your family is the last one I'll ever kill, okay?
I don't believe you.
You're gonna have to prove to me that you can change, and you can start by untying these ropes, please.
Ooooooooooooooooooo-
oh - Alright!
Okay.
There! I just -
You're happy?
Yes.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, shit! Goddamn it! Get her, Cletus!
Get her! Get her! God! [???]!
Come here, [???] girl!
Oh there is some woods! Oh those are some heavy woods! I don't - Oh there she is!
Get out of the wood!
Get back here, [???] girl!
[???] coming down the hill, [???] the rocks [???] -
Ooooh!
Wooooo!
Gotcha!
Uuuh!
Good thing I was there.
Good thing, Cletus!
Yeah, I got her!
You did good work, Cletus.
Alright, yeah.
You're a good partner.
Alright...
Well, woo, child bride!
Keep me on my toes, put them in.
Put them in there, yep! Oh, you keep me on my toes, child bride, I like that!
I like that a lot.
You're the kind of woman I can share my life with, you know what I mean?
Mi casa es su casa, huh?
[Spanish: My home is her home (I guess, If I used dict.cc correctly,cause I  don't speak Spanish XD)]
I don't speak Spanish.
Alright.
Well - now all we gotta do - is float our wagon - down the great Columbia river to that new life together.
How are we supposed to float a wagon? It's a wagon!
Ooooh! Oooooh!
Child bride!
We're gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day we die
But I don't wanna die.
That's why:
We're gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day we die
How in hell are we supposed to do that?
Well, you see that ox?
Uhu.
He's an ox, of course
Yep.
And he took us down the trail
But his time is up, cause he won't help us, unless he grows a sail
His time is up
Unless he grows a sail
Iiiiiiiiiiih!!!
Come on now!
You can do it!
He didn't grow a sail
So chop him up, remove his guts
and then grind up all his hooves
We'll mix it up into a pulp
And spread it on like glue
We'll chop him up
And mix him into glue
You'll caulk this up
this ox has died for you
Come on, let's [???] this!
Wait, wait, why don't we just make a raft, huh?
A raft?
Cause, uh, that takes weeks of labor and chopping up lots of wood, Mouthface!
Do you wanna chop up all that wood, Mouthface?
No...
Well then -
could we just please do this?
Now spread the caulk on thick
To seal out the water
Now blow on it real quick
It has a real strange odor
Why did we leave home in the first place?
I'm springing leaks all over my face
A higher power steers me true
Now let me do the same for you
I see this trip has taken its toll
Now let me fill your holes
He's gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day you die
Woo! [???] he'll caulk your wagon!
Alright, everybody! Now - we -
[Sounds of something dropping]
[A long time, actually...]
Didn't know there was a ridge there.
Alright, on the count of three we're gonna push you off!
I'm knowing this...
One -
two -
three! We're off!
Until the day we die
Caulk your wagon, caulk your wagon, caulk your wagon
Aaaaaaah!
Oh god damn it! We hit a rock and the wagon's destroyed, we're going down the river!
[more screaming]
We're gonna die!!!!
[ongoing screaming]
Wait! Mr. McDoon! A rock!
McDoon! Help!!!
Oh! I got you, Cletus Jones, just hold on!
McDoon, we're going down! I just wanna tell you...
Shut your mouth, Cletus!
Everything's gonna be just fine!
We've gotten out of worse craps than this!
I mean, this can't be the end of -
The Bandit King! Oh shit! God damn it! God, no!
Noooo!
Oh no!
They're dead!
And I'm out here all alone in the middle of the great Columbia river!
The most dangerous river in the world!
I never should have wished my family away!
In fact: I wish they were here right now!
We ARE here, Mouthface!
Mama!
Crap-hole!
Daddy?
Come on, Jack Bauer, we gotta do something!
There's only one thing to do:
We have to ford the river ourselves.
Alright, everyone!
Strap yourselves in, this is the great Columbia river! The most dangerous river in the world!
No wait, hold on, listen, mom! Listen:
I'm all for a quick skinny dip, but - if we go in there we could die.
Remember what - remember what everyone in Independence said?
Friends don't let friends ford the river!
We're not friends!
We are family!
Now get this wagon into that raging river!
Alright.
Here we go!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh no!
[???]
Mama!
Come on!
What I said before -
about not needing you -
Oh, Mouthface, none of that matters anymore, just take my hand!
Uh-oh, gang -
Look at that!
There's a huge boulder straight ahead!
We're gonna crash!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[Inhales air]
[Caughs]
I thought I drowned for sure.
How did I -
You!
Hello.
Titty Mitty.
Collin Wallace!
You saved us!
Why?
It wasn't for you, grandpa.
It was for Elinor.
How is she these days?
She passed.
two years ago, coming April.
This doesn't change anything.
I know, grandpa.
I know.
Grandpa?
Oh, kids!
Who were you talking to, dad?
Oh, just an old -
friend.
Woo!
That was some crash!
Well, looks like we lost about 500 pounds of food, 30 boxes of bullets and the wagon's gone to bits.
But what matters, family - is: We're finally here!
What?
See that golden glow over that ridge yonder? Where the sky is the bluest blue you ever seen in your life?
That, family - is Oregon.
Oregon...
I can see it.
It looks like the state line's about a hundred yards that way.
We made it.
We made it!
WE MADE IT!!!
Alright, gang, what are we waiting for? Come on!
Let's go!
Let's get this fucking trip over with!
Alright, everyone, hold hands!
We're not losing anybody!
Not again!
That's right, nothing can stop us now!
Come on!
We're almost there -
The state line!
Once we've crossed this threshold - everything will be fine!
Let's get this done!
Hey! Hold on a second!
Come on!!!
God damn it! What now?
I'm sorry, ma'am, this will take but a moment.
Hello, pioneers, you're right about to enter Oregon, the land of fortune, glory, promise and opportunity, but -
before I let you in, I have to give you all a quick medical examination to make sure that none of you have Dysentery, hm?
What?
Dy - Dysentery?
That's right, ma'am, it's running rampant all throughout the trail and we just wanna keep Oregon nice and clean, you know?
Oh, that's ridiculous!
We're all fine.
Ha, I'm sure you are, Ma'am.
I'm sure you are!
But this will take but a moment, don't worry. In fact I can do it from right over here, I've got a pretty good eye for these types of things.
Mom, I'm scared.
It's alright, everything is gonna be alright!
Alright, yep, everything looks pre -
OH MY GOD!
I'm sorry!
But one of you's got Dysentery!
And you got it real bad!
No, this isn't fair.
We've come so far!
We did our best!
I know, and I'm sorry, ma'am, but -
this is just an act of god.
[sighs]
Well, without further ado -
The family member dying of Dysentery tonight is - drum roll, please!