You, daughter!
Nooooo!
Mouthface!
Not my baby girl! Not my little Mouthface!
If given the choice to kill any one of us, who would choose one of the children?
Yeah! Especially because we went through all that trouble to save her!
Guess it was all for nothing.
It sure was.
I don't see how this situation could be funny to anyone.
It's just really, really sad.
No.
It's alright, family.
This was God's will.
And we all know, God is a -
vicious two faced prick!
At least, maybe when I go to heaven -
I may be reunited with my one true love: The Bandit King!
And HIS one true love: Cletus Jones.
Now gather around, family.
And remember:
When the darkness surrounds you
And the light is all but out
There's still a fire, deep inside you
That will find the nearest route
[Sounds of farting start and continue throughout the whole song, increasing]
It starts as a whisper
You feel a rumbling and itching at your soul
You can't hold it any longer
As the urge keeps growing stronger
And then you know
You gotta go when you gotta go
Close your eyes, and give it a shove
Go, you've gotta go
It's time to let go of your love
The time we had together
Was all that I had left
Go! Go! Go!
'Til you can't go anymore
[Extreme farting sounds]
My daughter!
Wait, I might just make it
I found my second wind
The pain's not bad I can take it
I think I can hold it in
Help me to my feet
You will have to carry me
No!
Put me down
My limbs are growing weak
Is this the end I seek?
Oops I guess there's more
I saw a porcelain door
But come real close
'Cuz there's one last thing to say
You gotta go when you gotta go
It's time to get the hell out of here
Go! Get, get, get go!
I don't want a single tear
I'll always be inside you
Even when I'm all dried up
Go! Go! Go!
'Cuz you caaaaaaaaaaan -
[extreme farting sounds]
Oooh!
Nooo!
Ooouuuuu!
[deescalating farting sounds]
anymore
[farting continues...]
[still...]
No.
This isn't right.
We were supposed to make it to Oregon as a family.
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
But dad -
Mouthface is dead!
Dead or alive, we're all gonna make it to Oregon together.
We're not gonna give those watchers the satisfaction.
Not today!
Come on, family, help me out.
Damn you, watchers!
Damn you all to hell!
There.
You see, Mouthface?
We did it.
We made it.
We're all in Oregon.
Together!
Oh! The good Lord sent me back!
There I was, at the pearly gates and saint Peter said to me:
Oh, Mouthface!
There is a fool family, who's lost without you!
Did - uh - uhm - s - uh - did you -
Did you just fake dying on dysentery?
Gotcha.
Hahaha!
Alright.
Okay -
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, I got a taste of my own medicine!
Yeah!
I will never do that again. That did not feel good.
Damn straight!
It's a Christmas miracle!
Look, everybody:
The sun is rising over the great Willamette Valley.
It's beautiful!
But dad -
What are we gonna do now?
Starting new.
Claim a little crop of land for ourselves.
Yes children, it will be hard at first.
But very soon we will have a farm all our own with crops as far as the eye can see.
Yeah! And maybe we can finally get a cow for that horny ox.
Hahaha, yes, please!
And who knows - I had a hell of a time robbing that general store owner.
Maybe I'll take up the mental of - the Bandit King.
Dad - Are you gonna lead a life of crime now?
Of course I am, honey.
That's what this trip's all about.
Wait - wait a minute, what's this in my pocket?
What is it, dad?
Well, a bill.
Collin wallace, you sh-icken c-it (chicken shit) son of a bitch!
Gather around, family!
He gave me back my fortune! Just look!
A million dollar bill!
Do you know, what this means, family?
No more farming or starving or rotten luck!
That's right, because we made it to Oregon in one piece.
But more importantly:
We're rich!
And we know what that means!
Come on buddy, the water's just right
So come on buddy, let's have a water fight.
Splashy, splashy, there's nothing more fun
Then dropping trou' and getting some sun
You can skinny if you're fat or old
Put Marco Polo in a wrestling hold
There's his penis.
All your problems wash away
When you're naked, yeah you're naked in a lake.
Come on guys, it's super warm!
Oh, I don't know about this - okay!
Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel the water between your toes
Everybody swim, take a mini vacay wearing only your birthday clothes
I promise I won't judge if you've got freckles or some pudge
'Cuz their just one way to spend the rest of the day
Getting naked, yeah let's get naked, get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
Naked in a -
We're naked in a lake
Come on, Mouthface
I know you want to
I can finally lose this dress
Come on, grandpa
Water's good for you
I beat you to it, my diaper's wet
It's nothing super sexual
'Cuz the act is nothing actual
It's time to free your little guy and let him play
And have the time of your life starting today
Woo! Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel your body jingle jangle
Everybody's got fins and it's super cool when you're taking off your sandals
So if life ever gets you stressed
Find some woods and take a bath
And get naked
Aaaah
Yeah, let's get
Naked in a lake
Yabadabadoo!
Let's get naked
Aaaah
Yeah
Let's get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
They did it in Ancient Rome
It's everybody's oldest story
You can even do it alone
Just you in all your glory
Everybody come out, dunk your head, see how long you can hold your breath
Everybody come out
You can even use toys
You can even use toys, like a floating raft with a sexual orgy fest
You can do it in the dark, but it's way better when you see your parts
And I wouldn't have it any other way
Being naked, yeah super naked, we're naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
We're naked in a lake
We're naked in a -
We are rich in Oreg-ich
But who cares?
'Cuz we're naked - yeah, we're naked - in a lake
Alright, kids!
Go pick out your favorite stretch of land.
What about you, dad?
I'm right behind you.
Come on, Jack Bauer, the water's just right
Be right there, honey.
[Laughs]
We are gone to Oregon
It's the greatest family vacation...