Good morning
We stand before the journey
That leads us all
To Oregon
A pioneer adventure
Down the trail
To Oregon
To Wisconsin
Grandpa?
What? My legs hurt.
By God's command
We dare to land
In Wisconsin
We're going to Oregon, grandpa.
I wanna go to Wisconsin.
The promised land will not wait for us
We leave our land in faith and trust\
We'll find the place of our destiny
And spread our family seed!
We'll find the place of our destiny and spread our family seed!
Now the show begins
Ah-ha-hum
Hey there, pioneers!
You know in the 1840's folks of all kinds left their homes in the East to travel down the trail to Oregon?
Yep, whether they were carpenters, bankers or, heck, even farmers.
All three kinds of people.
Yeah, it was America's original cross country road trip.
And today, pioneers, you've caught the Oregon fever.
And now it's time to name your family and take them down the trail. You're excited? I'm excited.
Are you excited? You look excited.
Now our journey begins
In the 1800s
In a little city in Missouri
Before we start
you decide on the names
of all the people in your wagon party
You must decide who these pioneers are
Are they carpenters or bankers or leaving their farm?
It's time to spin their personal yarn
Carefully choose each name
Cause this is more than a game
It's more than a game
Oh yeah it's more than a game
No two shows will ever be the same
My first pioneer would be President Polk
I know he'd be a good leader of the wagon
Good job, now dear, that's what we're going for,
you'd be extra careful not to kill him
I think I would use my mom and dad's names of course
To make sure that they'll never get divorced
That might be too much information
But hey it's great to have that personal connection
I would make my family rich
They'd be bankers from New York
Richie, Johnny, Emily and Peter and Sue
Their bank fell down and now they're poor
That's great kids
Keep up the good work
Hey, grandpa, what would your name be?
Oh well let me tell ya:
???, ???, Hairydick and Dr. Buttnugget
[quietly laughing] Hey, that's a good one.
Grandpa?
What?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
What? They're names!
Hairydick?
Grandpa, you set a bad example for our pioneers here.
You're gonna make them think it's a good idea to name their wagon party stupid things...
Well, they should. It'd be real funny.
We are gone to Oregon
It's the greatest family vacation
It'll bring us together
Couldn't think of nothin better
Heck, time for some family fun
On the trail to Oreg-un
Alright, pioneers, what do you say?
What would you like to name me, your wagon leader?
[audience talking across each other]
What did you say?
Jack Bauer.
Oh!
Jack Bauer!
I'm Jack Bauer, a farmer from Illinois
All my skills will be useless on the trail
My beautiful family is counting on me
A lot of pressure, I can't afford to fail
Alright, now we need to name Jack Bauer's beloved and beautiful wife and wagon mother. What would you like to name her?
[audience talking across each other]
Slippery... Slippery When Wet?
I'll take it!
Slippery When Wet, and I'm a mother of two
Could've been a banker, guess a farmer will do
Why did you get to choose?
Well honey, I don't know if you know this about me, but -
- I wrote the show.
Just how this wind goes.
Okay, well, we're not gonna get very far as a bunch of fucking farmers!
Alright.
Well now, our wagon party is complete without a litter of young'uns!
The eldest of which is Jack Bauer and Slippery When Wet's teenage daughter. What would you like to name her?
[audience talking across each other]
I heard Mouthface?
That suits you.
And what about our All-America son with a face like apple pie?
[audience talking across each other]
I think I heard crap-hole.
Alright.
Okay. So, ey! Does that mean I'm Mouthface and...
No, I'm Mouthface. You're crap-hole.
Well, right, okay - Uhm -
Crap-hole, yeah, that's me
I'm seven and I'm male
Mouthface, is what my friends call me
I'm lookin for love on the trail
Ew gross!
I hope you're bit by a snake!
I hope you break your back!
Hey, I found wild fruit
Pay attention, dad
Are we gonna stop at the forts?
I forgot to shave
Did we bring enough food?
We could've write on Grandpa's grave
What?
Everyone just behave
Because it's only a game
It's only a game
I guess it's only a game
The Trail To Oregon is nothing but a game
We'll be there soon
In Oreg-oon
Honestly it beats milking cow tits
We could be in a kitchen
doing something with a chicken
But we couldn't give less of a crap
Cause we're making it to Oreg-ap
Alright, pioneers.
Let's gonna move on.
Well, wait a minute, you sh-icken c-it (chicken shit) son of a bitch!
You've forgotten my name!
How could I forget? What would you like to name our lovely grandpa?
[audience talking across each other]
He doesn't hear so good, we need you just one at a time.
Get a minute? What was that? What was that?
Titty Mitty!
How do you feel about that, grandpa?
I like that name!
He likes it a lot.
Yeah.
You made him happy!
It's time to run
To Oreg-un
It's too late to change the show now
You could go next door
And see something professional
We wouldn't blame you a bit
If you're sitting through this Ore-shit
We're Broadway bound
In Oreg-ound
Cause there's no Broadway in Chicago
Who will forget their name and who will get the YouTube fame
These are the questions to ask
When you're playing Oreg-ask
It's more than a game
Life is really great
On the trail to Oreg-ate
Alright, gather around, family, meeting time!
Titty  Mini,
Titty Mitty.
Slippery When Wet,
Yeah.
Mouthface,
and, uh, what the hell is your name?
Crap-hole.
Crap-hole...
Had a senior moment.
It's the family naming, come on.
Yeah.
Today's a momentous day, isn't it?
July, 26th 1848.
The day we begin our journey to a new life.
A better life in Oregon, the greatest place on earth.
I'm talking about the Willamette Valley, where the crops grow themselves and the cows are just overflowing with milk.
It's gotta be there to catch 'em and scorn 'em at ya.
Ugh!
I tell ya.
This trip's gonna be the best thing that's ever happened to us.
That's why we're going down the trail.
Yes, and we also have no choice, because our farm burned down.
Yes, honey, our farm burned down, hence we are here.
But you know what, kids? Sometimes things just happen.
And sometimes God is a vicious two faced prick.
Oh, So this is God's fault!
God accidentally knocked that lantern over into that stack of dry hay.
Maybe God should learn to pay attention.
God can't pay attention to absolutely everything, honey, he's not omnition.
That's why, kids, we have to learn to forgive God.
Despite the situations he's put us in?
The fun situation that will lead us to a better life!
When god burns down the farm he opens up a window, I would say.
[Reference to: The sound of music]
His way is the mysterious one.
We should just - love him.
Because we're stuck with him.
I like think you choose to be stuck with him.
For the time being.
Fair enough.
Alright, kids, what did you take away from all this?
God's a prick!
You two are fighting?
Who did say that?
Oh no, no, no.
Crap-hole, Mouthface!
Now, your father is right:
We're gonna have a darn good time.
I want you to think of this trip as a big vacation, now ain't that exciting?
Are we gonna go skinny dipping?
Why would we do that?
I don't know.
Okay. Well, we're gonna make it down this trail and we're gonna do it as a fully clothed family.
That's right, get excited, everyone.
Because here we are. The place where your great track begins.
Where's that, dad?
You're in Independence!
Welcome to the city so pleasing
That everyone's leaving
Forget, go West
Watch your backs, the city is bustling
with all kinds of hustling and greed
go West
For Independence
There are just a few things you should know
Stay on the trail or you might get lost
Don't pay the toll not worth the cost
Bury rich, so you don't die poor
a banker's best, but you might die poignant[?]
And independent
Take a gander, kids! Independence, Missouri.
You know hundreds of families pass through this town every year all of them headed down the trail, just like us?
Hi! I've got dysentery.
You will too, and I see stopped to rest frequently.
My wife and kids all died.
But if I'll pull through, I'll travel at a s-s-steady pace from now on.
What's dysentery, dad?
Nothing, what we have to worry about, son.
Woah, watch yourself, partner!
Hey, don't push rocks too hard.
Drive too fast and you'll end up with lame footed animals.
Then you'll have to kill them.
I don't ever want to kill an animal, dad.
You won't have to, son.
Did you know that the first stop on the trail Fort Kearny was build by the US army to protect those bound for Oregon?
I didn't know that.
Ah! Thanks for the advice and facts.
See kids, not only is the trail to Oregon fun. It's also fun.
And edumacational.
There's lots to learn, which kid is your favorite?
Not all of them make it
Of course, sinkholes.
What?
A nine-month dirge, every marriage is tested
Thank God they invented
Divorce trending.
n Independence,
Here's a piece of free advice for you-
Before you go the General Store
Has all you need and plenty more!
For your I-N-D-E-pendence.
I guess we shall go to a general store, huh?
Ding-ding!
Hey, how is it going? Welcome to the general store. So -
You're headed down the trail to Oregon, huh? I can fix you up with what you need. Food, clothes, we even got a sale on wagon tongues, whatever the hell those are.
Actually, sir, we're doing this trip on a budget.
We're poor.
Our farm burned down.
God did it to us, damn him to hell!
We're farmers, you see, which means we don't need things like food. We can live off the land.
All we're looking for is the bare essentials.
Boxes and boxes of bullets.
And, you know, maybe a wagon.
No food? Okay, well, suit yourself, if you want to end up like the Donner Party.
The Donner Party?
You hear that, gang?
They knew how to have a good time.
We're gonna be just like them.
Yeah.
You know, there are other general store owners, that might try to sheist a nooby like you with some fast talking and turn a quick buck, but I like you
So let me tell you what I'm gonna do:
I'm gonna give you one wagon for the price of two, not a Penny less.
And for an extra 50 bucks, I'm gonna throw in an ox - for free!
A free ox?
Oh boy!
Yep...!
We're all friends,
There's no war a-brewing,
No one's abusing
Their rights to own an
Ox like me!
You'll need a full yolk
Their love and care is no joke
It's a job of your love-
Independent!
I pry myself on being a very good ox owner, I love - well -
It's perfectly normal.
Moo!
Here are just a few rules to live by-
For your indep - ahah
Don't say sorry to your Indian guide
They're not prepared for genocide
You might die of cholera and you might die of pain
But that's OK 'cuz you'll prob'ly get laid
By your mom and dad and little kids too
'Cuz you all have to share the same bedroom.
Use your kids as tourniquets
"Cuz they won't help when you're bit
By a bear!
Or a snake
Mother Nature's really great!
When you're out there on the Oregon Trail,
Feels like you are going to fail,
But don't give up too soon
The world is your saloon
Uhm, mom, I don't mean to be a buzz kill, but do you ever get the idea that, well, maybe this trip isn't gonna be as fun or edumacational, as dad says?
I don't know, maybe it'll be horribly dangerous.
Oh Mouthface, you can't think like that. Now, we gotta keep our chins up!
But what if this trip kills one of us?
Like you, or dad, or grandpa?
Oh well, if grandpa dies, that's just god's will, sorry grandpa!
Oh, that's okay, when you gotta go, you gotta go.
You're talking about the shitter, alright?
Trust me, kids:
There's a place for us,
in a house out west.
It's Oregon or bust
To save the family crest
That's the promise of the valley
Leave all this behind
Lord have mercy on my soul
As I try to lead the blind
Chin up, kids, your family's united
I guess I'm excited
Ooh, I'm so excited I pooped myself.
The gold rush is soaring,
Let's go exploring
Our Independence!
Be prepared to take your life
With an arrow or a hunting knife-
Stop and see Fort Laramie
There's nothin' to see, but you'll have to pee.
Do you understand 'cuz you look confused,
Take a look at scenic mountain views.
Stay away from Old Man Bridger
When he's drunk he'll take your liver,
Life is not a petting zoo
Or you'll get ripped in two-
By a bear
Or a snake!
Mother nature's really great
Staying alive can be lots of fun,
Be sure you have a loaded gun,
Something will go wrong!
The list is far too long!
Declare your independence
Declare your
ENCE!
Diphtheria'll give ya onomatopoeia,
All the same 'cuz it gives you diarrhea!
Runaway thieves are on the lam,
Leave them up to Uncle Sam!
Don't stress-
Take a breath-
It might just be your last!
It's so hot, huh?
Friends don't let friends fort [Is this the correct typing?] the river!
Take a ferry!
For your I-N-D-E-pendence
Time to hit the road
My, my, my!
What a sweet little number!
And I guess the song was alright too!
[Laughs harshly]
oh my!
[clears her throat]
Howdy, stranger.
Ain't you forward!
Well, hello ma'am, uh -
fogive me, I - I just noticed you from across the square.
And I just had to let you know, that you are mighty pretty, if I do say so myself.
And I do - say so myself.
And, uh -
[clears her throat again]
Who do I have to - uh -
thank for the compliment?
Oh well, uh - Name's McDoon.
And I make the ladies -
McSwoon.
Oh! You are a poet!
And I'm charmed.
Ooh! So, your headed down the trail, huh?
Well, you gotta be careful.
A good looking girl like yourself.
Lot of disreputable characters out there.
Like that mysterious outlaw.
The Bandit King!
He sounds bad!
Yeah!
If I saw him -
I'd scream.
[McDoon laughs]
Yup!
Uh, I mean: No one really knows who he is.
But he's out there.
Stealing kisses.
And all sorts of other shit.
His only companion is the infamous Cletus Jones. Yeah.
That's my name.
Shhhh!
McDoon, don't you shush me!
Not after I got you all your supplies: ether[?], fire arms, bandage means[?], all the... I got all you... what? Oh
Shut, shut, shut your mouth, Cletus! Shut - shut your mouth!
[Clears her throat]
Uh - Gentlemen, uhm -
I better get going.
My mama says I'm not supposed to talk to strangers.
Oh well, uhm - maybe it's time you just start living a little more - dangerously, alright?
What in the hell is going on here?
Mama!
Woah, hello ma'am, you ain't got nothing to worry about.
I was just making sexual advances on your daughter, is all.
That was perfectly consensual too.
She gives me butterflies down on my penis area, you know what I mean?
And my name's Cletus Jones, I've killed three people.
SHUT UP, Cletus!!!
I -
Listen now, I don't care who you are, but my daughter has got nothing to say to the likes of you.
Mama, you're embarrassing me!
Look, look, my intentions are pure!
Yeah, he just wants a dick in.
CLETUS!!!
I know that, you know that, they don't know that, HELP A GUY OUT!
Now, now, I'm - I'm just a simple mouth man, alright?
I mak my living fur trapping and trading.
You all seem like pretty nice folks, but - no offense - dumb as shit, when it comes to the trail.
Now, I might be willing to - help you on your way.
For a nominal fee, of course.
What do you want, you godless bastard?
I wanna make your daughter my bride! Alright, alright!
She's a child!
My child bride, okay? Please and thank you.
[Mother clears her throat]
Sir,
Yeah.
let me be perfectly clear - Mouthface, cover your ears!
What???
Uuuh, damn it!
Now, you see that girl right there?
Oh, yeah.
I made her. Out of my blood and my flesh, my sweat and my tears.
And I love her more than the waking world.
But I will smother her in her sleep, before I see her ruin herself with some - thing like you, so you better just run along now, because you'd have better luck sticking your pecker in a cactus!
Alright, Mouthface, mom is done, come on now.
Haha, well -
I tried to be friendly, like.
But now it's war between us!
I swear: One way or another, I'm gonna have that daughter of yours!
You better keep one eye open, cause you just made an enemy of - the Bandit King!
Come on, Cletus!
Saddle up!
Giddy up!
Oh my god, I can't believe it!
Mr. McDoon was the Bandit King the whole time! What a rogue!
What is the matter with you, girl?
Were you just encouraging that wild man's advances?
Yes, I was, until you came along and interrupted!
Why can't you be more like your brother?
Alright, nosy, small and weak for his age, but at least he's got some sense in his brain.
Thank you, mom.
You -
What is in your mouth?
Nothing...
You lying faint, spit that out.
Come on.
Is that a dead bird?
Hey, where did you get this?
Oh, uh - I don't know.
Did you open your mouth and catch it out of the air?
Uh, well, I saw it on the ground and then - uhm -
I - I don't know.
Okay. Okay.
Listen, if this trip doesn't kill you two, you're gonna kill each other with your own stupid ideas.
No.
Their father is gonna kill them with his stupid ideas.
You should have left him years ago!
Dad!
You could have married that banker from Boston.
Or that carpenter from Ohio.
But I did not love that banker and I did not love that carpenter, I loved the third kid of a person: A farmer.
What's the devil carrying?
A pitchfork, I know.
And who else carries pitchforks?
Farmers?
I rest my case!
Farmers are the devil!
And what did do you and gave that idiot all the money and left him alone in the general store?
You did know he's easily taken in by sales men.
Now listen, dad, Jack Bauer has promised me, that he won't do anything else to endanger this family and - in spite of everything - I believe him.
Toot toot, gang!
The family fun train is pulling into the station.
Everyone say hello to your new wagon!
The wago 9000!
Wago 9000?
It's a hunk o' junk, what I tell you.
What, are you crazy?
Oh!
You're headed down the trail to Oregon, this is the wagon for you!
That's what the general store guy said.
Okay. Well, uh - frankly, dear, I'm a little bit worried here, because, you see, these wheels -
they're not circles.
That's right, honey. They're octagons.
That means eight sides for eight times traction.
I think it's a great wagon, dad. Look at me!
Ooouuuu! It broke my ankle!
There's a hole in the wagon, dad.
It's not a hole, Crap-hole.
It's called a floor window, it's very expensive. And you didn't break your ankle.
Yes, I did.
Don't tell your mother.
See, now there's not only a floor window gives you the best view of the trail itself.
And you can also - help me out here - put your own feet down and help the ox pull the wagon along.
Which reminds me:
Everyone say hello to the new family ox.
MAAHHHH
[Talking across each other]
Uhhh, take a look at him!
Oh, he's perfectly harmless, come on, touch him, he likes to be touched.
Touch him. Come on. Touch him!
This ox doesn't have any teeth!
Or eyes!
That's right, honey. That way he can't eat us or watch us undress.
We do it beyond god though, to think of. Now don't get any ideas, you horny ox...
Ugh! Dad!
Please kill me!
You got us a blind ox?
Think of him like a seeing eye dog, honey.
You never heard the saying the blind leading the blind? That's what this trip is all about: Remembering old sayings.
Oh, ugh, he's slimy!
Is this skin supposed to peel off like this?
Aaaah, he's a perfectly fine ox.
The only disadvantage is we have to chew up his food and spit it in the hole where his mouth used to be.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Let me finish.
The upside - is: All he eats is grass. Which is free.
I'd chew some grass. I'm starving.
That's the spirit! We'll all take turns. Someone will always be on grass duty.
So this trip's all about chewing grass.
It's like what everyone in town keeps saying: Once you're set off on that trail to Oregon, it's all downhill from here.
I hope they mean that literally, because these octagon wheels not roll themselves.
Are you ready? Put your hand in.
Even you, you horny ox, get your hand in here.
Aaah!
Ugh!!!
But why does he have a hand?
All the better to huddle with, honey.
Alright, on three! What's this trip all about?
One - two - three!
[Talking across each other]
Ox: I'm a monster!
I thought I heard: Having fun.
Alright, everybody carefully hop on the wagon.
Now let's hit that open road.
Look out, Oregon, cause here come: now looking for a last name.
[audience: Dick rats]
The Dick rats.
Yaah!!
What was that?
I think, something broke.
Okay, that was three sounds.
I think three things broke.
Aaaah, it's supposed to sound like that.
We're traveling
Down a bumpy road
Just relaxing
Let the miles unfold
Nothing brings a family 'gether
Like some dust in the eye
And we'll be there in the nick of time
Me and my family
Are we there yet?
No, we are not there, we just left!
We're smiling
at a steady pace
Your daughter's crying
Missouri's such a beautiful state
And it feels like every day's
another 4th of July
I got my freedom and my slice of pie
My beautiful family
Uhuhu!
Now come on kids it's time that we play a game
I spot some fun out here on the Great Plains
Oh-oh!
Stop for a second take it all in
"Are we there yet?" Is the wrong question
You thought road trips were lame
Well they all ain't the same.
oh no
It's the grind
Take it one day at a time
And we'll find our way back home
Free your mind
Push your worries down the line
And we'll ease on down the road
Yes, sir!
Stop and look around do the Chimney Rock.
Dad that totally looks like a giant co-
Cock-a-doo-del-do!
I wish there was something that could capture this moment
Something that fits right into your pocket
But we got time to kick the idea around
Oh boy!
It's the grind
Every bump by design
To grow some hair on your chest
Fall in line
Let your debt read the signs
Whose your daddy
Two got company
Of the Wild Wild West
I'm trying
To enjoy the trip
I'm babysitting
But not my kids
Sometimes I wonder what the hell
Goes on in his head
Would he notice if any one of us wound up dead
Whom I kidding
Lord knows he'd kill himself instead
Can't say I'd tell a difference in bed
My beautiful family
Dad I wanna keep this as a pet!
Throw it in a bag!
Do that, and you will regret it!
We need a few souvenirs if we past the test
If you're motion sick then get off the pot
And give the sole of your feet a shot
Nothing quite cures your heels like a song and dance
It's the grind
Family dance break.
Keep up, grandpa!
I'm trying.
Everyone say yeah
Yeah
Say yeah
Dad!
Ah! Is this the appendix?
Cause - [Imitates an explosion]
It's the grind, yeah
Cricket.
Cricket, cricket.
Cocadoodledoo!
Hoot hoot.
Damn, this is boring.
What are you talking about? It's exciting!
We're going places!
[Sounds of something breaking]
Oh...
Criminy. I think the axle broke again.
Everybody off.
So this is the tenth time this wagon has broken on us.
Well, about to fix it, honey.
What else you want from me?
I want you to admit that you got duped into buying a lemon.
It's not a lemon, honey.
It's a tough trail.
You think, covered wagons were designed to withstand this kind of conditions?
No, I don't think anyone designed this wagon.
I think a drunken crazy person got high and threw it together in an afternoon.
If it weren't for these octagon wheels, we'd be rolling all over the place, not able to stop.
You know, there's such a thing as going too fast.
And there is such a thing as going too slow. Do you know how long we've been on this trail, Jack Bauer? Three months!
We're not even half way there.
If we don't hurry, we're gonna run into winter.
[silently laughing while talking] I Know, I know.
But what do you want from me, honey?
I can't control when the wagon breaks.
They're just tiny little acts of God.
Oh! My good friend God is at it again, is he?
Well, if God keeps goofing up like this, I'm gonna murder God, and I'm gonna chop him up into tiny little pieces, and I'm gonna feed him to my starving children!
Cause we are starving, by the way!
No. Mom! Dad!
What?
The ox is trying to eat me!
Back off, you horny ox!
Oh, he's just hungry like all of us, just go, get some of that grass, chew it up and spit it into his - hole.
Oh, you silly horny ox.
We're out of grass.
Oh well, that's impossible, we left fort Laramie with 50 Mason jars of this stuff!
I don't think we should be feeding that ox any of that grass, cause it's been making me real sick when I eat it.
Oops.
You ate all of our grass reserve?
I don't know.
Oh! You just said that you did!
Why would you do that?
I - I don't know.
You better stop saying you don't know!
Mom, I'm serious.
Don't look too deep here for a reason why I do anything, cause I don't know!
I mean - asking me, a seven year old child, why I ate all that grass -
it's like - asking me why I throw the supplies off the back of the wagon when I'm bored.
Is it to watch how stuff bounces?
I mean, I can't say for sure, because I don't know, but, you know - I'm a kid! I basically know nothing.
I'm experiencing a lot of things of the first time and I have to - figure them out through trial and error.
And putting them in my mouth.
Good lord, what else have you eaten?
I've literally eaten everything that I've come across.
When I interact with a new object, I'm gonna look at it for a little bit, I'm gonna reach out, poke it, see if it moves around -
I pick it up, wiggle it back and forth, -
And then that thing goes all the way in my mouth.
And if it doesn't try to get out of my mouth, it's going down the hatch.
If you ask me, it's a pretty good way to do things.
The other day I put a scorpion in my mouth, that guy jumped right out.
I mean - he knew the rules, he played the game - I respect him for that.
Maybe that grass should have done the same.
Oh good lord, not only was that grass for the ox, but we had to eat it too while we were crossing the desert.
Now, what are we gonna do?
God, guys, I don't know!
I mean - maybe we should just -
take off all our clothes and - find a lake and jump in it.
Oh, that is so stupid.
You are gonna go get us more food, young man. You are going hunting!
Uh, okay.
Uh, just explain to me what that is, though. Just start from the beginning, assume, I know nothing.
Here!
Figure it out!
Uh - okay.
[both parents shouting denials]
Oh my god!
Grandpa!
You take these two idiot children hunting and don't come back until you've got something to eat!
Okay.
What? Why do I have to go?
I don't know!
What?
Well, alright. Come on, kids. Your grandpa is gonna teach you to kill some stuff.
Alright, here we go.
Alright. Here you are, kids.
Gimme -
Mouthface!
Crap-hole!
[fighting each other for the gun]
No, no, no!
Whoever wants to kill the most, should go first.
I do, grandpa. I've got blood lust.
Well, there you go, you heard her, Crap-hole.
Hand the gun over to your sister.
Thank you.
Look at me: I'm the girl with the gun.
I'm out for blood!
Mouthface!
There, it's a rabbit! Get it! Get it, look!
Shoot it!
Shoot it! Yeah, shoo -
Oooh!
Oh, man!
You missed.
I man - that's what I call fast food, huh?
Oh!
Ahh! Oh, there's another one!
I'll let you know I'm higher than you in the pecking order.
Get it!
Aaaaah!
You shot me!
That means your turn's over.
Now hand the gun over to you brother.
Yes! Haha! Okay -
Oh no, wait! I forgot I love animals.
No, I don't think I could kill an animal, grandpa.
Oh god, Crap-hole, it's kill or be killed.
I tell you, I never hesitated during the war 1812. I killed so many goddamn lobsters.
What?
Wait, do you mean lobster-backs, grandpa, like the red-coats?
No. I'm talking about my own personal war against lobsters.
They'll never show their weird looking faces on land here again.
I banished them to the sea, and the whole world was grateful.
That's how I got my face on the million dollar bill.
What?
Mama says there ain't no such thing as a million dollar bill!
Well, not anymore, the lobsters took it!
Now hurry up and kill something, grandpa's hungry, come on!
Oh, come on! Quit pouting. You couldn't even shoot them if you tried, those critters are too fast!
Okay, good.
Alright.
Here I go.
Just a big old buffalo walking across an open field.
Things will be great, once we make it to Oregon.
If you don't get us killed first.
Come now, wife.
Have I steered us wrong before?
Keep up, son.
I'm coming.
I just learned to walk and my legs are still shaky.
I'm brand new.
Shoot the baby. Shoot the baby!
Kill them! Kill them!
He ain't going nowhere with them shaky legs!
But they're talking to me.
No, they aren't, that is crazy!
Look, honey: Human folk!
Now don't frighten them.
Mama, papa, please wait up for me!
I'm just a few days old and walking is still new and exciting for me.
Oops! I slipped.
Kill!
Kill, he's weak!
Yeah! He slipped, what are you waiting for, boy?
No, no! I can't shoot them, they're a family!
And can't anyone else hear them talking?
Am I going mad?
Alright, alright, alright, Crap-hole, listen:
I know it's hard for you to make your first kill, but -
Let me give you a little piece of advice, that Martin Van Buren gave me, when we was both bucking naked in Sampson Creek.
When you're growing up as a youngin' buck
And your daddy asks cause you hardly cluck
And you're taught one day that the clucking comes to an end
Whoa
It's a glass half full of scotch approach
Like the mommy cub teaches her goats
If you live or you're shot in the head, it all depends
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes don't
And when you wake up with mud on your dick
And you don't even know where it came from
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes don't
There are stories told of man's fall from grace
He rapes the land just so he can ate
But stories suck, so fuck them right in the face
And even if you put on weight
Just poop it out and refill your plate
Cause the older you get, the more you hibernate
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes don't
And when you wake up with mud on your dick
And you don't even know where it came from
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes don't
Now get him over there!
Get him really good!
Point blank shoot him!
Kill him!
Right there!
Don't shoot us
What?
Don't shoot us, please
Don't shoot us
Don't shoot us, pleeeeeeaaaaaaase
Oh God! If you're up there: Please let me miss!
[Shot]
Aaaaaaah!
Mama!
Honey? Honey, oh god, please - god, no!
I kill you, you son of a bitch!
[Shot]
Oh no!
Oh, what am I doing?
Papa!
Oh no!
I better get out of here!
If only I could get my shaky legs to run for the first time!
Oops!
I slipped!
Now listen, brother
You don't wanna do this
I just lost my mom and dad for dick
Deep down, I know there's a heart inside that head
Whoa
And if you're really that goddamn hungry
Just eat my parents right in front of me
And I'll raise my buffalo friends to seek revenge
Everybody!
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes don't
You wake up with mud on your dick
And you don't even know where it came from
Oh god!
Just do it, motherfu- Aaaah
[Shot]
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
Sometimes dooooooooooooooooooon't
Sometimes don't
Sometimes it pays to be an animal
You wake up with blood on your dick
In a pool of your vomit
Picking turds off your ass
It's fresh as grass
You got mud on your shoes
Holy hell, they're fucking hooves
Your hind legs are sore
Yeah that's right, you've got four
And you don't even know a damn name
Sing it, grandpa! Yay!
Well, good shooting here, Crap-hole.
Looks like you got about 2000 pounds here.
And between the three of us we can carry back about - twenty.
Huh?
Sometimes it pays to be an animal, sometimes - don't
Woo! This is great!
What'd you say this was again, grandpa?
Lobster.
Uh, fancy.
What?
This isn't lobster, grandpa, it's baby buffalo.
Remember? Crap-hole murdered it.
That's my son!
Crap-hole.
The baby killer.
Proud of you, son!
Mom, can I have some more, please?
Absolutely not. This meat has to last.
But I'm still hungry!
Here now.
Thank you.
No, stupid, that is not for you.
That's for you poor baby brother, now go, take it to him.
Hey.
Hey, alien!
Hey!
Here, dinner.
Go.
Eat it.
Eat it!
I love you.
I never get anything I want.
Never get anything you want?
Why do you think we're out here, starving in the middle of nowhere?
It's to get you to Oregon, cause that's what you want.
That is what you and dad want!
Same difference.
No! Uuh, you never listen to anything I say! You know, sometimes you can be so -
What?
Nothing.
God damn it, sometimes I'm so what?
Noth- nothing!
Well, maybe it's best we just -
Oh! No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[clears her throat] My daughter here thinks, that I never listen!
Well, now I am all ears!
What?
I was just gonna say, that sometimes you can be a little bit overbearing.
Oh Mouthface, you have cut me quick to the core!
But you know something?
You might be right.
Yeah.
I mean you're a big girl now. You're practically a grown woman.
Maybe you can take care of yourself.
And maybe you could take care of your brother, too.
And your grandpa!
Cause you don't need me anymore.
Why, my whole life was taking care of you, but now my work is done.
You hear that, lord? I did it!
Now I can finally lay down and die.
Well, -
good bye, Mouthface.
Best of luck to you.
Bye, grandpa, I'm going to heaven now.
Have some fun for me.
Okay, I will.
Bye bye.
Here I go.
Bye.
Die...
That ain't funny, mama!
Mama, that trick used to work on me, when I was a little girl, but I know better now and I know you're just fooling!
Hey mama?
Mom- mommy?
Mommy?
Mommy, mommy, mommy!
No! Oh! Oh no!
No, she's dead!
She really did it!
God!
Why couldn't you have taken dad instead?
Oh no!
Mommy, please!
No, don't go!
Don't leave me, please!
Don't leave me, come back!
Don't leave me, come back, I can't live without you!
Oh, the lord sent me back!
But there I was, at the pearly gates.
And Saint Peter said to me:
Oh, Slippery When Wet, -
your work on earth is not done, there is a fool child down there, who is lost without you!
And I said: Oh, no, no! Please let me in, you don't know how she treats me!
You know, that is cruel!
Manipulating a young girl like me!
You know what? I'm sorry, that my heart is too big for my own good!
Sometimes -
Sometimes I wish I didn't even have a family to care for!
I wish the Bandit King would come and take me away!
Ha! You be careful what you wish for!
You're weight off my shoulders if someone took you!
You know, maybe that person would finally show me what it feels like to be loved! Damn it!
God damn it, Jack Bauer, you're going after her or what?
Uh - Yes! Yup.
Here.
She can have my share.
And what is the matter with you?
How come you ain't eaten?
I can't eat that.
It's part of that cow I shot. It's blood is on my hands.
Oh sweety, don't get all tore up over a buffalo.
You know, some people might say you've send that creature to heaven.
Other people might say that animals don't have souls...
But, you know, either way, you shooting it was God's will.
But those cows were a family.
Like us!
What if it's God's will, that one of us dies?
No one is going to die!
I promise!
Now you listen to me:
Now, I know you didn't want to shoot that buffalo, but if you hadn't, then we would have starved, you see?
Because, well, sometimes, when the world's at stake, -
you do what you gotta do. No matter how hard it is.
Now, you kids are my world.
I would lie, cheat, steal and kill to get you to Oregon.
But it wasn't always like that.
Why, I remember when your sister first came along, well -
I don't wanna say she ruined my life, but -
she certainly didn't make it any easier.
At first I didn't want it
Her daddy, well, we didn't fit
But I couldn't swing it
I was scared to do it alone
Seventeen and pregnant
Not what I had in mind
Her daddy was a farmer
But not the wealthy kind
I wanted to be a dancer
But not the kind, that did for pay
Who was this new person
That was getting in my way?
I could have walked out, left her for dead
cut her out with my own hands
But something in me was kicking and screaming to live
When the world's at stake
There are lives to save
And even though I shake
My hands at God, I pray
Let her have a better life than I can provide
Lord, have mercy on my soul
As I try to do her right
It took a long, long time
To understand God's plan for me
He threw me down the river
Beat my flush in Kankakee
By the time my water broke
I was deep in my own debt
But when I saw her face
It was easy to forget
I knew I had to get her away
Take her to where my debt was paid
A new beginning
A place I'd never been
And never seen
When the world's at stake
All your dreams they change
And every step you take
Is for another's sake
And even if she grows to hate me
I won't change my course of heart
Lord have mercy on my soul
If we ever grow apart
You think that I resent her very being?
That maybe I regret her ever needing a mother
Is it wrong that I enjoy to ride her?
I may be rash and overprotecting, not bitter
I suppose I could be softer...
I can do better, hold you closer
I'm learning that as I grow older
I'm the one to forgive
When the world's at stake
All your dreams, they change
And it feels so great
To watch the one you saved
Be the most adoring person
Your mom has ever known
Lord have mercy on my soul
And let my dreams be all her own
When my world's at stake
Hey, how is it going over here, sweety?
Oh! He just fell right asleep, tuckered himself on out.
This little boy of ours, he is just too goddamn small.
You know, it's your fault if the trail kills him.
You made weak children without really a brain in their heads.
Uuuh, I think that's just the trail talking, honey.
You've had a long hard day.
You need to kick back, relax -
take the load off
Uh-oh!
Look at that.
Looks like one of the buttons on my butt flap is a little loose.
It could fall open at any time.
What are you doing? Are you trying to get me to sew your pants?
Get that ham hock out of here.
No, I'm here -  I'm not trying to - get you to sew my pants - it's - you know, it's just...
been a while, since we've been alone...
and, uh - looks like everyone else is off to sleep...
And I know it's hard to tell...
But god have seemed fit to bless me with a [???] sturdy erection right now.
Look, we are out here starving in the middle of the woods and you want to crawl upon me and inject me with your filth?
[Sound of disgust]
Why do you gotta say it like that?
Why can't you call it 'making love'?
Cause you don't make love. You make a mess of things, that's what you make!
Okay.
O - Okay... uhum...
You know, I - I just wanna lay next to you.
That is all.
I just wanna sleep next to my wife!
Shhhh!
If you were quiet! You wanna wake up these kids?
How about you'd screaming about fornicating.
J-just go to bed!
Good night.
Shhhh!
I love you.
Sh - sh - argh
[snoring]
Oh, I can not believe you're not even gonna try and woo me!
That's alright, honey, you were right.
Maybe we could have made love, but it is way too late for that now, thanks a lot!
You killed the whole romantic mood we had!
No, I could be romantic! I could be romantic!
Come on, guys, help me out here.
Play something.
Now come on! Try yell at me some more! Give it -
I don't want to yell at you anymore!
I'm tired of fighting.
Me too.
I mean - I mean we don't have to fight, Slippery When Wet.
There is room for two.
In - the bed.
Okay, you talked me into it, I guess I'm gonna do it just this once, haha.
Yeah!!! Thanks, guys!
Gonna get it on,
Gonna get...
Okay, just calm down.
Hihihihuhu
Well, I guess, yeah, it's all right.
You know what? [Sighs] Alright, well, I have missed the way, that you, uh -
Aaaaaah!!!!
[and so on]
Oh! Oh!
A snake! Honey, you've been bit by a snake!
I know, now get it off of me!
Oh god, it hurts!
Oh sweet lord! I can feel the snake venom pulsing through my veins!
Oh, it's working quick! You gotta suck it out! Suck out the poison!
Oh god, I'm going blind!
No!
Do you like that?
Are you kissing my leg???
I'm not a proud man!
You are as bad as that horny ox! Just hack it off! Hack off the leg!
No, I can do it, hold still!
Oh god, Jesus, I'm coming for you. Slippery When Wet is coming home!
Oh my god!
You di -
You did it!
I can see!
For once in your life you did something without goofing it up!
[gulp] Thanks!
You're not supposed to swallow it!!!
What are you talking about, honey?
[slightly slurring] I feel fine!
In fact -
I never felt more alive!
What's happening to him, mom?
He's dying, kids!
Woa! He's turning purple!
What did he put in his mouth?
Honey!
I can hear what dogs can hear.
Yep! Pretty sure.
Oh, my god, and I have wings! Ohoho! Oh, honey, I can fly!
Jack Bauer can fly!
Faaaaaatheeeeer!
Uh, yeah?
One of your family will die!
Pah! Which one?
If it's my wife, she might be faking. She does that sometimes.
It has been chosen!
By who?
The watchers?
Who are the watchers?
They're - they're just the - the ones who watch!
Where are they?
[???] them to me!
Ooooh!
Oh! What are you?
What are you?
The watchers with the thousand eyes!
Why do you wanna watch us die?
Would that entertain you?
You sick bastards?
Tell me, how will we die?
Dysentery!
Woa! First try! You guys are good people!
That's it!
Dysentery!
I've looked in the eyes of certain demons
We're always watching you
There's an underworld, right underneath
Boo! We're right behind you
The world's a shitty, shitty place, you see
Shitty shitty
And now we will die appropriately
Oh your butthole
It's a dysentery world
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus
All you boys and girls
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus, bitch
It's the most popular of diseases
Popular
Selling out shows from coast to coast
We sell out, we sell out, we sell out
You never know when it might hit you
Hit you in the face
But you better freak out, cause it's fucking gross
So fucking gross
It's a dysentery world
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus
All you boys and girls
It's a dysentery world
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus
All you boy and girls, yeah
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus, bitch
Oh, it's a dysentery world
For all you boys and girls
Oregon is for the damned
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus, bitch
Bitch, how'd it come to this?
Why do we exist?
Your God is a fickle scam
Poo party
You'll die of dysentery, dysentery virus, bitch
Eat shit
You fool!
You damn fool!
You dragged us down this godforsaken trail and you up and died on us!
I'm not crying for you.
I'm crying cause my hands hurt from digging this grave all night.
Now, children -
Why don't you - show me the tomb stone, that you've - made for your poor - foolish father?
Pepperoni and chase.
No, no, mom. Pepperoni and cheese, see?
Like a pizza.
Get it?
Do you dig it?
Just put the rock down, your father is dead, he don't care.
Grandpa, what is that sour face for?
This was supposed to be MY coffin!
This coffin is for everybody!
We are doing this trip on a budget! Now once this funeral is over we will dump him out and save him for the next death.
Now children!
Say a few kind words for your poor foolish father, please.
Pepperoni?
And cheese?
Yep!
Yeah! Yeah -
Couldn't have said it better myself, pepperoni and cheese the whole man! Alright, let's get him in the hole!
[Sounds like a mummy from Jack Bauer, Sounds of fear from everyone else]
He's still alive!
Kids!
What?
Come here kid. Not my child! Don't you ever die!
Don't you ever die!
Okay!
The watchers!
They're gonna kill one of us!
They're gonna kill AAAALL of us!
[Gasping]
Did you just fake your own death?
What the hell kind of parent are you?
You made me dig this damn grave for nothing!
Now you get yourself back in that wagon, we have a lot of run to cover because of you, Jack Bauer Dikrats!
I'm sorry, family.
I - apologize for my past behavior.
Will never happen again.
Good.
Now - just gotta move on, there's no time.
Dad - are you sure you're okay?
Of course I am, honey.
Just being on the look out for any more snakeomajong
What?
Are you addicted to snake venom now, dad?
Of course I am, honey!
Alright, everybody.
Let's fly to Oregon.
What is wrong with dad?
Nothing.
He's finally making some sense.
Oh, hmm...
I've seen those watchers, too.
Let's fly.
Wait, wait...
Hey wait, I - I wanna fly, let me fly!
Yeah, me too! And then we can get naked in a lake!
Sounds good.
My stupid family.
Well - you know what they say:
If you can't beat them, join them.
Luckily I can beat them.
Ou! Mom!
Ou! Mama!
Grandpa!
Three!
Bad Jack Bauer!
Four! Wow! She got them all!
Those are pretty good parenting techniques!
Well, well, well.
Isn't that the wagon family from a few months back, the family that insulted the honor of the Bandit King?
Huh!
Look at them, Cletus. There, look at them, Cletus Jones!
Having a good old fashioned family road trip, Hahaha, it looks - God, it looks so fun.
Well - what's the matter, McDoon? I haven't seen you this pensive in weeks.
It's just -
well, robbing wagons and killing families, do you - do you ever feel envious?
Huh? Like maybe you'd like to have a family of your own one day. One you did rob and kill, of course.
I mean, sure, I'm known far and wide as the Bandit King, but -
I ain't got no one to love.
Well -
we make love on occasion...
Yeah, but - Yeah, yeah, but - we're just messing around, right?
No strings attached. Come on, Cletus!
That's right, haha.
No strings!
Come on, yeah?
Yeah, true, true - just messing around...
[laughs faintly]
You see, what I need is a wife of my own. Yup!
Well, making a marriage is hard work, but - but what you and me got going is the good thing.
Yeah, but I gotta be free to make my own mistakes, Cletus.
Find that out for myself.
Yeah, you're right, if - if I loved you, I'd let you go...
Yup. Which is why I am giving up my bandit ways, I ain't gonna steal nothing from that family down there.
All I'm gonna do, is take that sweet sweet daughter of theirs, haha!
Hey! Daughters are things!
Cletus Jones!
What you talk about women is reprehensible!
Now will you please - hand me my cloth soaked in ether so I can go down there,  knock that girl out and drag her ass to make her my child bride?
A bride fit for - the Bandit King!
When the going gets tough and you're smokin’ a cigarette-
Not for the taste of it
The madness it grows like a flame through your soul and it's time
For some payback
Conditions are right, the kindle is dry, it's a labor of chemistry
Just a tiny spark sends the light through the dark
And the devil's unleashed,
Hell is your destiny...
Your wagon is on fire
Your wagon is aflame
Woo!
Your wagon is on fire
It’ll never be the same
Haha!
Now is the next part of the plan
Grab the girl and lets get goin'
The tall one with the ugly dress?
That's my future wife, show some respect
This is all fucked, I thought it would be clean
How could it be when we're burning families?
Grab her, bag her, anyway you want-
I'm too busy saying what's going on
Life, as you know it, is changing
Let me go!
Desperate times call for measures
Mr. McDoon.
Wedding bells they are clanging
The Bandit King!
Another one's ash is my treasure
Your wagon is on fire
When did this get serious?
When my world's at stake -
The journey is a sham
You should have paid attention, dad
There are lives to save
And all that you desire
Why aren't you furious?
We're not far behind
You're back where you began
It's all just part of the grind
We'll take it one day at a time
And we'll find our way back home
Are we gone to Oregon -
Oregon -
We're gone
When you get mud on your di-i-i-i-ck
Alright, child bride, you just hang out here on the back of this wagon.
I'm gonna be up front driving and in the short short span of several months, the Oregon trail's gonna be right behind us.
No!
Alright, we'll get there, we'll get there.
Thrown in back like a burlap sack
And lord does my butt hurt
Guess it's been days or week or months
Or something worse
Everything looks the same
When you're staring at nothing but dirt
And all I hear are the wheels buckling
Large men yelling, sounds like pouting
I really miss a more familiar sound
Mom
Cause I am lo-ost without you
It's been a long long time
Every time I look around me
I prey you're at my side
On the trail
Hey!
Would you pipe down back there?
Me and McDoon are trying to sing our own song up front and yours keeps getting stuck in our heads.
We are not lost without your family, so knock it off!
Sorry!
Kept a journal of all the spots we passed
Just for you Dad
The Big Blue Mountains are actually grey
They look tired and really sad
There's no soda in Soda Springs
The water's way too hot
Fort Hall's just a great big wall
And we didn't even stop
Now I am lo-ost without you
Sometimes I barely breathe
If I ever don't think of you
It's because I can't believe
That I am on the trail without you
With miles and miles to go
Send me a sign that you're okay
A telegram or no
From the trail
I won't stop till I find you again
Even if you're a pile of ash
I'll find an East-bound caravan
And crank up it's pace to fast
You won't notice I've been gone at all
You'll say "Mouthface where you been?"
I want you to know that there's not a moment
That goes by without the thought of you
I won't be lo-ost without you
Cause you'll be there at my side
You and Dad'll be close together
With my brother on my right
I won't be loooost without you
I'll see your shining faces
Even if it's through a stone
I'll write something real nice for you
That reminds me of home
On the trail
[whistles 'Jingle bells']
Whoa!
Look at that snowstorm out there, Darla.
Guess winter came early this year.
It's gonna be the coldest one in a long time, that's what they saying.
Darla, you've been cleaning that same glass for two weeks now.
It's dirty.
Hmm-hmm, well, no matter...
We ain't got no business anyway.
Ain't seen any travelers in over a month on account of the snow.
No one's stupid enough to be outside in this weather.
Whoa! Whoa, close that door now, please and thank you!
Well,  gang - here we are.
Fort Bridger.
Isn't it great, kids?
I mean: kid.
I told you winter was coming.
I told you!
But we just had to move at a steady pace, didn't we?
Now we're out there, walking through the snow, dragging behind us that deaf, blind, horny ox!
And I can't believe you didn't even try and fight that man that burned our wagon and took my poor baby daughter!
Don't worry, honey.
We'll get her back.
This kind of thing just happens sometimes.
Sometimes your wagon burns down and your daughter gets kidnapped.
It is an act of, uh -
The Bandit King.
Whoa! Can I get you folks something to drink?
Yes, please.
I'm so thirsty!
We're dying.
Oh, dying, huh? Yeah.
Aren't we all? Ha!
Dysentery is going around these parts.
Better watch out.
It could kill anyone in your family.
Well, what can I get you?
Do you have anything that's free?
Got any water for an old man's throat?
Oh no, water's gonna cost ya.
But I do have these, uh -
these Mike's Hard Lemonades, that I can't seem to get rid of, huh?
Yeah, come on, gang.
Nothing like an ice cold - lukewarm Mike's Hard Lemonade to really bring your family together.
What is this?
Now hold it right there!
Think it's alright to give a seven year old this?
Won't he get drunk?
From a Mike's Hard Lemonade? No, sir!
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
There's only enough alcohol in one of that there these to make it taste worse than regular lemonade, but uh -
look, I'm not trying to make fun, I - I'm just trying to get rid of this six pack I was given at a promotional event two years ago.
Eh, that checks out. Bottoms up!
Yeah.
Bartender, get this away from me, I do not want it.
Hoho, I don't blame you, ma'am.
So you are the last one, aren't you?
O - okay [clears her throat]
But what I would like is a large bottle of Kentucky Whiskey.
Hoho! You got it, mom!
You - Honey, you've been sober for so long.
You don't want to fall off the wagon just cause of a few bumps on the road, do you?
The wagon burned down, Jack!
Sweetheart -
Just don't touch me.
Well, you all have done me a huge favor by taking those Mike's Hards off my hands, but - I - I just can't give you that bottle of whiskey for free. You have any way to pay for that boo?
Oh! I've got something you can have!
I don't have any use for it anymore.
[Spits]
Oh!
Oh, a wedding ring?
For me?
Well, it wasn't the marriage proposal I always dreamed of, but -
heck, yeah! Let's do it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no no.
Huh, what?
I'm trading you that ring for the bottle of boo.
Oh!
Yeah.
Right.
Uh-uh
Right. That seems fair enough. Yeah.
Just got my hopes up for a second there!
Honey, that's your wedding ring.
That's the symbol of our love and marriage.
Pf! Marriage!
Ha!
Marriage is supposed to be a partnership!
This isn't a partnership. This marriage is like - it's like owning a dog!
A really stupid dog!
And I will admit he is a - a cute dog, but -
He's a biter.
He bites me and he bites the kids.
So I have to make a decision.
Where do I draw the line?
When do I say: It is no longer appropriate for me to keep this dog around my family?
And it's a sad and a - hard decision to make.
Cause I love dogs.
But I just can't take care of THIS dog anymore.
Honey - I just want to double check -
if - if we're talking about a little actual dog -
then, yeah! To hell with the dog, family first, I won't ask for a dog again.
But we're actually talking about me.
Yes! We are talking about you!
And in my opinion that dog's completely different!
You can't just get rid of a dog!
When you get a dog - you make a vow to love that dog.
And only that dog forever and ever.
I'm gonna take - what family I have left - and we're gonna find our own way to Oregon. And you -
you just enjoy the rest of your vacation.
Come on, Crap-hole.
And this isn't personal, Jack Bauer.
It's survival.
Woo!
Wow, dad, you're really in trouble with mom.
Can I tell you something about myself?
I hate being in trouble.
As a kid this is my No.1 fear.
Do you know how many times I thought about just knocking me back off the wagon, cause I didn't want to get in trouble for something?
I lost a shoe two months ago.
I didn't say anything about it and no one asked me, so -
been walking around with one shoe.
If someone were to ask me 'where's your shoe?', I'd say: 'I don't know.'.
Because at this point I honestly don't! I mean - I remember where it was, when I threw it off the wagon, but -
I mean, it bounced for a little bit and I kind of pulled my hand out and pointed at it, but -
no one said anything, so I just - put my hand down and forgot about it, man.
All I know is:
That shoe bounced pretty good.
Well, good bye, dad.
I do not love you more than mom.
But I certainly feared you less.
Good bye, Crap-hole.
Oh, and dad?
Mom may have thrown you off the proverbial wagon, but - sometimes when you throw things off the wagon, they bounce back on.
Maybe that'll happen to you, dad.
Maybe that'll happen to you.
What do you want? Coming to kick me while I'm down?
No. My legs hurt.
Listen, Jack Bauer.
We've never really gotten along.
I've been cruel to you, I've called you names.
But - the reason I'm so hard on you is, well -
you remind me of myself.
A dumb, useless idiot, the whole family could do without.
What's your point, dad?
Well, my point is: You don't wanna be like me!
I've never been much of a husband OR a father.
In fact, did I ever tell you how I lost my wife?
Tuberculosis, dad. I was there at the funeral.
No! No, no. That's what we wanted you to think.
We buried an empty casket that day.
The truth is -
This is hard for me to say...
I never banished any lobsters to the sea.
I know that, dad.
They banished me to the land!
What are you talking about?!?
I'm talking about Collin Wallace.
The leader of the lobsters!
We were friends once.
Brothers, even!
Eleanor was in love with both of us.
So to end our famous feud, I let her go with him.
He took my wife AND my million dollars.
He was more of a man, than I'll ever be.
And he was a lobster!
Grandpa, you just - kind of don't ever know what the hell's going on, do you?
Lokk, uh - What I'm trying to tell you is: You can't just let your wife go!
You gotta fight for her if you want her!
Or you're gonna lose your whole family - to a bunch of lobsters.
Lobsters will play no significant role in my life.
Well - I'm just saying it could happen.
No, it couldn't, Titty Mitty.
Wha -
Well, it doesn't have to be - lobsters, it could be any kind of crustacean!
Crabs, goats...
It's a similar situation.
No, it isn't.
Why do you got to pick apart everything I say to you?
I don't even know, why  I'm trying to help you, I hate you.
Yeah, and then when I says to these sappy asses I says: If you're going down the trail to Oregon, this is the wagon you're gonna wanna be on. And he bought it! What a birdbrain, right?
Oh, general store guy, you're such a shiester!
Yeah - I sure am.
But I will never lie to you, doll face.
Come on.
Hey!
That's the general store guy, that sold me that lousy Wago 9000.
If I were any sort of - real husband or father, I'd march over there and - register a complaint.
Or ask for a refund.
Oh, leave him alone, look: he's with a friend.
No.
I have to do this.
For my family.
[clears his throat]
Hey, you!
You sold me a bad wagon!
No, I didn't.
The wagon you sold me - kept falling apart on us - and almost got my whole family killed!
And if it weren't for you - we'd be in Oregon by now!
So I think -
[clears his throat again]
I think - you owe me a refund or something.
[laughs]
Me - Bad Wagon - sell you - a bad wagon, okay, well: In your opinion it was a bad wagon, but are you a carpenter, sir?
Nope.
Then what the hell do you know about wagons anyways, you stupid idiot? No offense!
None taken.
Alright.
Since I'm such a nice guy -
[laughs about it himself]
Let me tell you, what I'm gonna do. Alright:
I am gonna fix you up with a new wagon. And boy, have I got the model for you!
It is a brand new unit, I just picked it up on my way into town - now, it was on fire when I found it...
But I'm gonna give it to you for half price, huh?
That's the exact same wagon we abandoned a month ago.
Yeah, but I'm giving it to you for half price.
WE ALREADY PAYED FOR IT!!!
I want a new - quality wagon - with wheels, that are circles - and I don't want any fancy upgrades, like a horny ox or a floor window.
Oh!
I want a sturdy wagon!
And I want it - for free!
[laughs]
They're right, you're funny, sir!
You are very funny, but please tell me: Why on earth would I ever give you a wagon for free?
Oh, bwuahaha! I didn't think this through!
Yes, it's crazy!
I wasn't using my brain!
Yeah, it's crazy.
I wasn't using my brain! Oh grandpa, I wasn't using my brain!
Grandpa, I wasn't thinking at all! Oh my god, why would he ever do that?
I don't know, it's - it's nuts...
Why would he ever do that? Oh, I don't know -
Because if you don't, I'll kill ya!
Whoa!
And I'll kill her too!
Gasp!
I'll do anything to save my family.
At first I was a moron
I stood a little too tall
And I didn't know I was close
To losing it all
Listen now, please.
[Loads the weapon]
Okay!
I burned our farm down by my own hand
If God did it, he's a sneaky man
But now it's time I take control of his plan
When the world's at stake
There are lives to save
And every rap I take
And every rule I break
I'm one step closer to my family
I can feel it in my bones
Lord, have mercy on my soul
As I take back what's all my own
Alright.
I'll give you anything you want, just don't hurt her!
Kill me instead.
Oh, general store guy!
What are you doing?
When the world's at stake
And there are lives to save
And, yes, I'm one big fake
But please cut me a break
Cause AAAAAAAAH
No!
You really were in for it there.
I know, that based on what you just saw, you wouldn't believe it, but - I played Toni in Independence's community theater's production of 'West Side Story' a couple of years back.
It's like - it's like big fish, small pond, but -
I was proud.
Alright, I want the b - I want the best wagon you got.
Alright, that would be my wagon, here the keys - jingle, jingle...
And I want food.
So much goddamn food my son could never eat it all.
Uhm, food, yeah, you got it, okay!
Alright, let's go to move on!
That means you too, grandpa!
Get!
Wait, good, alright.
Okay. I'm going.
Oh, I know you can move faster than that!
Alright, I'm trying. I'm proud of you, son.
But don't shoot me.
When my world's at stake
Come on, Crap-hole.
We gotta find our own way out of there.
We're gotta get ourselves a horse, or a mule - heck, we will hitchhike if we have to!
Come on, son, keep up!
Where is your goddamn shoe?
I should have stayed with dad.
Crap-hole!
Honey!
Dad?
I'm coming!
Jack Bauer!
What? Dad!
Trust me, I'm coming!
Oh my god!
Wait, is this a new wagon? Where on earth did this come from?
Whoa!
I did what I had to do.
Look, you're right about me, I'm a dog.
I'm a dumb, dumb happy-go-lucky dog.
But you know what else a dog is?
Dirty!
More positive.
Amazing!
Dogs are amazing!
And I will do anything - with zero regard for my own safety - to get this family to Oregon.
I'm not asking for you to forgive me.
I'm just asking for a chance to help get our daughter back.
It is a good wagon. It doesn't have a floor window, does it?
No - sorry!
That's alright!
Alright, scoot over!
Yeah?
Yes!
Alright, Dikrats:
If we're gonna catch up to McDoon and get our daughter back, we're gonna have to go down this trail like no one's ever gone before!
We are setting our rations to bare bones, and our pace to grueling! We are not stopping for nothing!
We are gonna blaze this trail all the way to Oregon!
We are gonna do - A speed run!
Yeah!
She went off like a bolt of lightning
Mad as hell and the pace was frightening
Every stop on the trail was left for dead
The legend around her spread
Like a weed in a flower bed
Her mission was clear straight ahead
She tempted fate to its limit
Pushing all of us hard through the night
If the weather so much as shifted
She scared it off with a knife
She went on a run, speed run
To save the future
Run, speed run
The woman I love had fire in her eyes
She went on a run, speed run
To save her daughter, now
Run, speed run
The woman I love's come back to life
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Speed run
Nothing that needs exploring
That part of the game is boring
Hold onto your butts and let me drive
Speed run
Time to reduce our rations
Rational is out of fashion
The queen bee is back to claim her hive
I know all of the shortcuts
Using my motherly sense
If I have the minds of the devil
Then speed's our only defense
Oh my god, there's a gap in the road!
It's a river, dad. It's called a river.
Well, what are we gonna do? Fort it?
No! We're gonna jump it!
What?
Aaaaah!
run, speed run
To the future
Fanning the flames of the demon inside
It's time to run, speed run
To save our daughter, now
Cause the slower you play the faster you die
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Nothing can stop us now
Oh, nothing can take us down
Who needs to stop and piss
When you're in the lead?
Can't stop us now
Oh, nothing can break us down
Who knew that all this time
We had what we need?
Faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster
Faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster... oh...
Oh, they call it a speed run
It's the story of one motherfucking family
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
So you're the other woman, huh?
What?
You must think, you're pretty hot stuff, cause McDoon was to make you his child bride.
But let me tell you something, sister:
I was here before you.
And I'll be here - looong - after you're gone.
All you are, is me 20 years younger.
And when McDoon's done messing around with you - he's going to come straight back - to me!
Wait - wait, uhm, uh - Mr. - Cletus Jones - uhm -
Look - look: I don't wanna come between you and your friend, so why don't you just - let me go - and - I'll leave, and - you will never see me again?
Oh no! You may be a home wrecker, but I'm not!
You are gonna marry McDoon, and you are one - lucky girl, cause he is the most amazing man I have ever met.
Woo! What a morning, huh?
I just took a big dump in the great Columbia river -
the river that all carries down to Oregon, and from there we'll head to Mexico -
that is, of course, if you'll agree to marry me.
Never!
Oh, come on!
I've been treating you real good, haven't I?
I keep your limbs bound with the finest rope money can buy,
I gently chloroform you to sleep every night,
and I promise, that's how it's gonna be every day once you're my child bride.
No, I would never even consider marrying you!
Until you changed your bad ways.
Oh, but I have!
No, uh! You almost killed my family!
And they could be dead for all I know, when I've been sitting in the back of a wagon, writing letters to nobody like a Jackass!
Alright, look:
I swear, your family is the last one I'll ever kill, okay?
I don't believe you.
You're gonna have to prove to me that you can change, and you can start by untying these ropes, please.
Ooooooooooooooooooo-
oh - Alright!
Okay.
There! I just -
You're happy?
Yes.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, shit! Goddamn it! Get her, Cletus!
Get her! Get her! Goddamit, [???]
Come here, [???] girl!
Oh there is some woods! Oh those are some heavy woods! I don't - Oh there she is!
Get out of the wood!
Get back here, [???] girl!
She's coming down the hill, [???] the rocks [???] -
Ooooh!
Wooooo!
Gotcha!
Uuuh!
Good thing I was there.
Good thing, Cletus!
Yeah, I got her!
You did good work, Cletus.
Alright, yeah.
You're a good partner.
Alright...
Well, woo, child bride!
Keep me on my toes, put them in.
Put them in there, yep! Oh, you keep me on my toes, child bride, I like that!
I like that a lot.
You're the kind of woman I can share my life with, you know what I mean?
Mi casa es su casa, huh?
[Spanish: My house is your house]
I don't speak Spanish.
Alright.
Well - now all we gotta do - is float our wagon - down the great Columbia river to that new life together.
How are we supposed to float a wagon? It's a wagon!
Ooooh! Oooooh!
Child bride!
We're gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day we die
But I don't wanna die.
That's why:
We're gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day we die
How in hell are we supposed to do that?
Well, you see that ox?
Uhu.
He's an ox, of course
Yep.
And he took us down the trail
But his time is up, cause he won't help us, unless he grows a sail
His time is up
Unless he grows a sail
Iiiiiiiiiiih!!!
Come on now!
You can do it!
He didn't grow a sail
So chop him up, remove his guts
and then grind up all his hooves
We'll mix it up into a pulp
And spread it on like glue
We'll chop him up
And mix him into glue
You'll caulk this up
this ox has died for you
Come on, let's do this!
Wait, wait, why don't we just make a raft, huh?
A raft?
Cause, uh, that takes weeks of labor and chopping up lots of wood, Mouthface!
Do you wanna chop up all that wood, Mouthface?
No...
Well then -
could we just please do this?
Now spread the caulk on thick
To seal out the water
Now blow on it real quick
It has a real strange odor
Why did we leave home in the first place?
I'm springing leaks all over my face
A higher power steers me true
Now let me do the same for you
I see this trip has taken its toll
Now let me fill your holes
He's gonna - caulk your wagon, Mouthface
Until the day you die
Woo! Now that's how you caulk the wagon!
Alright, everybody! Now - we -
[Sounds of something dropping]
[A long time, actually...]
Didn't know there was a ridge there.
Alright, on the count of three we're gonna push you off!
I'm knowing this...
One -
two -
three! We're off!
Until the day we die
Caulk your wagon, caulk your wagon, caulk your wagon
Aaaaaaah!
Oh god damn it! We hit a rock and the wagon's destroyed, we're going down the river!
[more screaming]
We're gonna die!!!!
[ongoing screaming]
Wait! Mr. McDoon! A rock!
McDoon! Help!!!
Oh! I got you, Cletus Jones, just hold on!
McDoon, we're going down! I just wanna tell you...
Shut your mouth, Cletus!
Everything's gonna be just fine!
We've gotten out of worse craps than this!
I mean, this can't be the end of -
The Bandit King! Oh shit! God damn it! God, no!
Noooo!
Oh no!
They're dead!
And I'm out here all alone in the middle of the great Columbia river!
The most dangerous river in the world!
I never should have wished my family away!
In fact: I wish they were here right now!
We ARE here, Mouthface!
Mama!
Crap-hole!
Daddy?
Come on, Jack Bauer, we gotta do something!
There's only one thing to do:
We have to ford the river ourselves.
Alright, everyone!
Strap yourselves in, this is the great Columbia river! The most dangerous river in the world!
No wait, hold on, listen, mom! Listen:
I'm all for a quick skinny dip, but - if we go in there we could die.
Remember what - remember what everyone in Independence said?
Friends don't let friends ford the river!
We're not friends!
We are family!
Now get this wagon into that raging river!
Alright.
Here we go!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh no!
The waves are really picking up now!
Mama!
Come on!
What I said before -
about not needing you -
Oh, Mouthface, none of that matters anymore, just take my hand!
Uh-oh, gang -
Look at that!
There's a huge boulder straight ahead!
We're gonna crash!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[Inhales air]
[Caughs]
I thought I drowned for sure.
How did I -
You!
Hello.
Titty Mitty.
Collin Wallace!
You saved us!
Why?
It wasn't for you, grandpa.
It was for Eleanor.
How is she these days?
She passed.
two years ago, come April.
This doesn't change anything.
I know, grandpa.
I know.
Grandpa?
Oh, kids!
Who were you talking to, dad?
Oh, just an old -
friend.
Woo!
That was some crash!
Well, looks like we lost about 500 pounds of food, 30 boxes of bullets and the wagon's gone to bits.
But what matters, family - is: We're finally here!
What?
See that golden glow over that ridge yonder? Where the sky is the bluest blue you ever seen in your life?
That, family - is Oregon.
Oregon...
I can see it.
It looks like the state line's about a hundred yards that way.
We made it.
We made it!
WE MADE IT!!!
Alright, gang, what are we waiting for? Come on!
Let's go!
Let's get this fucking trip over with!
Alright, everyone, hold hands!
We're not losing anybody!
Not again!
That's right, nothing can stop us now!
Come on!
We're almost there -
The state line!
Once we've crossed this threshold - everything will be fine!
Let's get this done!
Hey! Hold on a second!
Come on!!!
God damn it! What now?
I'm sorry, ma'am, this will take but a moment.
Hello, pioneers, you're right about to enter Oregon, the land of fortune, glory, promise and opportunity, but -
before I let you in, I have to give you all a quick medical examination to make sure that none of you have Dysentery, hm?
What?
Dy - Dysentery?
That's right, ma'am, it's running rampant all throughout the trail and we just wanna keep Oregon nice and clean, you know?
Oh, that's ridiculous!
We're all fine.
Ha, I'm sure you are, Ma'am.
I'm sure you are!
But this will take but a moment, don't worry. In fact I can do it from right over here, I've got a pretty good eye for these types of things.
Mom, I'm scared.
It's alright, everything is gonna be alright!
Alright, yep, everything looks pre -
OH MY GOD!
I'm sorry!
But one of you's got Dysentery!
And you got it real bad!
No, this isn't fair.
We've come so far!
We did our best!
I know, and I'm sorry, ma'am, but -
this is just an act of God.
[sighs]
Well, without further ado -
The family member dying of Dysentery tonight is - drum roll, please!