Do you know, what this means, family?
No more farming or starving or rotten luck!
That's right, because we made it to Oregon in one piece.
But more importantly:
We're rich!
And we know what that means!
Come on buddy, the water's just right
So come on buddy, let's have a water fight.
Splashy, splashy, there's nothing more fun
Then dropping trou' and getting some sun
You can skinny if you're fat or old
Put Marco Polo in a wrestling hold
There's his penis.
All your problems wash away
When you're naked, yeah you're naked in a lake.
Come on guys, it's super warm!
Oh, I don't know about this - okay!
Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel the water between your toes
Everybody swim, take a mini vacay wearing only your birthday clothes
I promise I won't judge if you've got freckles or some pudge
'Cuz their just one way to spend the rest of the day
Getting naked, yeah let's get naked, get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
Naked in a -
We're naked in a lake
Come on, Mouthface
I know you want to
I can finally lose this dress
Come on, grandpa
Water's good for you
I beat you to it, my diaper's wet
It's nothing super sexual
'Cuz the act is nothing actual
It's time to free your little guy and let him play
And have the time of your life starting today
Woo! Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel your body jingle jangle
Everybody's got fins and it's super cool when you're taking off your sandals
So if life ever gets you stressed
Find some woods and take a bath
And get naked
Aaaah
Yeah, let's get
Naked in a lake
Yabadabadoo!
Let's get naked
Aaaah
Yeah
Let's get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
They did it in Ancient Rome
It's everybody's oldest story
You can even do it alone
Just you in all your glory
Everybody come out, dunk your head, see how long you can hold your breath
Everybody come out
You can even use toys
You can even use toys, like a floating raft with a sexual orgy fest
You can do it in the dark, but it's way better when you see your parts
And I wouldn't have it any other way
Being naked, yeah super naked, we're naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
We're naked in a lake
We're naked in a -
We are rich in Oreg-ich
But who cares?
'Cuz we're naked - yeah, we're naked - in a lake
Alright, kids!
Go pick out your favorite [???].
What about you, dad?
I'm right behind you.
Come on, Jack Bauer, the water's just right
Be right there, honey.
[Laughs]
We are gone to Oregon
It's the greatest family vacation...