You, son!
Noooooo!
No! Not my Crap-hole!
Oh!
If given the chance to kill anyone of us, who would chose one of the children?
It's alright, mom, it's okay.
I'm going to heaven now.
Or maybe I don't have a soul.
Either way, it was God's will.
And we all know that God is a -
vicious two faced prick!
I guess it's a good thing, that I'm the one dying.
I'd rather die than get in trouble for losing that shoe.
Speaking of which:
Mouthface, will you do something for me?
Yeah, anything.
Take off my other shoe, please.
Now toss it over there.
Oh yeah, that bounces pretty good.
Good bye, dad.
Looks like you're mom's only son now.
N- no, you - you're mom's son, I'm the father, remember?
Right! The father.
The oldest son.
Good bye, grandpa.
Go to the light, son.
I don't see a light.
I just see a skeleton in a rope, going: 'Come here! Come here!'
Well, you might as well do what he says.
Well, I guess it makes sense, that I'm the one dying of dysentery.
I shouldn't have put all that shit in my mouth.
Especially that shit!
Alright, family.
Gather around.
And remember:
When the darkness surrounds you
And the light is all but out
There's still a fire, deep inside you
That will find the nearest route
[Sounds of farting start and continue throughout the whole song, increasing]
It starts as a whisper
You feel a rumbling and itching at your soul
You can't hold it any longer
As the urge keeps growing stronger
And then you know
You gotta go when you gotta go
Close your eyes, give it a shove
Go, you've gotta go
It's time to let go of your love
The time we had together
Is all that I have left
Go! Go! Go!
'Til you can't go anymore
[Extreme farting sounds]
Oh! ou! Ou! Ou! Ou! Ou! Ou!
Wait, I might just make it
I found my second wind
The pain's not bad I can take it
I think I can hold it in
Help me to my feet
You will have to carry me
Nope!
Put me down
My limbs are growing weak
Is this the end I seek?
Ooh, I guess there's more
I saw a porcelain door
But there's one last thing to say
So come real close
You gotta go when you gotta go
It's time to get the hell out of here
Go! Get, get, get go!
I don't want a single tear
Ou!
I'll always be inside you
Even when I'm all dried up
Go! Go! Go!
Till you caaaaaaaaaaan't -
[extreme farting sounds]
Ou! Ou! It burns! Ou!
anymore
[farting continues...]
No.
This isn't right.
We were supposed to make it to Oregon as a family.
Dad -
Crap-hole is dead!
Dead or alive, -
we're all gonna make it to Oregon together.
Come on, help me.
We're not gonna give those watchers the satisfaction.
Not today!
Come on! Help me. Damn you, watchers!
Damn you all to hell!
There.
There, you see, Crap-hole?
We did it.
We all made it to Oregon.
Together!
You - you're alive!
Crap- hole?
But - but, but how?
I felt myself - falling into a deep black nothingness.
But then I - I felt the crisp, clean Oregon air fill my lungs, and -
it must have brought me back to life!
It's a Christmas miracle!
Look, everybody:
The sun is rising over the great Willamette Valley.
It's beautiful!
But dad -
What are we gonna do now?
Starting new.
Claim a little crop of land for ourselves.
Yes children, it will be hard at first.
But very soon we will have a farm all our own with crops as far as the eye can see.
Yeah! And maybe we can finally get a cow for that horny ox.
Hahaha, yes, please!
And who knows - I had a hell of a time robbing that general store owner.
Maybe I'll take up the mental of - the Bandit King.
Dad - Are you gonna lead a life of crime now?
Of course I am, honey.
That's what this trip's all about.
Wait - wait a minute, what's this in my pocket?
What is it, dad?
Well, a bill.
Collin Wallace, you sh-icken c-it (chicken shit) son of a bitch!
Gather around, family!
He gave me back my fortune! Just look!
A million dollar bill!
Do you know, what this means, family?
No more farming or starving or rotten luck!
That's right, because we made it to Oregon in one piece.
But more importantly:
We're rich!
And we know what that means!
Come on buddy, the water's just right
So come on buddy, let's have a water fight.
Splashy, splashy, there's nothing more fun
Then dropping trou' and getting some sun
You can skinny if you're fat or old
Put Marco Polo in a wrestling hold
There's his penis.
All your problems wash away
When you're naked, yeah you're naked in a lake.
Come on guys, it's super warm!
Oh, I don't know about this - okay!
Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel the water between your toes
Everybody swim, take a mini vacay wearing only your birthday clothes
I promise I won't judge if you've got freckles or some pudge
'Cuz their just one way to spend the rest of the day
Getting naked, yeah let's get naked, get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
Naked in a -
We're naked in a lake
Come on, Mouthface
I know you want to
I can finally lose this dress
Come on, grandpa
Water's good for you
I beat you to it, my diaper's wet
It's nothing super sexual
'Cuz the act is nothing actual
It's time to free your little guy and let him play
And have the time of your life starting today
Woo! Everybody jump in, come and splash around, feel your body jingle jangle
Everybody's got fins and it's super cool when you're taking off your sandals
So if life ever gets you stressed
Find some woods and take a bath
And get naked
Aaaah
Yeah, let's get
Naked in a lake
Yabadabadoo!
Let's get naked
Aaaah
Yeah
Let's get naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
They did it in Ancient Rome
It's everybody's oldest story
You can even do it alone
Just you in all your glory
Everybody come out, dunk your head, see how long you can hold your breath
Everybody come out
You can even use toys
You can even use toys, like a floating raft with a sexual orgy fest
You can do it in the dark, but it's way better when you see your parts
And I wouldn't have it any other way
Being naked, yeah super naked, we're naked in a lake
Naked in a lake
We're naked in a lake
We're naked in a -
We are rich in Oreg-ich
But who cares?
'Cuz we're naked - yeah, we're naked - in a lake
Alright, kids!
Go pick out your favorite stretch of land.
What about you, dad?
I'm right behind you.
Come on, Jack Bauer, the water's just right
Be right there, honey.
[Laughs]
We are gone to Oregon
It's the greatest family vacation...