Sigh. Joey Richter. Late again in the nick of time.
Jeepers, that Joey Richter really makes me feel funny.
Right here.
And right here!
Is it hot out here or is it just me?
Oh, Miss Cooter, it's just you.
I am not hot at all in any sense of the word.
Sure?
Cause I'm sure the spring's sun is burning particularly bright this morning.
Oh, I could go for a tall glass of lemonade.
I'm sweating like a stuck pig.
Miss Cooter, it's got nothing to do with temperature.
You're just excitable.
And a bit ancy.
And frustrated!
What? Why?
Because, Sally...
Everyday when we go to school, and we're walking down the halls...
Or changing in the locker room, I see all the other girls with their little Miss Cooters.
And they seem so happy and free.
I don't know. A flutter to the [???].
Miss Cooter, we can't do stuff like other girls.
I mean, just in case you haven't noticed, I'm kind of a freak of nature.
I mean I'm gangly and I got these big dumb feet.
I'm like the ugly duckling.
Except I'll never turn into a swan.
I'm just an ugly duck.
Well that's your problem right there, Miss Sally. It's that attitude of yours.
You act like you've been licked before you even started the [???].
Well, I guess I could try to be more positive.
That's the spirit.
And you tell me: What is one thing that you desire most of this whole cosmos.
Well...
Come on, Sally. Just say it.
You've got a god damn shrine devoted to him in your closet.
Joey Richter.
You should snatch him up like the last bit of cheese cake.
I don't know, Miss Cooter. I don't think he likes me like that.
Why would he?
Look at me with my pigtails to tight,
you'd think that I might explode, right?
Look at me with my arms in a twist,
not alarming I miss the right road.
It's not too late to turn around and find a better way.
It's not up to fate to lay the groundwork for a better day.
You gotta shake it up, put your hair down darlin'
You really need to unwind.
I've gotta pick it up cause my life is calling me on the other line.
It's time to start over, and today is like the first day of the year.
So get that chip off my shoulder.
Cause it's weighing me down and keeping you right here.
I want to get out see the great big world out there.
It's time to set out cause I feel:
There's something in the air.
I might be loosing my mind but there's one thing that I know.
That I'm finally ready - so ready to go.
Yeah, I'm finally ready...
Woo, there she goes, y'all!
I'm ready to...
Yo! You're ready to go or what?
Yes, alright. Let's go!
Fine Miss Sally. There he is. You gotta show what you're made of.
Um... um... Joey?
Um... I wanted to ask you - um...
If you - um...
You see, this is exactly what I'm talking about. It's like: Um neah - Salad!
I wanted to know if -
If you want to be chemistry partners with me.
Poetry. That will sure set his heart on fire. Come on!
Yeah. Sure, sure.
Great. Okay, well we're supposed to do this project on several  of the elements on the periodic table...
Well, and I was thinking if we could do one on a soluble compound, such as...
Silver nitrate, for example. AgNO3.
Except we could make ours fun and interesting...
because we could do a film noir detective type story...
- Hey Dick, does my hair look alright?
- Hell yeah, buddy you're a sight to see.
K' good.
Listen up, just try to relax, cause a mishap's last thing I need.
I wanna rise up to the next level - get of this middle ground.
I got this yearning burning like the devil, I'm here for the rebound.
Pass the ball. I know I'm on fire.
Yeah, yeah. You're on a roll.
I know.
What do you want from your kingdom, Sire?
I wanna take control!
Hyoo!
I need a brand new game plan.
No more warming benches like I've done before.
Just get your head in the game man. Here's what I'm thinking.
Shit! She's coming out that door.
Ah ah ah ah ah
Say yes! Vanessa yes! I must confess of my obsession...
With your design.
I will not rest. No not unless I find a way...
To make you mine.
Sigh.
I'm gonna get her if it's the last thing that I'll do.
But just remember you can't get her without me too.
So buckle up all you amateurs cause today we're going pro.
We're finally ready (Yeah!) So ready to go!
And it's only when the silver and the nitrogen find all three oxygens...
That they're able to solve the case.
Joey? Have you been listening to anything I've been saying?
Yeah, yeah. It's awesome. Awesome.
Sigh, Joey Richter. Okay, let's go to home room.
Hello.