Sally, sugar, when you're done with that, we've gotta figure out what we're gonna do with Joey.
I'm all a flutter in the gutter, if you know what I mean.
Oh, Miss Cooter, I don't know what to say to him.
Well, it's easy. You say: "Joseph Michael Richter. ...
... I am desperately in love with you. If you had half a brain, ...
...you would sweep me off my feet and carry me to some Caribbean isle...
...and make wild passioned love to me, ...
...‘till I die a naked and sexy death."
I mean to ask him if he wants to study tonight.
[???] a girl approve a pussy for good. But alright.
- Joey?
- Yeah?
Ugh! Hey, man. Who ordered the salad, right?
Please, don't touch me with your penis!
Joey Richter touched me with his dick.
I heard Joey Richter ate his [???] once, ‘cause his dick told him to.
I heard Joey Richter cries in the choir room.
Gosh, he's such a loser!
- Looks like an old lesbian.
- Yeah!
- Dick!
- I'm sorry, What...?
- Joey?  - I, uhm...
- What?!?
Carib - bean sex! Caribbean SEX!
I wanna have Caribbean study with you!
Tell ya: ...
that's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
One thing: I'm not even in ‘world cultures' with you, okay?
Weren't you talking about some chemistry project earlier, though?
- Uhm, yeah, I...
- Did somebody say: chemistry project?
‘Cause we were just discussing it.
- So who you guys gonna partner with?
- Well, actually Joey and I were gonna...
Vanessa needs a partner really, really bad, you guys.
No more partners, please!
So yeah, Joey, I was thinking...
I was thinking, we could partner up.
Whoa, what the, what the, what the, what about...
What about Rick?
Well, - Rick and I broke up, actually.
Whoot?!?
Oh yeah, and aren't you parents gone all weekend?
That would be a perfect time for you and Joey to work on this alone...
...in the master bedroom. You know, the one with the mirror on the ceiling.
- Mirrors? Her parents are kinky, man!
- I know.
That's an inherited trait.
This is what they were talking ‘bout in chemistry class. I knew it!
Okay, Joey. This is the most important day of our life.
Don't fuck it up!
Nessy and I would be partners, but sometimes a teacher is against you...
...when you work with your bff. And they grade you better, ...
...when you work with someone you don't like. So I was thinking, we should work together, Sally.
- Well, actually Joey and I....
- You know what? I think that sounds great.
I think, I couldn't think of a more convenient pairing for anyone involved.
Yeah, great. So you can come over to me after school and start working, if you want.
So...
...come over around five?
Yes, good.
See you then.
My God, it's unbelievable!
Man, that's the most incredible thing that ever happened.
Do not let the spoil off the hook, Miss Sally!
Sally!
Thank you so much!
You don't know how big this is for me.
I mean I've had the biggest, secretest crush on Vanessa for as long as I can remember.
And you know, when you are gonna school project with someone, there is just so much more going on there.
You know? I imagine, this is who most married couples met.
By working on school-projects, just like these.
Thank you so much for giving all that up, so I can have that with Vanessa and not with you. Thank you!
No problem, Joey.
- Anything for you.
- Yes!
- No!
You're amazing.
Oh.
- I'm sorry, I didn't...
- Gee, its fine.
- I mean, I hope you...
- I'm alright.
- I didn't mean to...
- My name's Miss Cooter.
I'm Dick.
- You've been here before, I think.
- Who, me?
- You slip by each time I blink.
- Couldn't be.
Yes, I've seen you around here before.
- I thought that you never looked.
- What? How?
- But I knew, that I was hooked.
- Now, now.
Yes, I've seen you around here before.
All the time just knowing. Not knowing how I knew.
I've had a funny feeling about you.
Thinking it was hopeless, I told love, adieu.
But when we touched ...
...and you came into view.
All the time just knowing. Not knowing how I knew.
I've had a funny feeling about you.
Always wanting something. That something was you.
- I've never felt quite like this.
- Is that true?
I could be about to piss!
Look at you.
Yes, I've seen you around here...
...be-
-fore.
Joey Richter.
What is this? What are you doing?
This guy has a boner now!
- Joey Richter is wiener-wild!
- Damn it!
I gotta go, bye!
Woah! Did you feel that?
Do you mean that little prig? I keep his arrow on my butthole.
Yeah, it felt good.