Yeah, so - come on in.
Okay.
Alright. Let's get this over with.
Do you wanna sit down?
- Yeah.
Ah... so I thought that while we are working on the project we could drink a few of these.
They're beers.
- Woah! You've got beers?
- Yeah, it's no big deal. Here you go.
Take the beer! You love beers.
I love beer. I would love to drink this beer with you.
It's an O'Doul's.
Oh, O'Doul's. I heart that's a great brand.
Yeah, they're awesome.
Cheers.
Oh, I've already had have one of these. I'm...
...already feeling buzzed.
- Yeah! I love getting buzzed of beer.
- Oh yeah, me too.
When I drink beer, I just lose all my inhibitions and start doing the craziest things.
- Like anybody could do whatever they wanted to me.
- Yeah.
Like have sex for example.
It would be fun and easy to do for whoever was interested.
Oh, alright.
Joey, that sounds like an "in". But be careful.
Girls are easily threatened.
Don't worry.
No one is gonna have sex with you while I'm here.
No matter how many beers you drink.
Do you wanna start working on this project?
Yes, I would enjoy that.
Dick!
- Dick, her knee is touching my knee!
- Cool it, man!
We don't want to be too far into this.
Hold back a little bit and see if she does it again.
- Vanessa, I'm beginning to like this boy.
- Shut up!
Do you want me to get you a back-scratch?
- No, we're fine.
- No, thanks.
Looks like things are going swimmingly, Joey.
Vanessa, sweety. I don't think this is gonna work.
- I'm just gonna go ahead and turn in, okay?
- No, thanks.
- Desperate times call for desperate measures.
- What?!?
I think there's some chemistry between us.
It was very ambiguous.
I wanna have sex with you.
- She wants to have sex with us!
- She does?
- Yeah!
- Nice, I did it!
So are we gonna do it or what?
Yeah, yeah. We're gonna do it. We're gonna have sex!
Uhm... now what we gonna do?
- Oh, me?
- Yeah.
Right.
Because I'm the dick...
So I have the sex.
That's good, ‘cause I know how to do the sex.
Step one...
...is to take your pants off.
Mmmm...
Step one complete, Joey.
Alright, ahem... step two is just to...
...grab her booby. No wait!
Slap her booby.
No soft!
Kiss her!
Okay, now that she's all hot and bother...
...just uhm...
...ask her where she wants to do it.
Where would you like to have sex with me?
I don't know, I was thinking of on the bed?
Come here!
Hey.
So now we go have the sex.
You know, Joey, if you're not ready for this, ...
...maybe we could play quick and risk, ‘cause there's the onyx edition over there.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
Okay, now we're here.
This is the hot Jewish bed.
Awesome.
We're gonna have sex, Joey!
Hello?!? Hello [echo]? Hello.
I guess, I'll just light match.
-Ohhh!!!
- Arrr!
Why, hello there, you [???] penis.
Oh, hi. I mean...
Hello.
Hello yourself. Now get over here. Let's get this over with.
Oh, okay. Uhm...
I'm gonna fuck you.
Yeah.
Now?
- Sure, come on!
- Okay.
Oh right.
You've been here before, I think.
You slip by each time I blink.
- Yes...
- I'm not gonna fucking sing with you!
God! Just get in here, we go around, and get out!
- Oh - just wiggle?
- Yeah, what's the matter with you?
Okay, we're going. I can do that. I can do that.
- Alright, come on! Get over here and do it already!
- Okay.
Let's do it.
Wait! What's the...?
- Oh, no...
- Now, penis! Penis, come in!
- No, I tripped!
- I don't believe you.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Wait. What...?
- Hey, what's the big idea, here, penis?
- Alright.
Joey, is there - is there something wrong with you?
No.
I'm probably just drunk from all those beers we drank.
Yeah, yep that's it.
Ahem... one second! One second, I'll be right back!
What's going on down here?
I don't know! It's wired. She's like Medusa, but the opposite.
Well, come on, man! You just gotta get your head in the game. Come on!
- Okay, okay. Just get my head in the game!
- Listen, penis: hurry up! I don't have all night!
One second, ...
Ms. Pussy.
Okay.
- Great. You're ready, dude?
- I'm ready.
Can I have a quick back-rub?
- Alright, okay! Let's do it!
- Awesome!
Alright, penis.
I've decided to make this easy for you.
Is this better?
Does this look good to you?
Not gonna have any problems now, are you?
Alright. Alright. Yeah. On the count of three?
- Get in me!
- Alright.
Three, ...
- two...
- Come on! What are you doing?!?
You've gotta be kidding me.
- Dick, that is the hot little Jewish girl up there.
- I know, don't pressure me.
No, I'm gonna pressure you! After you fucked up my life this far...
- ...I'm not gonna let you fuck this up!
- Don't yell at me!
- Work, god, damn you!
- Joey, Joey!
As much fun as it is watching you shake your wiener around in my parent's bed, ...
it is starting to gross me out.
- You've gotta go!
- What?!?
Uh, I knew this was such a bad idea.
No, it was a good idea.
Please, Joey! Just...  just... just...
Get out of my house!