- Hey, how is it going?
- Oh gross, it's dick!
- Hey, what's happening?
- Eww, is that a wiener?
- Hello.
- I would never...
Well word, here I am.
Footloose and fancy free.
A dick on the town.
Yeah, who needs Joey anyway, huh?
He did nothing but slow me down.
Now I can do all those things I always wanted to do.
Hey, excuse me.
Um, do you know how to find the house of one Miss Cooter?
Fuck you!
Hey!
Well, fuck you too, huh!
I don't need your help!
I don't need anybody's help.
I'll do this on my own.
All I gotta do is find Joey's street.
All I gotta do is orient myself.
Wit the sun.
Which I know rises on the north.
Which puts the mars on the south-side of the trees.
So, all I have to do is..
had to do is...
No that's - also wrong.
What was that?
Oh no.
I'm lost.
I'm a lost dick.
I'm the world's only lost dick.
How many time do I got to tell you, huh?
Can't you even read the sign?
No dicks!
This is an outrage.
And look. He got dirt all over my new...
genuine, 80% cotton,100% cool, leather jacket.
I ever see that guy again, ...
I'll pry open his mouth and pee in it!
Check out this sorry piece of shit over here.
Well, if I hadn't know any better, I'd say that was a dick.
And he looks lost.
What do you say we go help, brother?
I fine humanitarian like myself has always got time for a dick in need.
Hey, brother.
- What brings you over on these side of the [???]?
- Other dicks!
- Hi. Are you talking to me?
- No shit, dick.
I said what brings you out here all by alone, son?
Actually, I'm looking for a friend of mine.
Her name is Miss Cooter. Have you seen her?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
We've seen her. In fact, I think I saw her through that alleyway right over there.
- Right through that alleyway?
- Right through that alleyway. Right there.
Thanks guys.
Wow, today is my lucky day.
Hey, Miss Cooter.
Wait, that's just a curtain.
Get him!
-  Make him shake his balls!
- You heard Weenie! Shake!
Yeah.
- My balls!
- Making those balls shake.
Get out of here! This is our turf.
Jeez.
Who would have thought the first dicks I'd meet would be so mean?
That was fun.
I can't believe we made him shake his balls.
That'll teach him to fuck with us!
Oh shucks, Big T.
I think we hurt his feelings.
Yeah, you're right, Weenie.
Let's go talk to him.
And not make fun of him this time.
- Hey, wait up, friend.
- Hey there, brother.
Woah, woah. I'm not your friend!
And I ain't your brother!
Hey, we're sorry for acting so sour.
We've been just putting you through the wringer, that's all.
- The name's Big T.
- Yeah, and I'm Weenie.
Hi, I'm Dick.
- Cool.
- Hello.
What kind of trouble you're getting into tonight, Dick?
I don't know. I've never been down here before.
Oh, that's okay. We'll help you find your way home.
Well, actually, I don't have a home.
Not any more.
Well look at this noobie.
Yeah, look at this noobie bitch.
Hey, Weenie! I thought we said we wasn't gonna make fun of this bitch!
Now, look.
Just because you lost your guy don't mean you gotta be all alone.
Yeah. Look at me and Big T.
- We're a team.
- That's right.
We've been together ever since I rescued Weenie from a bird.
It was trying to eat me.
He taught Weenie were the worm.
A tiny little baby worm.
I swear, sometimes I can still hear his wings flapping.
He had a taste of my balls and now he wants the rest of me.
Weenie, you shut your dumbass mouth.
Now, listen.
Why don't you hang out with our group for a little bit?
We show you a place where a lot of lost dicks getting along.
You mean you guys are saying that there are other lost dicks out there?
You bet.
And we've got a place all to ourselves.
Yes.
-  Just smell this.
- Why..
Guys?
Guys?!?
You look a little lost, kid.
- You look a little scared.
- A little.
You look a little worried, kid.
A little unprepared.
You seem a little flaccid, kid.
It seems you've lost your wood.
Did you come here alone, kid?
You look misunderstood.
Let me guess.
Your masters gone astray?
No one around to sit and play?
No one to make you spurt and spray?
Well, today's your lucky day.
There's a warm, secluded place
where a dick can feel at home!
With miles of open space
where dicks are free to roam!
Got no time for your selfish owner
He sure missed out on a quality boner
Don't worry you'll get your kicks 'cause
You just stumbled into the land of the dicks!
You can let your hair grow out
there's nobody to make you trim!
You can flop or go kerplop
when you're everybody's favorite limb
You don't need to get total action
when you've got scrotal satisfaction
You can come anytime and get your fix
at a hot little joint called the land of the dicks!
A hot little joint called the land of the dicks!
That's right, bitches.
It's the land of the lost dicks.
Your leader: Big Tallywacker.
Cocks from far and wide
Oh, they lay down at my side
I take them in, and wipe their tears away
You may be lost now, Dick
but you're one lucky prick
We'll make a one-eyed king of you today!
- Some are big.
- And some are small.
- Some are slobs.
- And some well dressed.
- There are dicks of every kind.
- It's a regular sausage fest.
You have miles at your disposal if you wanna go pissin'.
The golden rain flows as you watch it glisten.
You can come anytime and get your fix
at a hot little joint called the land of the dicks!
Just do like me, kid.
- I said pee-pee....
- Pee-pee.....
- Ding dong.
- Me Tallywacker.
- You Tallywacker.
- Schloong.
-  Trouser snake.
- Private eye.
- Wing dang doodle.
- Sausage. - Choade. - Cock.
- Dick.
Foreskin, no skin, everyone's in!
There's a warm, secluded place
where a dick can feel at home!
With miles of open space
where dicks are free to roam!
Got no time for your selfish owner
He sure missed out on a quality boner
Don't worry you'll get your kicks...
You can come and get your fix...
It's time to mingle and mix 'cause
you just stumbled in to the land...
Of the dicks!